[	O
Innovation	O
]	O
The	O
best	O
ideas	O
come	O
from	O
people	O
closest	O
to	O
the	O
customer	O
:	O
http://t.co/tM0oN6JLB3	O

I	O
should	O
get	O
something	O
like	O
this	O
and	O
stick	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
my	O
door	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
whilst	O
im	O
doing	O
my	O
workout	O
http://t.co/lF2uF7VOyH	O

RT	O
@VintagePickles	O
:	O
#Vintage	B-product
Hand	O
-	O
Carved	O
/	O
Painted	O
#Wooden	O
#Jaguar	O
Head	O
Mexico	B-place
/	O
Central	O
Amer	O
.	O
#Tribal	O
!	O
http://t.co/js9hrSIXCa	O
via	O
@eBay	O

"	O
@AllforATL	O
:	O
Everyone	O
send	O
me	O
their	O
favorite	O
picture	O
of	O
"	O
fetus	O
"	O
young	O
ATL	O
for	O
a	O
shoutout	O
and	O
an	O
RT	O
.	O
"	O
This	O
one	O
omf	O
http://t.co/8nnoOCEjEa	O

RT	O
@Phil_Cosby_	O
:	O
Can	O
anyone	O
explain	O
or	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/Kwz2YnwxuP	O

@RBKillersComic	O
the	O
rich	O
family	O
.	O
Aunt	B-person
Bedelia	I-person
murdered	O
her	O
father	O
with	O
an	O
ash	O
tray	O
.	O
"	O
I	O
want	O
my	O
cake	O
!	O
"	O

@davidwford	O
@Yorkie71	O
thanks	O
for	O
sending	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
looking	O
into	O
it	O
and	O
will	O
come	O
back	O
to	O
you	O

Mulk	O
Bhar	O
K	O
15	O
Lakh	O
Hol	O
Sales	O
Or	O
Parchun	O
Farosho	O
Pr	O
Tax	O
Lagany	O
Ka	O
Imkan	O
FBR	O
Ny	O
Rs	O
.	O
10	O
,	O
000	O
Salana	O
K	O
Hisab	O
Sy	O
Tax	O
Ayed	O
Krny	O
Ki	O
Jajveez	O
Shoro	O

@Cicil_JTK48	O
iya	O
,	O
tau	O
aja	O
pens	O
;	O
3	O
wkwk	O

@Rapunzel_A	O
I	O
try	O
.	O
Bramsch	O
3a	O
whatsapp	O
&	O
gt	O
;	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O

@Jack_love_Elsa	O
*	O
she	O
blushes	O
*	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
sis	O
?	O

RT	O
@Linnilulu	O
:	O
@NWDogRescue	O
@BrianneTV	O
#luckypants	O
will	O
be	O
on	O
and	O
all	O
paws	O
crossed	O
for	O
Major	O
xx	O

Missouri	B-place
and	O
Kansas	B-place
join	O
crush	O
to	O
meet	O
Monday	O
health	O
care	O
deadline	O
:	O
Missouri	B-place
and	O
Kansas	B-place
residents	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
f	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/oJSMvyuady	O

Mike	B-person
WiLL	O
Made	O
It	O
Introduces	O
Rae	B-product
Sremmurd	I-product
+	O
K	B-person
.	I-person
Camp	I-person
Says	O
He	O
Likes	O
To	O
"	O
T	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
:	O
http://t.co/M7JGtCTnyY	O
via	O
@YouTube	O

RT	O
@GazetteUMass	O
:	O
UMass	O
was	O
a	O
No.	O
6	O
seed	O
in	O
both	O
the	O
A	O
-	O
10	O
and	O
NCAA	B-other
Tournaments	I-other

RT	O
@ant0nella__	O
:	O
Someone	O
tell	O
Mike	B-person
Trout	I-person
that	O
I'm	O
single	O
.	O

RT	O
@CODEBeautiful	O
:	O
@HarveyNichols	O
Liverpool	B-place
come	O
and	O
chat	O
to	O
Sarah	B-person
about	O
fab	O
#lashes	O
x	O
http://t.co/esRrahif5e	O

RT	B-organization
@mauryasarker	O
:	O
@SabinaYRahman	O
I	O
think	O
sometimes	O
it's	O
time	O
for	O
judicial	O
rule	O
in	O
India	B-place
,	O
maybe	O
the	O
Supreme	B-organization
Court	I-organization
should	O
run	O
the	O
country	O

my	O
voice	O
is	O
fucked	O
life	O
ain't	O
fair	O

@DemiLeigh__	O
@majidaaa_	O
I	O
know	O
right	O
stupid	O
boys	O

Tryna	O
be	O
better	O
than	O
everybody	O
thats	O
better	O
than	O
everybody	O
!	O
Rep	O
Detroit	B-place
everybody	O
!	O
Detroit	O
vs	O
everybody	O
!	O
http://t.co/zBH3DB4J9b	O

CEO	O
van	O
Grinsven	O
is	O
#Engaging	O
team	O
at	O
Cancer	B-organization
Centers	I-organization
of	I-organization
America	I-organization
to	O
"	O
Engage	O
,	O
Innovate	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
grow	O
"	O
#change	O
@	O
successful	O
biz	O
#acmp2014	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

The	O
Strokes	O
,	O
Call	O
me	O
back	O
.	O

RT	O
@KCoGoing	O
:	O
What's	O
going	O
on	O
KC	O
?	O
Customer	O
Appreciation	O
Night	O
-	O
Featuring	O
Trek	O
Travel	O
!	O
http://t.co/d5M84IIx6z	O

Some	O
niggas	O
live	O
for	O
fucking	O
as	O
many	O
bitches	O
as	O
possible	O
n	O
some	O
bitches	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
just	O
to	O
feel	O
loved	O
even	O
if	O
it's	O
for	O
the	O
moment	O
#DoBetter	O

@ashley_noellee	O
says	O
the	O
girl	O
who	O
bruised	O
Rachel's	B-person
arms	O
http://t.co/I2s1Y88rFi	O

kayanya	O
harus	O
membiasakan	O
diri	O
kirim	O
imel	O
trus	O
bales2	O
ndiri	O
.	O

Cali	B-person
I'm	O
coming	O
home	O
!	O

RT	O
@SipMyJuice_Box	O
:	O
"	O
@MurdaAveDomo	O
:	O
Ion	O
F	O
.	O
ck	O
w	O
/	O
B	O
.	O
tches	O
"	O
Fuck	O
Bitches	O
I	O
Don't	O
like	O
Em	O

Hickeys	O
feel	O
good	O
and	O
all	O
but	O
make	O
a	O
nigga	O
look	O
trashy	O
.	O
Even	O
if	O
you	O
wear	O
Versace	B-organization
.	O

Undercover	O
book	O
-	O
buying	O
today	O
.	O
Geared	O
up	O
.	O

@DrewCourt	O
He	O
thinks	O
"	O
private	O
charity	O
"	O
will	O
shovel	O
the	O
sidewalk	O
.	O

RT	O
@tanyaa___	O
:	O
It	O
bugs	O
me	O
when	O
i	O
dont	O
see	O
my	O
mom	O
that	O
often	O

I	O
LOST	O
A	O
HOUR	O
OF	O
SLEEP	O
WHY	O
SHOULD	O
I	O
EVEN	O
BOTHER	O
WITH	O
SCHOOL	O
I	O
HABE	O
BIGGER	O
ISSUES	O

Dream	B-product
Followers	I-product
of	O
the	O
day	O
Follow	O
Me	O
Please	O
@YG	O
@missnatalienunn	O
@Tyga	O
@souljaboy	O
@TRAEABN	O
@sarahSOoliver	O
@vgunvalson	O
@thegame	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
#FOLLOWME	O

Idgaf	O
about	O
no	O
Boosie	B-person

Apartamento	O
pequeno	O
em	O
Moscou	B-place
-	O
Constance	O
Zahn	O
|	O
Open	O
House	O
http://t.co/IiLZDEdwaL	O

vontade	O
de	O
enfiar	O
essa	O
materia	O
da	O
veja	O
no	O
cu	O
de	O
quem	O
escreveu	O
,	O
nossa	O
!	O

RT	O
@ElayneOkaya	O
:	O
#AMVCA2014	O
Amazing	O
platform	O
for	O
African	B-place
filmmakers	O
.	O
http://t.co/cWfLtNHPSf	O

@wutthestyles	O
@4Andy16	O
yo	O
solo	O
le	O
envie	O
pizza	O
celosaaa	O
!	O

Bayern	B-organization
president	O
jailed	O
for	O
tax	O
evasion	O
.	O
We	O
should	O
offer	O
Buckbeak	B-person
in	O
exchange	O
for	O
Kroos	B-person
.	O

RT	O
@lullabyhorxn	O
:	O
@spotifystyles	O
5sos	O
is	O
niet	O
preuts	O
maar	O
een	O
5pros	O
tituee	O

RT	O
@NavalHistWar	O
:	O
'	O
You	O
need	O
a	O
map	O
to	O
read	O
Jomini	B-person
;	O
you	O
don't	O
need	O
a	O
map	O
to	O
read	O
Clausewitz	B-person
'	O
Huw	B-person
Strachan	I-person
-	O
well	O
put	O
.	O

RT	O
@jack_agnew1994	O
:	O
@LashawnLamark	O
yes	O
bitch	O
!	O
Join	O
the	O
club	O
!	O

US	B-place
will	O
likely	O
destroy	O
thousands	O
of	O
MRAPs	B-product
,	O
Humvees	B-product
,	O
other	O
vehicles	O
,	O
#Afghanistan	B-place
http://t.co/Ikr3zdjzu1	O

#NEW	O
pic	O
of	O
Zayn	B-person
-	O
apparently	O
27	O
.	O
02	O
.	O
2014	O
via	O
@LASHTONWIFl	O
http://t.co/xMUEEGOj4M	O

When	O
in	O
doubt	O
,	O
eat	O
pizza	O

@YaBoySJam	O
to	O
live	O
.	O
So	O
income	O
will	O
be	O
better	O
.	O
So	O
in	O
an	O
attempt	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
more	O
affordable	O
,	O
will	O
leave	O
more	O
people	O
unemployed	O
afterwards	O
.	O

if	O
you	O
say	O
something	O
about	O
a	O
girls	O
eyebrows	O
the	O
claws	O
come	O
out	O

don't	O
feel	O
like	O
going	O
to	O
English	O

@LindaBVan	O
Thank	O
You	O
do	O
much	O
!	O
Very	O
generous	O
of	O
You	O
!	O

@harii21	O
KAO	O
INSTALIRAJ	O
GA	O
JER	O
DM	O
NE	O
RADI	O

RT	O
@Otrovnica	O
:	O
Ostavila	O
sam	O
utisak	O
da	O
sam	O
fina	O
i	O
postena	O
.	O
Ali	O
da	O
me	O
ubijete	O
ne	O
znam	O
gde	O
.	O

@filiuscodys	O
yaudah	O
lu	O
bakiak	O
:p	O

@Kevis_IGotHeart	O
it	O
just	O
feels	O
crazy	O

@Ky_Mike	O
boy	O
,	O
you're	O
fine	O
.	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
have	O
the	O
cutest	O
gap	O
ever	O
.	O
Don't	O
block	O
me	O
pls	O
.	O
Lmfao	O
.	O

@endorphinzarry	O
sarcasm	O
christina	B-person
sarcasm	O

*	O
heads	O
to	O
Burger	B-organization
King	O
bathroom	O
*	O
RT	O
@lvallana	O
Let's	O
get	O
busy	O
.	O

RT	O
@ammmynicolee	O
:	O
I'm	O
going	O
to	O
regret	O
laying	O
down	O
instead	O
of	O
getting	O
ready	O
.	O
Buhhh	O
I'm	O
comfy	O
so	O
fckit	O

RT	O
@dafuqtrolls	O
:	O
being	O
an	O
asshole	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/k9c1sfPkBI	O

@bradfordsgomez	O
really	O
?	O
How	O
is	O
it	O
not	O
exploding	O

@remiselitax	O
oh	O
shit	O
yeah	O
mcdonalds	B-organization
chicken	O
nuggets	O
are	O
the	O
best	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O

NIGGA	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
RT	O
@2TONEDASUPASTAR	O
:	O
Suwooo	O
!	O
RT	O
@MercedezUAZ	O
:	O
Y	O
'	O
all	O
better	O
ask	O
@2TONEDASUPASTAR	O
how	O
I	O
do	O
when	O
that	O
YG	O
come	O
on	O

Funny	O
RT	O
@ArmLegLegArmHD	O
:	O
LMFAOOOOO	O
LEBRON	B-person
A	O
FRAUD	O
http://t.co/GkO6DSHr9r	O

@SeXXXyDulce82	O
call	O
her	O
all	O
type	O
of	O
names	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
make	O
her	O
wanna	O
fight	O
you	O

@paynetrain__44	O
just	O
walk	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
hoe	O
$	O
be	O
like	O
what	O
dat	O
mouf	O
do	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
That's	O
what	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
1	O
/	O
10	O
success	O
rate	O

RT	O
@ccarpcat	O
:	O
Mortgage	O
News	O
:	O
Fannie	B-person
and	O
Freddie	B-person
fate	O
could	O
be	O
known	O
within	O
days	O
http://t.co/2QYyuC6GC0	O

@iReplaceDildos	O
Necessary	O
roughness	O
lol	O
.	O

@Jazz803	O
you	O
really	O
can't	O
,	O
I	O
just	O
like	O
your	O
enthusiasm	O
,	O
confidence	O
,	O
and	O
energy	O
when	O
you	O
slang	O
them	O
long	O
ass	O
arms	O
.	O

Apply	O
to	O
@havethefuture	O
summer	O
camp	O
in	O
Italy	B-place
on	O
law	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
econ	O
here	O
:	O
http://t.co/yarMv0jTXH	O
Great	O
opp	O
for	O
students	O
interested	O
in	O
#reinventlaw	O
!	O

RT	O
@ggcill	O
:	O
"	O
@sjkunyet	O
:	O
mentionan	O
sm	O
icill	O
greget	O
pisan	O
"	O
/	O
kebaca	O
/	O
duh	O
jadi	O
merasa	O
'	O
-	O
'	O

@BibiMcCullen	O
Thanks	O
for	O
the	O
Follow	O
!	O
Have	O
you	O
been	O
enjoying	O
#LoveChild	B-product
so	O
far	O
?	O

#np	O
:	O
@linkinpark	O
ft	O
.	O
@steveaoki	O
-	O
A	B-product
Light	I-product
That	I-product
Never	I-product
Comes	I-product
#itsmysong	O

@CChappell1967	O
@DRUDGE	O
Really	O
.	O
You're	O
including	O
that	O
draft	O
dodger	O
Bush	B-person
,	O
eh	O
.	O

@PorschaSinclair	O
u	O
think	O
that'll	O
help	O
his	O
focus	O
in	O
school	O
?	O
If	O
so	O
,	O
there	O
a	O
karate	O
school	O
up	O
the	O
street	O

Tetiba	O
dia	O
ngada2	O
gila	O
pagi	O
td	O
~	O

Ajnabi	O
sa	O
ek	O
mausam	O
ek	O
be	O
'	O
mausam	O
si	O
shaam	O
Jab	O
usay	O
aana	O
nahi	O
tha	O
aur	O
usay	O
aana	O
bhi	O
tha	O
#JaunElia	O
http://t.co/C0oE8znEkg	O

Had	O
a	O
super	O
deep	O
conversation	O
with	O
the	O
cabbie	O
about	O
antibiotic	O
resistance	O
and	O
superbugs	O

AP	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
random	O
question	O
.	O
Does	O
it	O
bother	O
anyone	O
else	O
to	O
call	O
someone	O
and	O
them	O
have	O
you	O
on	O
the	O
speaker	O
phone	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/bqcljSvmLx	O

RT	O
@RedLyteSpecial	O
:	O
Females	O
be	O
SCREAMING	O
for	O
attention	O
,	O
then	O
wonder	O
why	O
a	O
nigga	O
talk	O
to	O
em	O
crazy	O
.	O

Women	O
can't	O
take	O
birth	O
control	O
pills	O
.	O
No	O
abortion	O
once	O
pregnant	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
if	O
the	O
child	O
is	O
hungry	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
pray	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
US	B-place
we	O
call	O
that	O
Freedom	O
.	O

Going	O
to	O
deuce	O
out	O
to	O
my	O
bat	O
cave	O
today	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

Fav	O
si	O
me	O
regalas	O
una	O
vida	O
social	O

It's	O
Saturday	B-other
I	O
need	O
to	O
be	O
doing	O
down	O
thing	O
today	O
/	O
tonight	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O

"	O
Alright	O
spunk	O
flake	O
!	O
Alright	O
ya	O
bum	O
pilot	O
!	O
"	O
#trashbat	O

@LeighNaturkach	O
Oh	O
yeah	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
well	O
I'm	O
8	O
track	O
tape	O
old	O
.	O

RT	O
@KrystalNiaaa	O
:	O
You	O
betta	O
hop	O
on	O
that	O
horse	O

De	O
bouas	O
na	O
barca	O
esses	O
dias	O
http://t.co/akfvLAkx2w	O

Ran	O
1	O
.	O
4	O
miles	O
and	O
didn't	O
do	O
too	O
badly	O
,	O
considering	O
I	O
haven't	O
gone	O
jogging	O
for	O
like	O
6	O
weeks	O
!	O
#running	O
#summeriscoming	O

@slmhld	O
iya	O
kita	O
ke	O
mie	O
aceh	O
aja	O
ya	O
@meriiw	O
@wiwiiiw	O

On	O
my	O
way	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
almost	O
falling	O
asleep	O
.	O
If	O
only	O
.	O

I'm	O
at	O
Ayam	O
Goreng	O
ABC	O
,	O
Batu	O
-	O
Malang	O
(	O
Batu	O
-	O
Malang	O
)	O
http://t.co/KpWtXA8q1c	O

Share	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
loving	O
Trunx	B-product
!	O
Trunx	B-product
:	O
Your	O
All	O
in	O
One	O
Photo	O
Solution	O
http://t.co/u9r4QcE7Jd	O

Let	O
it	O
snow	O
,	O
let	O
it	O
snow	O
,	O
let	O
it	O
snow	O
.	O
#snow	O
#iwantspring	O

HE	O
CHANGED	O
HIS	O
INSTAGRAM	O
USERNAME	O
AN	O
HIS	O
SHOTS	O
ONE	O
BUT	O
HE	O
CHANGED	O
IT	O
BACK	O
ON	O
INSTAGRAM	O
IT	O
DOESN'T	O
MEAN	O
ANYTHING	O
IT	O
WAS	O
FOR	O
FUN	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O

Im	O
learning	O
to	O
just	O
let	O
things	O
flow	O
an	O
to	O
stop	O
worrying	O
so	O
much	O
.	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
what	O
It	O
is	O
.	O

RT	O
@Gissellefinest	O
:	O
The	O
shit	O
angels	O
sends	O
me	O
wtffff	O
lmao	O

@Amirosie	O
it's	O
looks	O
really	O
good	O
doesn't	O
it	O
?	O
!	O

Photo	O
:	O
(	O
via	O
35	O
fascinating	O
photos	O
of	O
Korea	B-place
from	O
100	O
years	O
ago	O
(	O
before	O
K	O
-	O
dramas	O
took	O
over	O
Asia	B-place
)	O
|	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/SB5yuJCtFs	O

Every	O
year	O
,	O
about	O
40	O
,	O
000	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
US	B-place
suffer	O
from	O
toilet	O
related	O
injuries	O
.	O

@BrianRomanowsk1	O
And	O
then	O
it'll	O
all	O
be	O
undone	O
when	O
they	O
get	O
bought	O
out	O
by	O
Comcast	B-organization
:D	O

@stephysahni	O
;	O
)	O
hor	O
ki	O
bnda	O
?	O
songs	O
ton	O
bina	O
:p	O

NOT	O
YET	O
LATER	O
RT	O
@RobinTheShip	O
:	O
@ATW1062	O
Have	O
you	O
had	O
the	O
one	O
you	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
yet	O
?	O

@BradTubb	O
Duck	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
Waffle	O
is	O
the	O
dream	O
but	O
may	O
be	O
fully	O
booked	O

#merdeka	O
Taylor	B-person
swift	I-person
tak	O
pernah	O
sesali	O
masa	O
lalunya	O
:	O
Seandainya	O
pun	O
aku	O
bisa	O
kembali	O
ke	O
masa	O
lalu	O
,	O
ak	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/HBENrSrTlx	O
#berita	O

really	O
want	O
my	O
cartilage	O
pierced	O
ffs	O

what	O
is	O
hayes's	B-person
full	O
name	O
?	O
someone	O
said	O
hayes	B-person
is	O
his	O
middle	O
name	O
like	O
nash	B-person

Resmikan	O
PT	O
TransJakarta	O
,	O
Jokowi	O
Ingin	O
Pelayanan	O
dan	O
Fasilitas	O
Dibenahi	O
http://t.co/0vhC4Pkbst	O

"	O
@TeeTheCreator_	O
:	O
I	O
don't	O
respect	O
nobody	O
but	O
my	O
mama	O
and	O
granny	O
"	O

how	O
do	O
i	O
get	O
amber	B-person
and	O
kira	B-person
to	O
follow	O
me	O
am	O
i	O
not	O
exciting	O
they	O
said	O
my	O
ustream	B-organization
name	O
like	O
three	O
times	O
and	O
read	O
all	O
my	O
comments	O
out	O
loud	O

RT	O
@Bitcoin_Spain	O
:	O
Mining	B-organization
ASICs	I-organization
Technologies	I-organization
B	I-organization
.	I-organization
V	I-organization
.	I-organization
(	I-organization
MAT	I-organization
)	I-organization
Joins	O
Scrypt	O
ASIC	O
Race	O
Towards	O
The	O
Bottom	O
:	O
http://t.co/YDDPMPShtw	O
#bitcoin	O
#btc	O

Mieno	B-person
voted	O
KRA	B-organization
vs	O
Sofapaka	B-organization
Man	O
-	O
of	O
-	O
the	O
-	O
match	O
http://t.co/BwAnPEFFvd	O

Gaada	O
vakum2an	O
gue	O
mah	O
.	O

Check	O
out	O
my	O
new	O
Video	O
Glove	O
Compartment	O
-	O
UPDATE	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
Dan	B-person
Allen	I-person
http://t.co/2z2LsAeAtL	O

RT	O
@WheresCharles	O
:	O
My	O
iphone	O
screen	O
cracked	O
today	O
.	O
http://t.co/VgKPwzhX0f	O

RT	O
@Mariablanca	O
:	O
Tears	O
b	O
/	O
c	O
of	O
@alleniverson	O
'	O
s	O
speech	O
!	O
#AI3Forever	O

Use	O
the	O
hashtag	O
#AtMiddleton	B-product
before	O
our	O
April	O
1st	O
Bluray	O
/	O
DVD	O
release	O
date	O
and	O
you	O
could	O
win	O
an	O
At	O
Middleton	O
t	O
-	O
shirt	O
used	O
in	O
the	O
movie	O
.	O

@jennevansxo	O
We	O
would	O
like	O
to	O
help	O
follow	O
up	O
,	O
Jennifer	B-person
.	O
In	O
order	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
please	O
follow	O
/	O
DM	O
us	O
your	O
name	O
,	O
number	O
,	O
and	O
property	O
address	O
.	O
^	O
JB	O

RT	O
@LongLiveDenzy	O
:	O
@GoodOnesGo_x	O
yyyyyaaaaasssss	O
slay	O
for	O
the	O
king	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
Thank	O
him	O
later	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O

RT	O
@CliqueForLife	O
:	O
ww	O
#VoteAriana	O
#KCA	O

RT	O
@missymetz	O
:	O
@tsgpodcast	O
I	O
love	O
the	O
subject	O
of	O
anatomy	O
!	O
!	O

today	O
is	O
the	O
best	O
day	O
ever	O
:	O
got	O
an	O
A	O
on	O
my	O
exam	O
,	O
got	O
a	O
close	O
parking	O
spot	O
,	O
got	O
a	O
seat	O
in	O
class	O
next	O
to	O
an	O
outlet	O
.	O
#happytweeter	O

Melonie	B-person
just	O
really	O
brings	O
that	O
good	O
side	O
of	O
me	O
out	O
.	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
knows	O
how	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
bad	O
one	O
away	O
.	O

Everybody	O
seems	O
sooooo	O
worried	O
about	O
Ukaine	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
we'd	O
show	O
half	O
this	O
concern	O
for	O
what's	O
happening	O
(	O
or	O
not	O
happening	O
)	O
in	O
Muzaffarnagar	B-place
!	O

RT	O
@xImJAYx	O
:	O
my	O
best	O
going	O
to	O
georgia	B-place
on	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
week	O
or	O
so	O
.	O
.	O
im	O
gone	O
miss	O
her	O

RT	O
@TopFloorPromoti	O
:	O
@StackBoys864	O
@TraxxOnDekk	O
Y	O
'	O
all	O
ain't	O
tryna	O
pregame	O
tho	O
http://t.co/FxrI0Prcqx	O

RT	O
@K1dR2tchet	O
:	O
Girls	O
never	O
believe	O

Wait	O
so	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
Regan	B-person
is	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
Robert	B-person
as	O
well	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
o	O

@IAMSU	O
mess	O
wit	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
beats	O
broham	O
.	O

Leo	B-person
loving	O
his	O
new	O
'	O
travel	O
buddy	O
'	O
#HenryHugglemonster	O
@sharkeytweets	O
the	O
quality	O
is	O
outstanding	O
!	O
http://t.co/NtryUJ9la4	O

RT	O
@itsJarm	O
:	O
Hobbies	O
include	O
:	O
taking	O
naps	O
and	O
then	O
subtracting	O
the	O
hours	O
from	O
the	O
real	O
time	O
to	O
justify	O
why	O
I	O
am	O
up	O
so	O
late	O

"	O
@lukeytwerks	O
:	O
if	O
u	O
call	O
me	O
shy	O
I'll	O
mentally	O
stab	O
u	O
"	O
shy	O
Do	O
u	O
want	O
one	O
knife	O
or	O

RT	O
@NFLonReddit	O
:	O
Source	O
close	O
to	O
DeSean	B-person
Jackson	I-person
:	O
"	O
He	O
wants	O
to	O
play	O
for	O
Washington	B-organization
.	O
"	O
http://t.co/tGyGC2q14x	O
#reddit	O
#nfl	O

Andrew	B-person
Garfield	I-person
threw	O
a	O
fit	O
at	O
the	O
#Oscars	O
,	O
reportedly	O
.	O
Someone	O
tell	O
him	O
he's	O
not	O
playing	O
the	O
Superior	O
Spidey	O
-	O
-	O
yet	O
.	O
#AmazingSpiderman	B-product

A	O
litte	O
reminder	O
of	O
just	O
how	O
bad	O
things	O
have	O
been	O
and	O
must	O
never	O
be	O
again	O
!	O
@Punisher666aoz	O
:	O
#auspol	O
http://t.co/hVplA053Qy	O

@petuniaskincare	O
thanks	O
for	O
the	O
follow	O
too	O
!	O
x	O

RT	O
@Glam_Mari	O
:	O
Don't	O
sleep	O
when	O
you	O
know	O
you	O
got	O
a	O
girl	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

Am	O
drinking	O
since	O
am	O
up	O

Cali	B-place
people	O
pop	O
too	O
many	O
pills	O
no	O
sir	O

RT	O
@smevsss	O
:	O
there	O
is	O
absolutely	O
no	O
reason	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
at	O
work	O
rn	O

RT	O
@baespinosa	O
:	O
The	O
boys	O
love	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
.	O
Remember	O
that	O
please	O

China	B-place
News	O
-	O
Obamas	B-person
climb	O
Great	O
Wall	O
after	O
lunch	O
of	O
trout	O
http://t.co/iC3orolMgM	O

@BritniB	O
Can	O
you	O
"	O
Mark	O
the	O
Spot	O
"	O
for	O
us	O
when	O
you	O
have	O
issues	O
?	O
It	O
sends	O
feedback	O
directly	O
to	O
our	O
network	O
team	O
:	O
http://t.co/FNspzh177t	O
(	O
2	O
/	O
2	O
)	O

never	O
had	O
enough	O
shoes	O
to	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
shoes	O
more	O
-	O
women	O

duh	O
sedih	O
yah	O
selingan	O
doang	O
kali	O
beb	O
doi	O
nya	O
hahah	O
RT	O
@nikinabilla	O
:	O
Jalannya	O
sama	O
siapa	O
tp	O
hatinya	O
masih	O
kesiapa	O
.	O
.	O
ya	O
makanya	O
jgn	O
suka	O
bawa	O

RT	O
@WellSpokenTokn	O
:	O
This	O
is	O
Oregon's	B-place
loss	O
more	O
than	O
Wisconsin's	B-place
win	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
your	O
foot	O
on	O
a	O
team's	O
throat	O
,	O
you	O
push	O
harder	O
.	O

RT	O
@JagAthletics	O
:	O
Citrus	B-organization
Valley	I-organization
scores	O
.	O
Game	O
over	O
.	O
Great	O
season	O
Jags	O
.	O
@Devin_Ugland	O
@AntonioCMorales	O
@OCSidelines	O

Besok	O
di	O
'	O
Ada	O
Ada	O
Aja	O
'	O
GTV	O
pasti	O
kamu	O
belom	O
bisa	O
ikut	O
yaah	O
:	O
(	O
aleee	O
cepett	O
sembuh	O
:	O
(	O
@iqbaale	O
SEMBUH	O
SEMBUH	O
SEMBUH	O
:	O
-	O
*	O

@FSUNolegurl	O
hang	O
tough	O
you	O
can	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
ya	O
!	O
!	O

@moorehn	O
\	O
\	O
\	O
o	O
/	O
/	O
/	O
There	O
you	O
go	O
!	O
:)	O
Congrats	O
!	O
:)	O
Desormais	O
,	O
on	O
peut	O
se	O
parler	O
en	O
Francais	O
!	O

jelena	B-person
just	O
saved	O
me	O
ty	O

It's	O
not	O
spring	O
break	O
if	O
there's	O
no	O
102	O
-	O
degree	O
fever	O
.	O
#parenting	O

I	O
forgot	O
I	O
had	O
hw	O
ughhhhh	O
nigga	O

Bedazzle	O
me	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
light	O
up	O
your	O
world	O
.	O
http://t.co/39yvv6iaXB	O

Netherlands	B-place
to	O
become	O
the	O
first	O
country	O
to	O
legalize	O
carrier	O
-	O
free	O
SIM	B-product
cards	O
http://t.co/Z19wiuvGwU	O

@rahma09	O
@arditi13	O
@rosmaday	O
aku	O
rameri	O
lo	O
nek	O
kur	O
dipameri	O
malmingan	O
:D	O

I	O
love	O
5sos	B-product
so	O
much	O
aAAaahg	O

RT	O
@aka_candyman	O
:	O
I'm	O
not	O
looking	O
for	O
love	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
love	O
.	O

@andino_briana	O
@DonnieWahlberg	O
mind	O
if	O
I	O
steal	O
the	O
picture	O
?	O

#ONAIR	O
@LYLAINDONESIA	O
-	O
Tak	O
Kan	O
Ada	O
#SiaranTengahMalam	O

@Marcia4Science	O
has	O
tons	O
of	O
excellent	O
questions	O
in	O
this	O
editorial	O
:	O
Improving	O
Scientific	O
Communication	O
http://t.co/ITp5QiWyeC	O

So	O
my	O
legal	O
teacher	O
isn't	O
at	O
school	O
again	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
out	O
why	O
.	O
.	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
car	O
crash	O
on	O
the	O
weekend	O
.	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
he's	O
okay	O

@Musicalgoose71	O
most	O
of	O
it	O
is	O
smog	O
I	O
been	O
in	O
China	B-place
far	O
to	O
long	O
I'm	O
ready	O
to	O
head	O
out	O
.	O

new	O
snap	O
from	O
chop	O
what	O
the	O
fukc	O
do	O
u	O
want	O
bitch	O

Apple	B-product
MA350LL	I-product
question	O
:	O
Not	O
Recognized	O
By	O
Computer	O
-	O
http://t.co/DYEzMcbuIK	O

Jeezy	B-person
really	O
wasn't	O
lyin	O
,	O
this	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
classic	O
album	O
.	O
.	O

HEY	O
TWITTER	O
THERE'S	O
A	O
NEW	O
PLACE	O
OFF	O
TWITTER	O
WHERE	O
YOU	O
CAN	O
DO	O
TWITTER	O
http://t.co/yS1FZf01hW	O

@BSNComedy	O
tweeting	O
you	O
.	O
I've	O
missed	O
you	O

@francetajohnson	O
facts	O
only	O
!	O
That's	O
what	O
I'm	O
here	O
for	O
.	O
Haha	O

I'm	O
probably	O
providing	O
so	O
many	O
people	O
with	O
new	O
backgrounds	O
omg	O

@GOLFWANGJ	O
que	O
carajo	O
,	O
tenes	O
idea	O
por	O
que	O
?	O
quiza	O
esten	O
grabando	O
algo	O

@Yuoaman	O
@JoOnBulba	O
-	O
Multiple	O
times	O
!	O
Somehow	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

rapatkan	O
-	O
&	O
gt	O
;	O
RT	O
@JoyMoron	O
INDIE	B-other
MOVEMENT	I-other
FEST	I-other
#	O
1	O
NightCoustic	O
at	O
McDonald	B-organization
joglo	O
28maret	O
w	O
/	O
@JoyMoron	O
@pnprivatenumber	O
http://t.co/JeoBGFcYcG	O

@JuSlim_	O
hell	O
yeah	O
.	O
.	O
and	O
it's	O
a	O
Saturday	O
.	O
.	O

Hellow	O
!	O
RT	O
"	O
@LeMfukz6	O
:	O
U	O
can	O
say	O
that	O
again	O
"	O
@NattyAdonis	O
:	O
Its	O
weird	O
to	O
lose	O
RT	O
@ThaFabVallee	O
Chiefs	O
fans	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
early	O
:(	O
"	O
"	O

HOLY	O
FUCKINF	O
BUTTHOLE	O
SHKSKSS	O
http://t.co/5vlpRYoGHs	O

@foreveryounggxo	O
word	O
.	O
My	O
internship	O
probably	O
won't	O
really	O
let	O
me	O
take	O
off	O
=	O
(	O

@podidosai	O
here	O
Whole	O
Food	O
market	O
is	O
selling	O
canned	O
"	O
Organic	O
coconut	O
water	O
"	O
lololol	O

RT	O
@Itha_Sririta	O
:	O
Be	O
your	O
self	O
.	O
.	O
:-)	O
(	O
{	O
}	O
)	O

Lesser	B-product
Baier	I-product
-	I-product
Hume	I-product
vehicle	O
,	O
but	O
pleasant	O
.	O
#PraiseFOX	O

@MarkLazerus	O
Guess	O
I'm	O
never	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
game	O
again	O
.	O
#HelpMeImPoor	O

@VERNALICIOUS1	O
@MannCenter	O
@phish	O
I'm	O
ready	O
,	O
see	O
you	O
there	O
Verna	B-person
.	O
#notmyfirstshow	O
#willnotactuallybeworking	O
#lookwhoseinthefreezer	O

Somebody	O
in	O
Iowa	B-place
bring	O
me	O
Pizza	O
Hut	O
.	O
Since	O
@Iowa_Guy_	O
won't	O
!	O
!	O

why	O
the	O
story	O
got	O
psl	O
nenek	O
duduk	O
dekat	O
tepi	O
katil	O
walauwei	O
walao	O
walao	O
walao	O

#TommyBahama	O
annual	O
Friends	O
and	O
Family	O
Event	O
Save	O
25	O
%	O
March6	O
-	O
9	O
http://t.co/F5VOJTArkv	O

happy	O
birthday	O
dear	O
,	O
wish	O
you	O
all	O
the	O
best	O
(	O
y	O
)	O
RT	O
@WidyartiD	O
:	O
@Azofers_Crew	O
mimin	O
ucapin	O
happy	O
birthday	O
ke	O
aku	O
dong	O
hahaaa	O

@non_existent_x3	O
I	O
laugh	O
just	O
looking	O
at	O
it	O
.	O

#floral	O
:	O
Debra	B-person
Prinzing	I-person
,	O
CCFC	O
Set	O
To	O
Promote	O
Domestic	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
CA	O
Cut	O
Flowers	O
At	O
SF	B-product
Flower	I-product
&	I-product
amp	I-product
;	I-product
Garden	I-product
Show	I-product
http://t.co/7igVOySmK1	O

@Space_News_Intl	O
It's	O
cool	O
the	O
@Mapbox	O
API	O
lets	O
lawyering	O
of	O
@skyboximaging	O
HD	O
video	O
on	O
top	O
of	O
@DigitalGlobe	O
imagery	O
+	O
@openstreetmap	O
roads	O

@_DayaMichelle	O
I	O
just	O
want	O
some	O
food	O
cthu	O

RT	O
@fidofinder	O
:	O
Found	O
dog	O
in	O
O	B-place
Fallon	I-place
,	I-place
IL	I-place
US	I-place
(	O
62269	O
)	O
http://t.co/uuZv2iKooC	O
#founddog	O

RT	O
@SOUTHWEST_Dessy	O
:	O
God	O
Is	O
So	O
Amazing	O
omg	O
,	O
the	O
blessings	O
are	O
just	O
exciting	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
father	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
everything	O

RT	O
@Flat12_Josh	O
:	O
Triton	B-organization
&	O
amp	O
;	O
Flat	B-organization
12	I-organization
collaboration	O
.	O
3	O
Years	O
in	O
the	O
making	O
.	O
Epic	O
day	O
of	O
lulz	O
shall	O
ensue	O
.	O
http://t.co/2dNs5ojg0k	O

@SBGillani	O
bikers	O
generally	O
thinks	O
tht	O
every1	O
on	O
road'll	O
account	O
for	O
their	O
recklessness	O
,	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
don't	O
have	O
mirrors	O
,	O
don't	O
use	O
indicators	O

I	O
miss	O
my	O
kitty	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
:(	O
#LonelyFennec	O

@KEEMSTARx	O
because	O
the	O
water	O
strips	O
all	O
the	O
non	O
-	O
neutral	O
charged	O
particles	O
away	O
from	O
your	O
body	O
.	O

@anastasia_sarna	O
I	O
will	O
also	O
be	O
there	O
.	O
#phoenixpanda	O

Hey	O
Courtney	B-person
I	O
love	O
you	O
more	O

Me	O
and	O
my	O
boy	O
@ThomasClanton84	O
trying	O
the	O
new	O
@Cellucor	O
#MysteryFavor	O
before	O
the	O
gym	O
@CellucorDan	O
@BBBenWilliamson	O
http://t.co/fag2TDplhE	O

@mrpdpxix	O
@itsssA	O
Anong	O
day	O
off	O
?	O
!	O
?	O
!	O
HAHAHA	O

General	O
Session	O
Theme	O
:	O
Synergies	O
and	O
unlikely	O
pairings	O
(	O
young	O
techies	O
+	O
middle	O
-	O
age	O
human	O
service	O
providers	O
=	O
solutions	O
for	O
aging	O
)	O
#AiA14	O

"	O
@iAdultPanny	O
:	O
"	O
@DemureCaptain	O
:	O
@iAdultPanny	O
@BrilliantPan	O
"	O
Wilfred	B-person
?	O
"	O
"	O
PRINCE	O
Wilfred	B-person
A	I-person
.	I-person
Spencer	I-person
.	O
"	O
"	O
I	O
REIGN	O
ABOVE	O
HIM	O
"	O

Sun	B-organization
Herald	I-organization
&	O
gt	O
;	O
&	O
gt	O
;	O
Recap	O
:	O
Washington	B-organization
vs	O
.	O
Brooklyn	B-organization
http://t.co/g2BNJVKO2h	O

My	O
family	O
are	O
all	O
gone	O
out	O
and	O
I'm	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
I	O
honestly	O
think	O
I'm	O
becoming	O
a	O
vampire	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
slowly	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
and	O
slowly	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
I'm	O
serious	O
.	O
.	O

Each	O
day	O
interesting	O
and	O
exciting	O
new	O
developments	O
unfold	O
in	O
preparation	O
to	O
share	O
the	O
music	O
of	O
'	O
The	O
SHIYR	O
Poets	O
'	O
(	O
Pronounced	O
'	O
Sheer	O
'	O
)	O

"	O
If	O
you're	O
not	O
laughing	O
you're	O
learning	O
"	O

RT	O
@Bdub93	O
:	O
It's	O
nice	O
talking	O
to	O
someone	O
who	O
can	O
hold	O
a	O
real	O
conversation	O

Thousand	B-product
Years	I-product
/	O
/	O
Christina	B-person
Perri	I-person

@bmeegwun	O
Better	O
than	O
those	O
other	O
actors	O
in	O
those	O
kinds	O
of	O
movies	O
xD	O

ie	O
.	O
-	O
Glad	O
I'll	O
be	O
speaking	O
truths	O
when	O
I	O
tell	O
my	O
future	O
son	O
you	O
can	O
be	O
a	O
loser	O
in	O
highschool	O
and	O
still	O
marry	O
the	O
hottest	O
girl	O
in	O
your	O
class	O

Just	O
got	O
this	O
#TheAmericans	B-product
sticker	O
.	O
Check	O
out	O
my	O
82	O
other	O
stickers	O
on	O
#tvtag	O
http://t.co/4D2lqENZlL	O
#TheAmericans	O

Top	O
5th	O
:	O
Edinburg	B-organization
North	I-organization
8	O
,	O
Sharyland	B-organization
6	O
.	O
HUGE	O
4th	O
for	O
North	O
,	O
scores	O
six	O
runs	O
on	O
five	O
hits	O
and	O
goes	O
through	O
the	O
lineup	O
.	O
#RGVsoftball	O

RT	O
@DatGrandeAss	O
:	O
Somebody	O
best	O
of	O
recorded	O
that	O
and	O
got	O
it	O
up	O
on	O
YouTube	B-organization
in	O
the	O
next	O
five	O
minutes	O
or	O
I'll	O
cry	O
.	O
.	O
wait	O
I	O
already	O
am	O

RT	O
@jamlin_	O
:	O
sandy	B-person
and	O
nashita	B-person
thinking	O
they	O
have	O
a	O
chance	O
at	O
getting	O
me	O
to	O
ship	O
h	O
/	O
e	O
even	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
lol	O
[	O
merah	O
voice	O
]	O
cute	O

@rusihart91	O
wtf	O
ugh	O
lucky	O
im	O
the	O
same	O
!	O
how	O
much	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
*	O

RT	O
@syahrul_senrose	O
:	O
Orang	O
tak	O
Tweet	O
Pasal	O
dia	O
,	O
Mention	O
Pun	O
tak	O
.	O
Tapi	O
dia	O
yang	O
terasa	O
,	O
apa	O
Kebodohannya	O
kau	O
ni	O
.	O

@Sibkiddtheworld	O
doesnt	O
always	O
work	O
like	O
that	O
boo	O
.	O

aaaa	O
ugi	O
kangennn	O
(	O
?	O
?	O
?	O
)	O
wqwqwq	O
=	O
)	O
)	O
"	O
@Reu_nathaniel	O
:	O
Sekarang	O
kita	O
ke	O
dreamers	O
:)	O
#TheOvertunes	O
"	O

Did	O
you	O
know	O
?	O
It's	O
Backup	B-other
Awareness	I-other
Week	I-other
!	O
http://t.co/yGTQ27gtdG	O
#backupweek	O

why	O
is	O
there	O
a	O
goat	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
?	O

RT	O
@minnie3218	O
:	O
@NayLassiter	O
you	O
thought	O
"	O
boo	O
boo	O
"	O

Sing	O
maha	O
kuasa	O
Rt	O
"	O
@ArifW786	O
:	O
Harus	O
percaya	O
siapa	O
"	O

New	O
drinking	O
game	O
Take	O
a	O
shot	O
everytime	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
words	O
Justin	B-person
and	O
20	O
on	O
your	O
tl	O

Nine	O
Thousand	O
Two	O
Hundred	O
Ten	O
#Vote1D	O
#KCA	O
#Directioners	O
#SoFantastic	O
@radiodisney	O

What	O
towns	O
are	O
nice	O
near	O
Harry	B-person
Potter	I-person
world	O
?	O

When	O
u	O
start	O
hittin	O
me	O
wit	O
the	O
one	O
word	O
answers	O
,	O
I	O
say	O
fuck	O
you	O
and	O
stop	O
texting	O
lol	O

Great	O
idea	O
,	O
methinks	O
.	O
(	O
Ericsson	O
Base	O
Stations	O
Built	O
Inside	O
Street	O
Lighting	O
Poles	O
)	O
http://t.co/VcD70Z52Jz	O

RT	O
@risinglastking	O
:	O
God	O
first	O
.	O
.	O
never	O
be	O
second	O

The	B-product
Bryce	I-product
Cotton	I-product
show	I-product

Hey	O
all	O
wrestlers	O
,	O
sorry	O
that	O
no	O
one	O
gives	O
a	O
shit	O
about	O
your	O
match	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
blame	O
#Bootista	O

@JoshUJWorld	O
#JoshUJExcited4Album2	O
DON'T	O
FORGET	O
MEEEEE	O

RT	O
@ExclusiveChild_	O
:	O
Three	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
horrible	O
things	O
that	O
could	O
possibly	O
happen	O
.	O
http://t.co/H86DzDaaLj	O

@nyjetscenter	O
agreed	O
but	O
just	O
cause	O
he's	O
the	O
best	O
available	O
doesn't	O
always	O
mean	O
he's	O
the	O
best	O
fit	O
.	O
$	O
always	O
a	O
factor	O
.	O
Other	O
guys	O
available	O
.	O

@classicj311	O
-	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
DVRed	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
watching	O
#Reven8e	B-product
-	O
getting	O
ready	O
to	O
watch	O
now	O
.	O

Rudy	B-person
and	O
Ludvig	B-person
begin	O
with	O
playful	O
foreplay	O
,	O
with	O
Ludvig	B-person
undressing	O
Rudy	B-person
and	O
moving	O
in	O
with	O
some	O
well	O
receive	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/oP2eJeuLb0	O

Everyone's	O
going	O
on	O
tour	O
with	O
Ladyhawk	O
!	O
First	O
it's	O
Marine	O
Dreams	O
in	O
ON	O
,	O
then	O
@jimmieshotgun	O
out	O
west	O
!	O
Dates	O
at	O
http://t.co/7itkq6fxA5	O

RT	O
@_LoveLauri	O
:	O
all	O
this	O
love	O
in	O
me	O
no	O
one	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
.	O

Next	O
week	O
Guitar	B-other
Center	I-other
Employees	I-other
Showcase	I-other
featuring	O
:	O
,	O
Brother	B-product
Rabbit	I-product
are	O
in	O
town	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
be	O
there	O
?	O
http://t.co/75p5pybuzE	O

Make	O
2014	O
your	O
year	O
.	O
Enter	O
the	O

@olisighs	O
I	O
couldn't	O
even	O
get	O
through	O
that	O
book	O
.	O

@cvllum2k14	O
happy	O
birthday	O
bro	O
;	O
)	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
3	O

There	O
is	O
so	O
many	O
things	O
I	O
wanna	O
do	O
.	O

Watching	O
Benedict	B-person
Cumberbatch	I-person
being	O
interviewed	O
post	O
#Oscars	B-other
you'd	O
never	O
think	O
he'd	O
be	O
the	O
guy	O
to	O
photobomb	O
U2	O
-	O
hilaro	O

@k_treen	O
@CGWTF	O
@animateobserver	O
discussing	O
CG	O
,	O
photography	O
and	O
animation	O
@tpgallery	O
#TPGHAPP	O
http://t.co/T8xllUXxIn	O

Pray	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
win	O
the	O
lottery	O
.	O
RT	O
@Champions8	O
:	O
@btcoop71	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
work	O
.	O
I'll	O
pray	O
for	O
you	O
.	O

Lijsttrekkers	O
Overbetuwe	O
:	O
#CDA	O
grootste	O
,	O
#PvdA	O
en	O
#VVD	O
verliezen	O
:	O
Het	O
#CDA	O
wordt	O
volgens	O
vrijwel	O
alle	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/WmEUJOd8WQ	O
#Arnhem	O

@LegendofBrooke	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
was	O
your	O
friend	O
then	O

FACT	O
OF	O
THE	O
DAY	O
:	O
EVERY	O
female	O
is	O
"	O
THAT	O
TYPE	O
OF	O
FEMALE	O
"	O

@causaturpis	O
acho	O
q	O
faltam	O
elementos	O
p	O
/	O
ser	O
tipificado	O
como	O
escrotice	O
.	O
Mas	O
apenas	O
acho	O

@imVkohli	O
ARE	O
YOU	O
WATCHING	O
KOHLIIII	B-person
?	O
?	O
?	O
?	O

Bout	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
some	O
mmmoonnnayyyy	O
#selfie	O
#work	O
#smile	O
#msdimples89	O
http://t.co/LKynMsbPpO	O

yep	O
i	O
do	O
love	O
@TheScript_Danny	O
#NOTSORRY	B-product

@brookebaskin	O
is	O
defence	O
leading	O
evidence	O
?	O

In	O
the	O
studio	O
cooking	O
up	O
with	O
my	O
bro	O
!	O
!	O
#TiredMomentsFindMeAdelightfulTreat	O

RT	O
@fresnnatural	O
:	O
Gak	O
mungkin	O
kan	O
Gals	O
ga	O
mau	O
dapet	O
camera	O
dan	O
voucher	O
belanja	O
GRATIS	O
?	O
Mau	O
?	O
http://t.co/5cm3Do2LeL	O

@adidasNEOLabel	O
OMG	O
.	O
Your	O
never	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
mine	O
https://t.co/tUZsDbJy7v	O

Want	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
we're	O
up	O
to	O
?	O
http://t.co/9cT8u8lpuh	O
#thegiftofgoodtour	O
http://t.co/2TYBjXxvMP	O

@TheAzzo	O
andys	B-person
special	O
cocktail	O
?	O

minum	O
Herbal	O
Aloe	O
Concentrate	O
;	O
p	O
RT	O
@info_wanita	O
:	O
Simak	O
yuk	O
ulsan	O
cara	O
mengatasi	O
#Maag	O
,	O
sobat	O
cantik	O
!	O

you	O
get	O
treated	O
the	O
same	O
exact	O
way	O
you	O
treat	O
me	O
,	O
there's	O
no	O
in	O
between	O

Gothic	B-product
Girl	I-product
2	I-product
(	O
Hardcore	O
)	O
#porn	O
#sexy	O
#xxx	O
#adult	O
#hardcore	O
#nsfw	O
#Amateur	O
#Teen	O
#Gothic	O
http://t.co/dc1wLMwmr8	O

@Deorro	O
dealing	O
with	O
that	O
in	O
vancouver	B-place
rn	O
.	O
1	O
officier	O
on	O
duty	O
.	O
brutal	O

@RichHomieCogs	O
@selaleanapa	O
hell	O
yeah	O
see	O
y	O
'	O
all	O
there	O

RT	O
@ImanixJonas	O
:	O
Laje	O
just	O
blew	O
me	O
.	O

@KruleWatts	O
@Ford	O
#RossMAP	O
can	O
be	O
a	O
shocking	O
experience	O

Too	O
tired	O
to	O
do	O
anything	O
kms	O

@Sumol67	O
response	O
to	O
Polish	O
mobilization	O

I	O
guess	O
I	O
claim	O
Texas	B-place
more	O
than	O
anything	O
since	O
I	O
was	O
pretty	O
much	O
raised	O
there	O
more	O
than	O
any	O
other	O
place	O
.	O

How	O
we	O
beefin	O
I	O
didn't	O
put	O
no	O
burgers	O
in	O
my	O
cart	O

Bitcoin	O
Difficulty	O
Increased	O
!	O
http://t.co/MDsVbi6JOt	O
[	O
http://t.co/KXmxzl4OQF	O
]	O
#mining	O

SCIENCE	O
!	O
MT	O
@GAJenniferG	O
:	O
Fireballs	O
and	O
other	O
fun	O
experiments	O
to	O
come	O
!	O
@ATLSciFest	O
is	O
making	O
#science	O
cool	O
:	O
3	O
/	O
22	O
-	O
29	O
http://t.co/j6E4T8XmCl	O

#Free	O
#Porn	O
#Chat	O
xmorfx's	O
room	O
Join	O
now	O
.	O
#Enjoy	O
it's	O
Free	O
http://t.co/3jJd4ZAUQw	O

kalo	O
kamu	O
pemain	O
Saxo	O
,	O
wajib	O
beli	O
,	O
,	O
AKG	O
C519	O
,	O
mini	O
clip	O
-	O
on	O
w	O
/	O
goosneck	O
,	O
nett	O
2	O
.	O
2jt	O
,	O
tersedia	O
dalam	O
pilhan	O
cable	O
/	O
wireless	O
http://t.co/9qVglftIYI	O

Brand	O
spankin	O
'	O
new	O
@Chromeo	O
helping	O
the	O
anticipation	O
for	O
upcoming	O
#WhiteWomen	O
-	O
Check	O
"	O
Jealous	O
(	O
I	O
Aint	O
With	O
It	O
)	O
"	O
-	O
-	O
https://t.co/M6we1KJq3d	O

I'm	O
rob	O
his	O
ass	O
blind	O
no	O
WITNESS	O

ASA	O
BIG	O
AIR	O
TRIPLES	O
,	O
MIAMI	B-place
http://t.co/IAgye7DwMJ	O

Revolt	B-organization
TV	I-organization
is	O
doing	O
a	O
good	O
job	O

@CosmicGirl78	O
of	O
course	O
!	O
Lol	O
come	O
on	O
over	O

@PGBeauty	O
thank	O
you	O
everyone	O
for	O
the	O
congrats	O
!	O
This	O
seriously	O
made	O
my	O
day	O
!	O
#SB14Beauty	O

RT	O
@TTZilla	O
:	O
lol	O
RT	O
@basedniggers	O
I	O
still	O
laugh	O
at	O
this	O
lol	O
nigga	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
chill	O
http://t.co/ugBRNjXPBE	O

cok	O
sikildigim	O
icin	O
size	O
parti	O
kumanyalarini	O
yazicam	O
:	O
-	O
akp	O
:	O
ekmek	O
arasi	O
doner	O
+	O
kola	O
+	O
su	O
-	O
chp	O
:	O
2	O
sandvic	O
+	O
meyve	O
suyu	O
+	O
topkek	O
+	O
su	O

KEEP	O
VOTING	O
!	O
#KCA	B-product
#voteUKMahomies	O

@saipul_jamil	O
ga	O
nyadar	O
sih	O
dibully	O
di	O
@DAcademyID	O
klo	O
gue	O
malu	O
deh	O
hih	O

Esta	O
noche	O
se	O
escucha	O
a	O
Estacion	O
Experimental	O
en	O
vivo	O
.	O
http://t.co/cXV2cxnkNC	O

@NiallOfficial	O
hi	O
babe	O
if	O
you	O
see	O
this	O
it'd	O
mean	O
the	O
world	O
if	O
you	O
could	O
follow	O
me	O
i	O
love	O
you	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
please	O
niall86	O

IT	O
TOOK	O
SO	O
LONG	O
TO	O
CONVINCE	O
YOU	O
I	O
KNEW	O
I	O
HAD	O
TO	O
SHOW	O
MYCOLORS	O
I	O
NEVER	O
WANTED	O
TO	O
BE	O
RESCUED	O

RT	O
@2ndMikay	O
:	O
grabe	O
fan	O
din	O
naman	O
yun	O
eh	O
bat	O
kayo	O
mag	O
seselos	O
-	O
_	O
-	O
ang	O
oa	O
talaga	O
ng	O
mga	O
ranzters	O
-	O
_	O
-	O

@Dainty_BabyDoll	O
I	O
wish	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
That	O
would	O
be	O
so	O
much	O
fun	O
because	O
I'm	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
bored	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
I'm	O
there	O
.	O

@GlennF	O
Too	O
grey	O
.	O
You	O
need	O
something	O
blue	O
in	O
there	O

Reds	B-organization
hang	O
on	O
to	O
beat	O
Stormers	B-organization
in	O
Brisbane	B-place
:	O
The	O
Reds	B-organization
recovered	O
from	O
their	O
two	O
match	O
losing	O
streak	O
on	O
tour	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/dpbjU4Dww9	O
#Rugby	O

@KINGSLVNSK	O
well	O
alrightyyyyy	O
then	O
http://t.co/da2IE5iJu5	O

@freedom2marry	O
yeah	O
I	O
know	O
lol	O
I'm	O
putting	O
up	O
all	O
the	O
sarcastic	O
ones	O
.	O

Onaaa	O
phone	O
with	O
nesey	O
neee	O
#LISAshit	O

Boleh	O
ke	O
pensyarah	O
kempen	O
utk	O
BN	O
/	O
non	O
-	O
BN	O
?	O
answer	O
:	O
TAK	O
BOLEH	O
.	O
kalau	O
dia	O
buat	O
jgk	O
?	O
answer	O
:	O
dia	O
macai	O
/	O
balaci	O
/	O
pembodek	O

According	O
to	O
Internet	O
Trends	O
2013	O
,	O
People	O
check	O
their	O
mobile	O
phones	O
150	O
times	O
a	O
day	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
do	O
you	O
check	O
your	O
#KCBMbenki	O
account	O
?	O

I	O
don't	O
understand	O
the	O
Applauze	O
ticketing	O
system	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
like	O
are	O
these	O
tickets	O
that	O
are	O
being	O
resold	O
like	O
on	O
stubhub	O
or	O

The	O
#HorsePLAY	O
#podcast	O
is	O
now	O
on	O
iTunes	B-organization
and	O
TuneInRadio	B-organization
.	O
Give	O
us	O
a	O
listen	O
and	O
leave	O
us	O
VM	O
at	O
(	O
206	O
)	O
415	O
-	O
4987	O
-	O
we'll	O
play	O
them	O
LIVE	O
!	O
=	O
oD	O

Murph	O
!	O
(	O
at	O
@RootNola	O
w	O
/	O
2	O
others	O
)	O
http://t.co/WHrtz3xZqG	O

Thank	O
You	O
Dear	O
Lord	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
(	O
@	O
CypressGH	O
Head	O
Office	O
)	O
http://t.co/Oj76ZnoIZ5	O

confessions	B-product
of	I-product
a	I-product
murder	I-product
suspect	I-product
by	O
james	B-person
patterson	I-person
is	O
so	O
goooodddd	O
aahhh	O

@cctvnews	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
Malaysian	O
flight	O
was	O
highjacked	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
for	O
a	O
later	O
event	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
hidden	O
somewhere	O
in	O
Iran	B-place
.	O

DTN	O
Health	O
:	O
Mothers	O
'	O
monitoring	O
of	O
media	O
tied	O
to	O
kids	O
'	O
weight	O
:	O
"	O
At	O
this	O
point	O
we	O
can	O
say	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
associati	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/31inriHwzt	O

RT	O
@esfahanhanim	O
:	O
We	O
r	O
choking	O
on	O
gas	O
,	O
people	O
still	O
pushing	O
forward	O
against	O
Polis	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
Tomas	B-person
in	O
Izmir	B-place
-	O
maybe	O
5	O
,	O
000	O
-	O
rough	O
estimate	O
!	O

RT	O
@ALotOfBees	O
:	O
If	O
you	O
still	O
think	O
I'm	O
shy	O
,	O
you	O
don't	O
know	O
me	O
at	O
all	O
.	O

@madwixxy	O
@transportworker	O
I	O
thought	O
that	O
was	O
just	O
a	O
picture	O
of	O
what	O
Tony's	B-person
doing	O
to	O
Joyce	B-person
:P	O

This	O
still	O
makes	O
me	O
happy	O
tho	O
http://t.co/6M6VdkfubA	O

my	O
sims	O
are	O
all	O
gonna	O
die	O
by	O
the	O
time	O
i	O
get	O
my	O
phone	O
back	O

i	O
would	O
love	O
to	O
be	O
on	O
carters	B-person
timeline	O
but	O
that'll	O
never	O
happen	O

How	O
about	O
that	O
?	O
The	O
Nos	O
.	O
3	O
,	O
5	O
and	O
12	O
#Dodgers	B-organization
prospects	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
Rancho	O
rotation	O
.	O

My	O
business	O
card	O
is	O
actually	O
just	O
a	O
Post	O
-	O
It	O
Note	O
with	O
"	O
Asshole	O
"	O
written	O
on	O
it	O
!	O

@Raekwon_96	O
bruh	O
aint	O
nobody	O
talkin	O
bout	O
u	O
,	O
Hit	O
my	O
line	O

@ErzaJR_	O
ck	O
ah	O
boleh	O
tuh	O
lempar	O
peypalnya	O
dikit	O
.	O
_	O
.	O

@coconono	O
Have	O
you	O
heard	O
Nostalgia	B-product
Ultra	I-product
?	O
It's	O
his	O
free	O
album	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
like	O
that	O
,	O
you	O
should	O
enjoy	O
Channel	B-product
Orange	I-product
.	O

#Oakland	B-place
#CA	B-place
Hiring	O
senior	O
#caregiver	O
#jobs	O
#training	O
Apply	O
2	O
PT	O
/	O
FT	O
#job	O
#	O
eldercare	O
#hiring	O
#employment	O
#tweetmyjob	O
http://t.co/HfTwkV24Fe	O

MAS	O
ASSIM	O
EU	O
VOU	O
CONTAR	O
UMA	O
PIADA	O

thebookofmormon	B-product
tourmons	O
in	O
#NYC	B-place
#love	O
#family	O
#100happydays	O
#day9	O
http://t.co/foZt7Qptob	O

@Barrieshepley	O
@Level_Six	O
@mec_toronto	O
Barrie	B-person
is	O
interested	O
in	O
hosting	O
some	O
SUP	O
races	O
in	O
Caledon	B-place
at	O
the	O
quarry	O
,	O
suggestions	O
on	O
formats	O
?	O

@_melxmarley	O
mornings	O
will	O
be	O
guaranteed	O
with	O
good	O
French	O
toast	O
lol	O

@joshdallas	O
can	O
you	O
say	O
"	O
alo	O
alo	O
gatinhas	O
"	O
to	O
us	O
?	O
pls	O
means	O
a	O
lot	O
,	O
we	O
love	O
u	O
@givemeddl	O
@charmdallas	O
@alwaysrumbelle	O
@fcksfrey	O
#askjosh	O
x	O

"	O
@ViewHipHopBlog	O
:	O
New	O
Music	O
:	O
YG	B-person
ft	O
Natasha	B-person
Mosley	I-person
-	O
459	O
"	O

ive	O
stopped	O
at	O
600	O
no	O
motivation	O
to	O
continue	O

AAAA	O
I	O
WANNA	O
GOTOTHIS	O
PLC	O
RT	O
@kompascom	O
:	O
Pantai	B-place
Pandawa	I-place
,	O
Keindahan	O
Tersembunyi	O
di	O
Bali	O
Selatan	O
http://t.co/FUhHSDT7bL	O
http://t.co/mJnKRDCCqB	O

@shevfenty	O
if	O
its	O
medcezir	O
finna	O
skitz	O

From	O
#WordPress	B-product
to	O
#Magento	B-product
:	O
Working	O
with	O
#templates	O
|	O
Pixafy	O
:	O
http://t.co/BygqgszUY0	O
#MagentoMonday	O
#themes	O

@anandkatakam	O
if	O
you	O
coat	O
yourself	O
in	O
zombie	O
guts	O
they'll	O
ignore	O
you	O

Everything	O
we	O
want	O
from	O
the	O
new	O
Mad	B-product
Men	I-product
season	O
:	O
http://t.co/QWncTrLzgU	O

Next	O
on	O
the	O
@wzzm13	O
Morning	B-product
News	I-product
-	O
more	O
from	O
Michigan	B-place
prison	O
escapee's	O
letter	O
,	O
changes	O
coming	O
to	O
M	O
-	O
40	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
@wmwhitecaps	O
temporary	O
home	O
.	O

@ThePinkSensei	O
Ewww	O
non	O
!	O
C	O
'	O
est	O
vrai	O
mdr	O

RT	O
@joelquarles	O
:	O
For	O
Your	O
Glory	O
I	O
will	O
do	O
anything	O
!	O
Just	O
see	O
you	O
,	O
to	O
behold	O
you	O
as	O
my	O
KING	O
!	O
#morningworship	O

ah	O
estava	O
maior	O
fera	O
a	O
musica	O

did	O
medlen	B-person
arm	O
died	O
?	O

@BYEKatee	O
I	O
KNOW	O
OH	O
MY	O
GOD	O
I	O
LITERALLY	O
CANT	O
BREATHE	O

@Cimorelliband	O
Hi	O
girls	O
!	O
If	O
you	O
see	O
this	O
can	O
you	O
please	O
take	O
a	O
second	O
to	O
follow	O
me	O
?	O
than	O
you	O
so	O
much	O
ily	O
x1	O

RT	O
@floresbiebers	O
:	O
@fadingbieber	O
thts	O
chinese	O
u	O
dummy	O

RT	O
@Aiming_4_RIO	O
:	O
@ItsRaniiiii	O
final	O
scores	O
have	O
been	O
looking	O
like	O
this	O
lately	O
lol	O

@TheGoWPink	O
Just	O
get	O
a	O
1080p	O
or	O
720p	O
Blu	B-product
-	I-product
RayRip	I-product
Torrent	O
.	O
Well	O
worth	O
it	O
.	O

Bath	O
time	O
is	O
so	O
much	O
fun	O
!	O
Grants	O
For	O
Moms	O
in	O
USA	B-place
:	O
http://t.co/aP1hMnSQy4	O
Grants	O
For	O
Moms	O
in	O
UK	B-place
:	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/uFLjoW93wP	O

Read	O
our	O
reviews	O
of	O
the	O
winners	O
at	O
the	O
2014	O
#Oscars	O
-	O
Spike	B-person
Jonze's	I-person
subtly	O
beautiful	O
'	O
Her	B-product
'	O
won	O
Best	O
Original	O
Screenplay	O
http://t.co/zZZ3nhFRb2	O

@oppspinnock	O
faz	O
alguns	O
70	O
anos	O
ahsuahauhs	O

@ISmellLovely	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
George	B-person
xxx	O

Ladies	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
gents	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
@FredsBile	O
is	O
obviously	O
THE	O
authority	O
on	O
human	O
nature	O
.	O
He	O
can	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
opinion	O
.	O
#proggie	O
@TomBeltz	O

@SiedVanRiel	O
OMG	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
he	O
answered	O
.	O
#BestDayEver	O
#Madisonism	O

mani	O
stop	O
rting	O
my	O
rts	O
i	O
hate	O
you	O

Penuh	O
.	O
Lambat	O
.	O
(	O
@	O
Homst	O
Restaurant	O
)	O
http://t.co/4igryGRmTI	O

RT	O
@uberfoxy	O
:	O
Love	O
me	O
from	O
nowhere	O
.	O

Tact	O
RT	O
@steveisDOPE	O
:	O
@lilsmokedog	O
it's	O
apologize	O
to	O
ya	O
old	O
hoes	O
night	O
.	O
so	O
yeah	O
just	O
paying	O
my	O
dues	O
.	O

RT	O
@BPWest_	O
:	O
"	O
@SiRackedUp	O
:	O
what	O
artists	O
would	O
u	O
like	O
to	O
see	O
on	O
the	O
official	O
"	O
Like	O
That	O
"	O
Remix	O
?	O
"	O
Wholagun	B-person
n	O
stormzy	O

RT	O
@TheGingerChef	O
:	O
Happy	O
mums	O
day	O
today	O
,	O
clocks	O
go	O
forward	O
and	O
full	O
restaurants	O
for	O
lunch	O

RT	O
@BethanyMota	O
:	O
@lyricaljustin	O
yes	O
omg	O
loooooove	O

some	O
of	O
y	O
'	O
all	O
are	O
actually	O
clinically	O
insane	O

@mark_doubt	O
Cheers	O
!	O
I	O
feel	O
very	O
special	O
.	O

RT	O
@HOWARTHUK	O
:	O
@HirstsYard	O
can't	O
wait	O
to	O
be	O
playing	O
or	O
you	O
guys	O
on	O
the	O
3rd	O
of	O
May	O
!	O
LOVE	O
x	O

RT	O
@USEstate	O
:	O
Real	O
estate	O
transactions	O
for	O
Hampden	B-place
,	O
Hampshire	B-place
and	O
Franklin	B-place
counties	O
,	O
March	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/3v2zYWbk1u	O

if	O
youre	O
tall	O
beautiful	O
and	O
smart	O
you	O
get	O
so	O
many	O
leg	O
ups	O
in	O
this	O
world	O

@Luke5SOS	O
hiya	O
luke	B-person
hemmings	I-person
from	O
5sos	O
!	O
please	O
follow	O
me	O
it'll	O
be	O
the	O
best	O
thing	O
ever	O
.	O
not	O
kidding	O
i	O
love	O
you	O
so	O
much	O
:)	O
xx	O
2489	O

Waiting	O
to	O
get	O
labs	O
done	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
some	O
asshole	O
has	O
his	O
volume	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
up	O
on	O
his	O
phone	O
playing	O
a	O
game	O
.	O
I'm	O
about	O
to	O
commit	O
justifiable	O
homicide	O
.	O

Mark	B-person
#Carney	I-person
statement	O
cont'd	O
-	O
Jim	B-person
#Flaherty	I-person
has	O
exhibited	O
the	O
very	O
best	O
of	O
Canadian	O
virtues	O
in	O
service	O
to	O
our	O
country	O
.	O

Omgggg	O
just	O
let	O
me	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
already	O
.	O

RT	O
@ahjobslist	O
:	O
Operations	O
Manager	O
,	O
Scrum	B-organization
Alliance	I-organization
.	O
http://t.co/tuWJTuFnCA	O
#denver	O
#jobs	O
@ScrumAlliance	O

Every	O
twitter	B-product
app	I-product
I	O
try	O
4	O
my	O
phone	O
is	O
acting	O
up	O
.	O
Anybody	O
else	O
got	O
this	O
issue	O
?	O

RT	O
@Only1JSmith	O
:	O
About	O
to	O
go	O
ride	O
around	O
and	O
jam	O
@Kevin_Gates	O
#ByAnyMeans	O
if	O
anyone's	O
in	O
Lafayette	B-place
hit	O
me	O
up	O
!	O

Not	O
mad	O
,	O
Just	O
Hurt	O
and	O
confused	O

If	O
your	O
in	O
a	O
relationship	O
,	O
your	O
line	O
is	O
suppose	O
to	O
be	O
dry	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
expect	O
?	O
People	O
complain	O
too	O
much	O
.	O

On	O
my	O
rich	O
nigga	O
Shit	O
and	O
dese	O
Hoes	O
fuck	O
Wit	O
anyone	O

Hate	O
it	O
when	O
niggas	O
get	O
their	O
eyebrows	O
done	O
.	O

how	O
long	O
will	O
our	O
magic	O
work	O

@NewAgeIkeTurner	O
and	O
I	O
ain't	O
talmbout	O
no	O
weak	O
ass	O
Miami	B-place
or	O
Vegas	B-place
shit	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
islands	O
bruh	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
sippin	O
Mai	O
Tai's	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
ya	O
feel	O
me	O
?	O

@sinisterjhk	O
that's	O
awesome	O
!	O
My	O
comic	O
shop	O
owner	O
always	O
raves	O
about	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
rings	O
it	O
through	O
.	O

@JordanKae	O
I'd	O
appreciate	O
if	O
you	O
did	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

I	O
just	O
speak	O
my	O
peace	O
,	O
keep	O
my	O
piece	O

Day	O
1	O
Blue	O
Zone	O
Diet	O
.	O
Tofu	O
Pho	O
with	O
Bok	O
choy	O
@	O
Quang	O
Restaurant	O
http://t.co/xLb1vumAoo	O

Oh	O
it's	O
gross	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
stfu	O
bitch	O
2	O
of	O
em	O
has	O
you	O
immortal	O
.	O

RT	O
@MacFarlaneNews	O
:	O
Days	O
before	O
primary	O
.	O
.	O
incumbent	O
DC	B-place
mayor	O
losing	O
ground	O
.	O
Via	O
http://t.co/3cAWnb2IUx	O

ppl	O
are	O
not	O
allowing	O
other	O
ppl	O
to	O
be	O
.	O
that	O
messes	O
w	O
my	O
aura	O
.	O
wooooooooooo	O
!	O
!	O

@lamesouls	O
WAIT	O
ARIANA	B-person
HAVE	O
U	O
GOTTWN	O
YE	O
PHONE	O
BACK	O

Hold	O
On	O
To	O
Me	O
As	O
We	O
Go	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

@JessTrog	O
LOOOOOOL	O
why	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
in	O
you	O
egg	O

On	O
the	O
air	O
tonight	O
with	O
IRAS	B-organization
,	O
showing	O
love	O
to	O
all	O
my	O
Caribbean	B-place
Family	O
@EPICexpo	O
http://t.co/tUaYZijhWc	O

@Rakataca_	O
I	O
appreciate	O
that	O
.	O
.	O
You	O
don't	O
even	O
know	O
!	O
*	O
wipes	O
tear	O
*	O
lol	O

@waIama_	O
RT	O
me	O
once	O
more	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
4	O
%	O
#magic	O

@kodoqu	O
Kucko	O
jedna	O
mislio	O
sam	O
da	O
si	O
na	O
mojoj	O
strani	O
:	O
'	O
(	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
3	O
@GeekHotnesss	O
@DeckoSaRomea	O

Grateful	O
I'm	O
single	O
.	O
No	O
one	O
has	O
to	O
break	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
via	O
email	O
this	O
St	B-other
Patrick's	I-other
Day	I-other
.	O
#StPatricksDay	O
#Vegas	B-place
not	O
#Hollywood	B-place

RT	O
@monclerlouis	O
:	O
HIS	O
LOCK	O
SCREEN	O
LITERALLY	O
SAME	O
http://t.co/dh58Y4ZZlz	O

Happy	O
St.	B-other
Patrick's	I-other
Day	I-other
from	O
Sedona	B-place
,	I-place
Arizona	I-place
!	O
http://t.co/5M0Ze53y79	O

.	O
@audreywatters	O
very	O
critical	O
of	O
#SXSWEDU	O
.	O
"	O
SXSWedu	O
.	O
This	O
Again	O
.	O
"	O
http://t.co/pE3qhCQbZw	O
via	O
@hackeducation	O

Kakak	O
@Yudi_SAGA	O
follow	O
@QibooClothing	O
dongg	O
,	O
dan	O
simak	O
TL	O
nya	O
,	O
ada	O
new	O
product	O
:)	O

RT	O
@juthy	O
:	O
ME	O
?	O
TOO	O
AGGRESSIVE	O
?	O
!	O
?	O

@MVJPhot	O
This	O
record	O
was	O
signed	O
by	O
@garlandjeffreys	O
and	O
the	O
DJ	O
was	O
shocked	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
NEVER	O
played	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
hear	O
it	O
first	O
.	O

hmm	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
malem	O
minggunya	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

RT	O
:	O
DJs	O
send	O
your	O
mixtapes	O
to	O
mixtape	O
@	O
septin911	B-organization
.	O
com	O
#septin911	O

Shit	O
tooo	O
to	O
funny	O
to	O
me	O

@custardtop	O
Hello	O
Madeline	B-person
Hows	O
you	O
?	O
X	O

#Parenthood	B-product
-	O
Joel	B-person
is	O
still	O
a	O
jackass	O

@Hamzified	O
Hayee	O
Rabba	O
.	O
Yeh	O
kiya	O
keh	O
rahay	O
hain	O
aap	O
?	O
:	O
O	O

@gabbyxnoud	O
ewww	O
omg	O
:	O
(	O
so	O
embarrassed	O
but	O
I	O
just	O
didn't	O
gafos	O
ja	O
feel	O
?	O

Sorry	O
guysRT	O
@Leafs93dmart	O
:	O
8	O
losses	O
in	O
a	O
row	O
for	O
the	O
#Leafs	B-organization
why	O
always	O
this	O
time	O
of	O
year	O
why	O
!	O
!	O
Choke	O
much	O
?	O
#TMLtalk	O
http://t.co/iboPEmgycz	O

Ak	O
xsey	O
tidur	O
male	O
nim	O
,	O
nok	O
buat	O
fyp	O
rapak	O
ph	O
subuh	O
pg	O
esokkk	O

Macieeeeek	O
jak	O
najdalej	O
!	O

RT	O
@hamiltonecdev	O
:	O
Just	O
met	O
with	O
SBEC	B-organization
client	O
@Specialappu	O
-	O
great	O
things	O
to	O
come	O
with	O
this	O
small	O
biz	O
!	O
#HamOnt	O
#autism	O

No	O
booty	O
selfies	O
y	O
'	O
all	O
suck	O

Quetta	O
:	O
Mashriqi	O
Bypass	O
Say	O
Aik	O
Shakhs	O
Ki	O
Laash	O
Mili	O
Hain	O
.	O
Rescue	O
Zarai	O
Balochistan	O
A	O
.	O
S	O
AZIZ	O

smh	O
is	O
all	O
i	O
can	O
say	O
.	O
lls	O

@amorgan_11	O
welp	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
stx	O

@ShotLeft	O
@scarletnguni	O
I'm	O
waiting	O
for	O
ma	O
Nguni	O
and	O
the	O
cobra	O
!	O

@Elbarbie	O
EU	B-organization
Parliament	I-organization
event	O
20	O
March	O
:	O
http://t.co/sy2LIr4SVS	O
Let	O
us	O
know	O
if	O
you	O
wish	O
to	O
join	O
!	O

falem	O
a	O
merda	O
que	O
for	O
eu	O
amo	O
ser	O
fa	O
da	O
magcon	O
fo	O
da	O
se	O

"	O
I'm	O
officially	O
retiring	O
"	O
RT	O
@justinbieber	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
studio	O

RT	O
@iMeDrama	O
:	O
#TumhariPaakhi	O
He	O
said	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
.	O
Hahaha	O
Cutest	O
Scene	O
!	O
you	O
guys	O
are	O
SO	O
CUTE	O
@Miqbalkhan	O
@AryaSmilesa	O
#BestCoupleOfAllTime	O

Never	O
forget	O
5sos	O
loves	O
you	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
https://t.co/WgyNa9EuhV	O

Selamat	O
bersantap	O
sahur	O
bagi	O
yg	O
akan	O
menjalankan	O
ibadah	O
puasa	O
hari	O
ini	O
,	O
waktu	O
Imsak	O
Sidoarjo	O
pukul	O
04	O
.	O
07	O
WIB	O
.	O
Semoga	O
berkah	O
Dulur	O
:)	O

RT	O
@sarangniall	O
:	O
"	O
@irwinhelp	O
:	O
antisocial	O
,	O
sexual	O
and	O
drunk	O
wbu	O
http://t.co/2jnS6vCDYJ	O
"	O
pervert	O
drunken	O
and	O
antisocial	O
oops	O

@sopiyyyaaa	O
hahahah	O
sachet	O
lang	O
to	O

RT	O
@polaa26	O
:	O
Yes	O
RT	O
@LaUReNsSDaD1118	O
:	O
Are	O
you	O
happy	O
?	O

Ain't	O
nothin	O
sexier	O
than	O
sexy	O
women	O
complimenting	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
.	O

{	O
@_somerholiclove	O
}	O
OMG	O
YOUR	O
COLOUFUL	O
BG	O
,	O
HEADER	O
AND	O
ICON	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
LOVE	O
THEM	O
ALL	O

RT	O
@urbanjibaro	O
:	O
Tonight	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
very	O
proud	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
host	O
and	O
showcase	O
the	O
talents	O
of	O
an	O
amazing	O
Latina	O
#stereotypicallyme	O

@TheAngryElk	O
Are	O
you	O
familiar	O
with	O
Joseph	B-person
Campbell	I-person
?	O

So	O
I'll	O
let	O
you	O
guys	O
know	O
how	O
today	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O

@douxteemarie	O
@mybbpage	O
@AubraMarie	O
@Mike_Gruenling	O
@idkconner	O
yeah	O
right	O
!	O
'	O
We	O
will	O
see	O
lol	O

'	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
german	O
'	O
'	O
i	O
chose	O
spanish	O
'	O
*	O
silence	O
*	O
'	O
well	O
we	O
use	O
a	O
lot	O
of	O
german	O
here	O
'	O
'	O
oh	O
'	O

If	O
Eminem	B-person
wasn't	O
a	O
rapper	O
he	O
would	O
probably	O
be	O
a	O
Favstar	O
bigwig	O

im	O
here	O
for	O
Chris	B-person
Evans	I-person
and	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
touch	O
me	O

Need	O
a	O
survey	O
group	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
would	O
like	O
to	O
give	O
feedback	O
on	O
a	O
C4V	B-organization
feature	O
please	O
DM	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
really	O
need	O
your	O
help	O
.	O
#TeamC4V	B-organization

I'M	O
GOIN	O
'	O
WILD	O
FOR	O
THE	O
NIGHT	O
FUCK	O
BEIN	O
'	O
POLITE	O

@Bronco_Mike251	O
@CJ_BroncosPFS	O
Paste	O
your	O
tweets	O
into	O
an	O
article	O
.	O
There	O
,	O
you	O
wrote	O
something	O
!	O
:)	O

Or	O
whatever	O
that	O
poor	O
bastards	O
name	O
is	O
lol	O

Pokemon	B-product
triplet	O
gym	O
leader	O
bRothers	O
oh	O
my	O
god	O
http://t.co/KzhKhN9GI1	O

Ahmed	B-person
a	O
peddy	O
smh	O
should've	O
known	O

Fr	O
@sekar_sningsih	O
lalin	O
dayeuhkolot	O
ramai	O
lancar	O
,	O
walaupun	O
tdk	O
banjir	O
ttp	O
hati2	O
tweeps	O
,	O
jalan	O
berlubang	O
parah	O

RT	O
@edamamari	O
:	O
@blessyoujdb	O
@BibblesAriana	O
hey	O
your	O
eyes	O
are	O
really	O
pretty	O

Desculpa	O
,	O
mas	O
eu	O
sou	O
#ForaMarcelo	O
#FicaPolly	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
/	O
3	O

Local	O
Storm	O
Report	O
by	O
NWS	B-organization
TBW	I-organization
:	O
5	O
SE	O
Pinellas	O
Point	O
[	O
Gmz830	O
Co	O
,	O
FL	O
]	O
buoy	O
reports	O
MARINE	O
TSTM	O
WIND	O
of	O
M40	O
MPH	O
a	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
https://t.co/uhiclhk7iH	O

@BrooklynSadex	O
@kouri_yee	O
my	O
dad	O
always	O
come	O
with	O
the	O
curry	O
coat	O
and	O
jerk	O
chicken	O
.	O
Some	O
white	O
people	O
don't	O
ramp	O
.	O

I	O
want	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
cop	O
so	O
I	O
can	O
shoot	O
people	O
and	O
get	O
a	O
paid	O
vacay	O

@CARAMELNIAM	O
I'll	O
buy	O
you	O
some	O
English	O
tea	O
and	O
bring	O
it	O
back	O
for	O
you	O

RT	O
@DuduMavundla	O
:	O
@BBMzansi	O
Kuli	B-person
Roberts	I-person
cleaning	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
Lexi	B-person
is	O
just	O
sitting	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
watching	O
her	O
instead	O
of	O
helping	O
her	O
*	O
ClappingOnce	O
*	O

@JonHeem	O
nigga	O
I	O
can't	O
call	O
you	O
my	O
phone	O
is	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
use	O
the	O
iMessage	B-product

so	O
close	O
to	O
begin	O
in	O
love	O
#KCA	O
#VoteTheWantedUK	O

If	O
we	O
draft	O
Wiggins	B-person
,	O
I'm	O
going	O
out	O
and	O
buying	O
a	O
Wiggins	O
jersey	O
quick	O

@notrab	O
Did	O
you	O
get	O
ScreenFlow	B-product
yet	O
?	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
like	O
it	O
?	O

Somebody	O
That	O
I	O
Used	O
to	O
Know	O
-	O
Walk	O
off	O
the	O
Earth	O
(	O
Gotye	B-person
-	O
Cover	O
)	O
http://t.co/RfEoUbliRQ	O
via	O
@youtube	O

And	O
if	O
a	O
double	O
decker	O
bus	O
kills	O
the	O
both	O
of	O
us	O
,	O
the	O
pleasure	O
the	O
priveledge	O
was	O
mine	O
-	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
light	O
that	O
never	O
goes	O
out	O

@BigJimSports	O
Here's	O
how	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
could	O
happen	O
:	O
http://t.co/Be90wDGXFI	O

@_sarah_smile	O
listen	O
.	O
I	O
just	O
overpaid	O
like	O
a	O
fiend	O
.	O
I'm	O
done	O
.	O

Hi	O
,	O
@ATebbz	O
!	O
To	O
prevent	O
girls	O
from	O
matching	O
,	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
list	O
of	O
all	O
prom	O
dresses	O
at	O
each	O
school	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
let	O
girls	O
know	O
if	O
someone	O
has	O
a	O
dress	O
!	O

RT	O
@AkifDanials	O
:	O
Bila	O
kesakaian	O
kau	O
melanda	O
,	O
memang	O
aku	O
sekali	O
laa	O
jadi	O
sakai	O
macam	O
kau	O
.	O
Tapi	O
kau	O
lagi	O
sakai	O
-	O
.	O
-	O

Dinner	O
of	O
Pan	O
-	O
Fried	O
Duck	O
Breast	O
with	O
Chilli	O
Fried	O
Pok	O
Choi	O
,	O
Rice	O
Noodles	O
and	O
Pomegranate	O
Jus	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/tm4JhBI3g0	O

@LousPikachu	O
so	O
you	O
get	O
a	O
emoji	O
app	O
then	O
go	O
to	O
settings	O
and	O
find	O
your	O
keyboard	O
and	O
add	O
emoji	O

anyone	O
still	O
up	O
to	O
trade	O
follows	O
?	O
you	O
first	O
,	O
i	O
have	O
10	O
,	O
lemme	O
know	O
:)	O

ima	O
delete	O
all	O
these	O
social	O
network	O
apps	O
:(	O

One	O
more	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
a	O
few	O
hills	O
around	O
here	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
view	O
from	O
one	O
I	O
walk	O
dog	O
up	O
.	O
http://t.co/jzXVBNuTzf	O

Scary	O
listening	O
over	O
radio	O
l	O
Saying	O
they	O
needed	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
there	O
asap	O
l	O
They	O
are	O
out	O
now	O
,	O
safe	O
l	O
Water	O
now	O
over	O
roadway	O

All	O
my	O
cats	O
have	O
come	O
in	O
to	O
say	O
hello	O
before	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
.	O
Isn't	O
that	O
nice	O
?	O
Oh	O
no	O
,	O
hang	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
forgot	O
I	O
didnt	O
feed	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/yHG5SBU7Sp	O

@Isla_78	O
she	O
should	O
go	O
on	O
a	O
speaking	O
tour	O
.	O
Adorable	O
.	O

Very	O
proud	O
to	O
count	O
among	O
my	O
family	O
,	O
friends	O
and	O
colleagues	O
a	O
group	O
of	O
inspiring	O
and	O
dynamic	O
women	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
who	O
you	O
are	O
.	O
#IWD2014	O

@Renegal	O
Unless	O
of	O
course	O
its	O
about	O
close	O
friends	O
.	O

Earth	B-other
Hour	I-other
2014	I-other
with	O
#Acacia	B-organization
Africa	O
http://t.co/pr2gL92wH6	O
#acaciaafrica	O
#overland	O
#smallgroupsafaris	O
#southafrica	B-place

@MileyCyrus	O
@katyperry	O
YOU	O
ARE	O
SUCH	O
A	O
QUEEN	O
I	O
LOVE	O
YOU	O

@abmukaddam	O
jannat	O
granted	O
to	O
you	O
:	O
'	O
)	O

Listen	O
to	O
Happy	O
Mondays	O
this	O
morning	O
,	O
bringing	O
me	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
childhood	O
.	O

@bomikawe	O
be	O
mine	O
sinih	O
chage	O

@jngoddard	O
haha	O
that's	O
quite	O
the	O
collage	O
!	O
Love	O
you	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
thank	O
you	O
!	O

@AbbyHoward	O
we	O
need	O
them	O
to	O
look	O
more	O
relatable	O
,	O
give	O
them	O
human	O
skin	O
and	O
eyes	O
yes	O
perfect	O

@fadibau	O
Hi	O
Fadi	B-person
,	O
I'm	O
in	O
Los	B-place
Angeles	I-place
so	O
I	O
record	O
one	O
day	O
before	O
!	O
I	O
love	O
the	O
show	O
,	O
Bliss	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
guys	O
too	O
much	O
to	O
leave	O
.	O

yellow	O
cab	O
and	O
mcdo	O
in	O
a	O
day	O
.	O
di	O
ko	O
na	O
talaga	O
alam	O
sa	O
man	O
boobs	O
ko	O
hahaha	O
medyo	O
vulgar	O

@iAmTyraShanell	O
smile	O
young	O
lady	O
!	O
.	O
.	O
lol	O

MY	O
HEART	O
IS	O
BEATING	O
SO	O
LOUD	O
ARCHIE	O
IS	O
ABOUT	O
TO	O
COME	O
OUT	O
TO	O
FINN	B-person
CHLOE	B-person
IZZY	B-person
AND	O
CHOP	B-person
FUCK	O
FUCK	O

@papadaaaniell	O
ah	O
,	O
mamaya	O
,	O
inaantay	O
ko	O
pa	O
txt	O
ni	O
Jes	O
and	O
Lawr	O

@xshtonirwn	O
@fivesosfangirl	O
@4seconds_of_1d	O
oH	O
MY	O
GFD	O
WHAT	O
IS	O
THI	O
S	O

RT	O
@FirstKingMvni	O
:	O
I'm	O
not	O
sad	O
or	O
happy	O
.	O
Just	O
content	O
w	O
/	O
everything	O
.	O

Let's	O
celebrate	O
the	O
mikitary	O
chivers	O
among	O
us	O
@theCHIVE	O
@Seblastoff	O
http://t.co/557rIGYX2N	O

@eskimoguitarist	O
identifies	O
as	O
something	O
other	O
than	O
female	O
,	O
who	O
you	O
could	O
be	O
attracted	O
to	O
sexually	O
and	O
/	O
or	O
romantically	O
and	O
thus	O
sexually	O
?	O

RT	O
@NerudaLove	O
:	O
Farewell	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
go	O
within	O
a	O
drop	O
of	O
blood	O
circulating	O
in	O
my	O
veins	O
#neruda	B-person

@Miss_TaurusJ	O
Yes'm	O
.	O
Been	O
in	O
jail	O
for	O
the	O
past	O
two	O
months	O
.	O
His	O
hearing	O
for	O
fraud	O
should	O
be	O
coming	O
up	O
soon	O

@Mikey_ToBeOne	O
Today	O
is	O
my	O
birthday	O
and	O
i	O
was	O
wondering	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
follow	O
me	O
it	O
would	O
mean	O
so	O
much	O
to	O
me	O

Hate	O
men	O
that	O
when	O
are	O
drunk	O
like	O
fighting	O
:	O
(	O

@Movermike	O
Hey	O
Mike	B-person
.	O
Thanks	O
so	O
much	O
for	O
the	O
supportive	O
tweets	O
!	O
I	O
appreciate	O
it	O
.	O
David	B-person
http://t.co/QWkn0POlia	O

nothing	O
but	O
chance	O
lyrics	O
stuck	O
in	O
my	O
head	O

Thank	O
you	O
for	O
participating	O
in	O
#dnaofhappiness	B-other
and	O
making	O
it	O
a	O
big	O
success	O
.	O
Congratulations	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
winners	O
and	O
participants	O
.	O

RT	O
@metroj	O
:	O
Taste	O
of	O
the	O
Islands	O
Mobile	O
Cafe	O
@eatdrinkjax	O
http://t.co/zdlIceonbQ	O
http://t.co/xat1xN24Os	O

@iamageek	O
i	O
thought	O
literally	O
everybody	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
complete	O
shit	O

@CouncillorFord	O
Y	O
did	O
ur	O
bro	O
refuse2meet	O
w	O
/	O
me	O
5x	O
,	O
y	O
did	O
u	O
fall	O
back	O
on	O
promise2help	O
me	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
anything	O
i	O
needed	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
disrespect	O
my	O
culture	O
?	O
!	O

#HuffingtonPost	B-organization
~	O
14	O
-	O
Year	O
-	O
Old	O
Leah	B-person
Kritzer	I-person
Disappears	O
While	O
Walking	O
Family	O
Dog	O
http://t.co/987wHnSjd7	O
#UFO4UBlogUS	O

The	O
chances	O
of	O
a	O
band	O
opening	O
TWICE	O
in	O
a	O
row	O
for	O
another	O
group	O
is	O
so	O
rare	O
and	O
for	O
5SOS	B-organization
to	O
accomplish	O
that	O
is	O
fucking	O
incredible	O

@JustJoshinYu	O
Solar	O
power	O
nut	O
?	O
Check	O
out	O
:	O
@SolarReserve	O

I	O
donated	O
$	O
10	O
!	O
#birthdayproject	O

A	O
possible	O
Wichita	B-place
St.	I-place
/	O
Kentucky	B-place
in	O
the	O
second	O
round	O
?	O
Yes	O
please	O
.	O

Tiffany	B-person
Evans	I-person
-	O
Promise	O
Ring	O

@TEQUILASUNRlSE	O
@beaniekeaton	O
thats	O
in	O
missouri	B-place
lol	O

EXM	O
:	O
Andrew	B-person
Demetriou's	I-person
reign	O
as	O
AFL	B-organization
supremo	O
will	O
end	O
after	O
the	O
2014	O
season	O
.	O
http://t.co/ZtJXg2TSeD	O

Geeente	O
a	O
Angela	B-person
dormiu	O
na	O
prova	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
tu	O
viu	O
isso	O
Bones	O
?	O
#TeamMarcelo	O
#BBB14	O

#AngelaYEG	O
Nairobi	B-place
conference	O
challenged	O
prioritization	O
of	O
white	O
women	O
.	O

@WRahMada	O
semoga	O
harinya	O
berkah	O
,	O
mas	O
'	O
eeee	O
!	O
:D	O

Group	O
seeks	O
more	O
jobs	O
-	O
http://t.co/nFR6cD7zZi	O

You	O
know	O
you	O
were	O
completely	O
frozen	O
and	O
snow	O
covered	O
when	O
your	O
hair	O
freezes	O
#thawingout	O

@chris_fecci	O
@jetswhispers	O
Vick	B-person
has	O
already	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
DJack's	B-person
on	O
team	O
.	O
Now	O
someone	O
is	O
stretching	O
that	O
for	O
a	O
headline	O
.	O

@aahfeekiee	O
u	O
watch	O
hannibal	B-product
too	O
oh	O
ur	O
perfect	O
!	O
!	O

@OktaWRP	O
hihihi	O
aku	O
no	O
comment	O
aja	O
deh	O
(	O
?	O
)	O
xD	O

RT	O
@CRKARLA	O
:	O
#EarthSciences	O
Great	O
earthquakes	O
,	O
water	O
under	O
pressure	O
,	O
high	O
risk	O
:	O
http://t.co/3eR7DcgnGE	O
http://t.co/nurANBRVF2	O

She	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
off	O
on	O
us	O
about	O
our	O
tattoos	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
my	O
piercings	O

It's	O
like	O
we	O
stumbled	O
on	O
the	O
storyboards	O
for	O
the	O
next	O
Wes	B-person
Anderson	I-person
film	O
.	O
http://t.co/piiO2Fnnu7	O

Kalau	O
jadi	O
gubernur	O
Jakarta	B-place
cuma	O
jadi	O
batu	O
loncatan	O
,	O
jadi	O
Presiden	O
juga	O
jadi	O
batu	O
loncatan	O
aja	O
untuk	O
target	O
berikutnya	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
gak	O
tau	O
apa	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

Photoset	O
:	O
stay	O
-	O
nakd	O
:	O
Franco	B-person
Klein	I-person
http://t.co/7DNtpVPNzM	O

EPL	B-organization
champions	O
Elect	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
#Chelsea	B-organization
fc	I-organization

kupotea	O
njia	O
ndo	O
kujua	O
njia	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
waaah	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

@MEr_winZ	O
sekalian	O
bantu	O
masak	O
jg	O
ya	O
,	O
,	O
Kk	O
:D	O

@mjdawgs	O
I	O
guess	O
you	O
should	O
just	O
stick	O
with	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
:	O
boy	O
bands	O
.	O

Rugged	O
and	O
take	O
being	O
tossed	O
around	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
please	O
!	O
Huntington	B-product
Canvas	I-product
Laptop	I-product
Brief	I-product
on	O
sale	O
@Thrillist	O
http://t.co/mTQIGl4I96	O

Not	O
only	O
is	O
it	O
Friday	B-other
but	O
it's	O
the	O
last	O
Friday	B-other
of	O
Winter	O
#morereasontocelebrate	O
#tgif	O
#whereismydrink	O

V8	B-product
Supercars	I-product
should	O
just	O
run	O
an	O
extra	O
race	O
over	O
in	O
Aussie	O
to	O
keep	O
us	O
entertained	O
#F1	O
#BBCF1	O
#Rain	O

Spitting	O
Image	O
.	O
MT	O
@FIFAcom	O
Messi	B-person
&	O
amp	O
;	O
Ronaldo	B-person
get	O
'	O
ninot	O
'	O
treatment	O
in	O
Valencia	B-place
for	O
Las	B-other
Fallas	I-other
.	O
http://t.co/TFVAOWUe1j	O
http://t.co/yNX71JnQg5	O

@notsohemmings	O
@RyanAbe	O
@orionnichole	O
*	O
photoshops	O
a	O
picture	O
of	O
all	O
of	O
us	O
hugging	O

RT	O
@wgfenix	O
:	O
Las	O
palabras	O
solo	O
llenan	O
un	O
vacio	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
Las	O
acciones	O
un	O
recuerdo	O
para	O
toda	O
la	O
vida	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
#anecdotasdeunBolo	O

@LGrides	O
@Mightybee1983	O
my	O
wife	O
doesn't	O
want	O
me	O
but	O
LSP	O
sure	O
does	O
.	O

good	O
morning	O
#Gamers	O
#Geeks	O
and	O
#Misfits	O
I'm	O
running	O
on	O
4	O
hours	O
sleep	O
,	O
but	O
that's	O
completely	O
fine	O
because	O
I	O
played	O
#StickOfTruth	B-product
last	O
night	O
!	O

@Sianakeis_	O
loooool	O
choong	O
uno	O
well	O
thanks	O

RT	O
@mukezayn	O
:	O
fell	O
asleep	O
with	O
my	O
phone	O
on	O
lost	O
30	O
%	O
chargers	O
and	O
followcan	O

@dukeofmuke	O
I	O
am	O
Luke's	B-person
lady	O
im	O
sorry	O

@GrooveGrl4	O
(	O
contd	O
.	O
)	O
sending	O
you	O
their	O
strength	O
and	O
wisdom	O
to	O
help	O
carry	O
you	O
through	O
!	O

@Sir_Tiago	O
lol	O
,	O
sorry	O
sir	O
.	O
Don't	O
I	O
get	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
committee	O
member	O
also	O
?	O
Lol	O

Only	O
cosmos	O
change	O
was	O
@john1988murphy	O
in	O
Alan	B-person
out	O
.	O
Says	O
a	O
lot	O
that	O
mate	O
.	O
@adamduffy1983	O
@woodyl	O
@StephenMaddo78	O
@gedscott27	O
@CarlMckenna4	O

I	O
framed	O
the	O
Free	O
#Disney	O
Park	O
Maps	O
and	O
used	O
them	O
as	O
art	O
in	O
my	O
guest	O
room	O
!	O
http://t.co/noCTjwEfF8	O

How	O
many	O
times	O
can	O
you	O
put	O
two	O
Lego	B-product
pieces	O
together	O
before	O
they	O
break	O
?	O
30	O
,	O
000	O
+	O
http://t.co/AMokNvnMq8	O

Blacklight	O
music	O
is	O
always	O
fucking	O
mint	O

Associate	O
Veterinarian	O
-	O
CO	O
(	O
http://t.co/s1qUnT8VVA	O
)	O
#Veterinarian	O
#jobs	O
#job	O
#GetAllJobs	O

@ebnast	O
no	O
,	O
you're	O
just	O
dark	O
.	O

@susiekearley	O
and	O
I	O
add	O
people	O
to	O
my	O
lists	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
and	O
again	O
I	O
post	O
a	O
tweet	O
to	O
get	O
people	O
talking	O
and	O
intro	O
them	O
:)	O
0O	O
-	O

@sarangh4e	O
contempt	O
is	O
like	O
the	O
opposite	O
of	O
content	O
.	O
thanks	O
ho	O

put	O
your	O
ass	O
on	O
my	O
dick	O
and	O
pose	O
that	O
shit	O

Niggas	O
was	O
speaking	O
Spanish	O
all	O
damn	O
day	O
B	O
.	O

2	O
.	O
"	O
@teddyferrari1	O
:	O
"	O
He	O
fool	O
pass	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
@TheoPhlow	O
:	O
He	O
Be	O
Senior	O
Boy	O
roff	O
"	O
@teddyferrari1	O
:	O
But	O
Welbie	B-person
be	O
some	O
underrated	O
dude	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
"	O
"	O
"	O

@netmediatama	O
min	O
,	O
kok	O
pas	O
pertandingan	O
habis	O
hendra	O
/	O
ahsan	O
di	O
wawancarai	O
gak	O
di	O
tayangin	O
min	O
:(	O

Helpful	O
@ImpactSP2	O
analysis	O
of	O
ntl	O
#ece	O
sector	O
.	O
http://t.co/Zx1zXMKz1U	O
.	O
Tip	O
of	O
the	O
hat	O
@ClyonsSFC	O

Dan	O
buat	O
yg	O
pake	O
android	O
sekarang	O
udah	O
ada	O
aplikasinya	O
jadi	O
bisa	O
lebih	O
gampang	O
aksesnya	O
.	O
Download	O
link	O
nya	O
ada	O
di	O
website	O
suma	O
.	O
;	O
)	O

18	O
-	O
1	O
BUCS	B-organization
!	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
7th	O
vs	O
.	O
Toronto	B-organization
.	O
This	O
is	O
obviously	O
the	O
premiere	O
offense	O
in	O
MLB	B-organization
right	O
now	O
.	O
:-)	O
#LetsGoBucs	O

Semangat	O
kuliahnya	O
mas	O
,	O
kuliah	O
yg	O
rajin	O
ya	O
@Asep_Nur23	O
^	O
,	O
^	O

#NewRelease	O
-	O
My	B-product
Nature	I-product
Friends	I-product
:	I-product
A	I-product
-	I-product
Z	I-product
Rhyming	I-product
Picture	I-product
Book	I-product
http://t.co/KGdQFmlaCT	O
#rhyming	O
#childrensfiction	O
pls	O
retweet	O
n	O
x	O
@vickiemckeehan	O

CMS	B-organization
proposes	O
tweaks	O
to	O
risk	O
corridor	O
calculations	O
,	O
"	O
in	O
recognition	O
of	O
the	O
ongoing	O
uncertainty	O
and	O
changes	O
in	O
the	O
market	O
in	O
2015	O
"	O
.	O

"	O
this	O
next	O
song	O
goes	O
out	O
to	O
my	O
baby	O
"	O
PANFHOSNFHAKS	O
http://t.co/lmh8yctpRn	O

@Drag0nista	O
Also	O
,	O
moderates	O
,	O
by	O
definition	O
,	O
are	O
willing	O
to	O
compromise	O
.	O
The	O
hard	O
right	O
doesn't	O
.	O

RIHANNA	B-person
UNFOLLOWED	O
DEMI	B-person
NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO	O

lifes	O
-	O
messy	O
-	O
palette	O
asked	O
:	O
Hello	O
Ms.	B-person
Han	I-person
!	O
First	O
off	O
thank	O
you	O
so	O
much	O
for	O
all	O
your	O
wonderful	O
books	O
.	O
I	O
just	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/golyLuOe2P	O

"	O
@Cupidscupcakes	O
:	O
Today's	O
#ChefsChoice	O
is	O
Muskoka	B-product
Mocha	O
!	O
#espresso	O
#chocolate	O
http://t.co/kCkrGiQFcI	O
"	O
#Oakville	B-place
#ShopLocal	O

The	B-product
Sims	I-product
3	I-product
:	I-product
King	I-product
Family	I-product
(	O
Part	O
27	O
)	O
The	O
Genie	O
and	O
Star	O
:	O
http://t.co/n1md8sZwJU	O
via	O
@YouTube	O

@CrickChris	O
Thanks	O
for	O
the	O
rt	O
,	O
Chris	B-person
.	O
Looking	O
forward	O
to	O
checking	O
out	O
your	O
work	O
.	O

@TaylorFaulk	O
I	O
almost	O
stuck	O
the	O
landing	O
*	O
takes	O
bow	O
*	O

"	O
Oi	O
eu	O
sou	O
dono	O
de	O
uma	O
gravadora	O
famosa	O
e	O
voce	O
tem	O
futuro	O
como	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
baterista	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
"	O
m	O
o	O
r	O
r	O
i	O

Current	O
installation	O
of	O
#FreeBSD	B-product
has	O
been	O
on	O
my	O
Thinkpad	B-product
for	O
nearly	O
2	O
years	O
now	O
,	O
building	O
world	O
one	O
last	O
time	O
before	O
a	O
fresh	O
reinstall	O

@mjfreshyfresh	O
and	O
a	O
bar	O
.	O
With	O
mood	O
lighting	O
.	O
#urgentrequest	O

RT	O
@saraahpina	O
:	O
turn	O
off	O
your	O
mind	O
,	O
relax	O
and	O
float	O
downstream	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

@Aishahichaa	O
hehe	O
,	O
intro	O
donk	O
?	O
:D	O

I	O
didn't	O
even	O
notice	O
twitter	O
was	O
down	O
.	O

@SouthLondonGirl	O
@carolinesweetie	O
I'm	O
going	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
one	O
of	O
me	O
aged	O
25	O
and	O
peachy	O
.	O
Sod	O
the	O
false	O
advertising	O
.	O
You	O
lot	O
have	O
seen	O
me	O
anyway	O
.	O

RT	O
@olegunnnn	O
:	O
Mending	O
jomblo	O
tapi	O
bahagia	O
apa	O
punya	O
pacar	O
tapi	O
pasea	O
wae	O
?	O
#jawab	O
~	O
@pry_carraba	O

RT	O
@TallPaul612	O
:	O
We	O
could	O
just	O
go	O
out	O
back	O
and	O
dig	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
ground	O
like	O
them	O
ol	O
'	O
gete	O
-	O
anishinabeg	O
did	O

#MinnieMouse	B-product
had	O
no	O
bedroom	O
in	O
#wdw	O
#ToonTown	B-place
.	O
For	O
more	O
#disney	B-organization
facts	O
listen	O
to	O
http://t.co/YfSZ8W3SFh	O
#vaultofwalt	O
#disney	B-organization

These	O
are	O
REAL	O
birthday	O
jorts	O
.	O
Who	O
doesn't	O
want	O
a	O
pic	O
of	O
themselves	O
on	O
their	O
own	O
butt	O
?	O
http://t.co/fdT37LLDWI	O

Move	O
Glee	B-product
back	O
to	O
Thursdays	O
,	O
nobody	O
is	O
watching	O
TVD	O
anyway	O

Check	O
out	O
my	O
other	O
logo	O
i	O
made	O
yesterday	O
:)	O
http://t.co/OVlzEkS63u	O

@scienceofeds	O
I	O
do	O
know	O
that	O
"	O
forced	O
feed	O
"	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
synonymous	O
with	O
"	O
no	O
emotional	O
support	O
"	O
,	O
so	O
I'm	O
not	O
sure	O
if	O
it's	O
still	O
correllated	O
.	O

Aduh	O
RT	O
@dwitasaridwita	O
:	O
Jangan	O
bikin	O
orang	O
terlalu	O
lama	O
nunggu	O
,	O
ketidakpastian	O
darimu	O
suatu	O
saat	O
akan	O
menabung	O
luka	O
untuk	O
dirimu	O
sendiri	O
.	O

TAH	O
BACA	O
RT	O
"	O
@TweetRAMALAN	O
:	O
#Pisces	O
Gerak	O
-	O
geriknya	O
cepat	O
,	O
otaknya	O
jernih	O
dan	O
ambisius	O
,	O
sensitif	O
dan	O
mudah	O
sekali	O
tersinggung	O
"	O

RT	O
@bitpay	O
:	O
BitPay	B-organization
Abre	O
Sede	O
Latinoamericana	O
en	O
Argentina	B-place
#Bitcoin	B-product
http://t.co/uMXYPKFcv8	O

@fymd	O
It	O
is	O
tough	O
to	O
fit	O
it	O
all	O
in	O
isn't	O
it	O
!	O
I'd	O
like	O
to	O
do	O
a	O
conference	O
outside	O
Belfast	B-place
as	O
I	O
get	O
easily	O
distracted	O
by	O
client	O
work	O
!	O

It	O
is	O
highly	O
unlikely	O
that	O
the	O
much	O
-	O
anticipated	O
verdict	O
in	O
the	O
Vybz	B-person
Kartel	I-person
murder	O
trial	O
will	O
be	O
handed	O
down	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/FSHFk0ly6Y	O

Bellator	O
MMA	O
112	O
:	O
699	O
,	O
000	O
viewers	O
http://t.co/sEKU8r5Xpk	O

@karachikhatmal	O
The	O
4	O
southern	O
states	O
are	O
Aussie	O
-	O
rules	O
.	O
The	O
game	O
was	O
invented	O
here	O
in	O
Melb	B-place
.	O
We're	O
the	O
home	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
cricket	O
Test	O
and	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

Getting	O
ready	O
for	O
#hoth	O
only	O
the	O
essentials	O
http://t.co/0mMHfkJMFj	O

Pacers	B-organization
bet	O
not	O
lose	O
to	O
fuckin	O
Boston	B-place

Hi	O
guys	O
.	O
New	O
post	O
!	O
Grilled	B-product
Almond	I-product
Butter	I-product
Honey	I-product
Banana	I-product
Sandwich	I-product
http://t.co/X8Hfdi7VP0	O

RT	O
@BuzzFeedBooks	O
:	O
Writing	O
?	O
Get	O
inspired	O
by	O
these	O
@NewYorker	O
writers	O
and	O
editors	O
:	O
http://t.co/V0ZzuAX1uP	O

RT	O
@z_dizzle14	O
:	O
You	O
know	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
Iowa	B-place
when	O
it's	O
43	O
degrees	O
out	O
and	O
it	O
feels	O
like	O
summer	O

#AsarMoments	O
7am	O
classes	O
.	O

RT	O
@OwnNathan	O
:	O
RT	O
@TWofficialArmy	O
:	O
My	O
timeline	O
has	O
suddenly	O
gave	O
up	O
and	O
stopped	O
voting	O
.	O
#KCA	O
#VoteTheWantedUK	O

Creamy	O
Avocado	O
Hummus	O
http://t.co/rUCbAVKfF5	O

Only	O
Napoleon	B-person
did	O
more	O
than	O
me	O
.	O
But	O
I'm	O
taller	O
than	O
him	O
-	O
Silvio	B-person
Berlusconi	I-person

RT	O
@NUbaseballcoach	O
:	O
Baseball	O
3	O
/	O
7	O
friday	O
.	O
Everyone	O
will	O
be	O
outside	O
3	O
-	O
5	O
.	O

#Lrt	O
I'm	O
bout	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
gonna	O
come	O
sit	O
wit	O
me	O

RT	O
@cautionespinosa	O
:	O
@TheMattEspinosa	O
One	O
day	O
I'll	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
THAT	O
timeline	O
bet	O

@excuseyou77	O
I	O
hate	O
when	O
that	O
happens	O
.	O
Bring	O
on	O
Spring	O
!	O

RT	O
@CHORAVALDIVIA	O
:	O
Corinthians	O
na	O
TL	O
Kd	O
?	O

If	O
Harry	B-person
is	O
racist	O
for	O
wearing	O
an	O
indian	O
hat	O
then	O
Justin	B-person
Bieber	I-person
is	O
racist	O
for	O
acting	O
so	O
nigga	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
racist	O
for	O
loving	O
tacos	O
?	O
WTF	O

@kezeuka	O
the	O
girl	O
with	O
the	O
beanie	O
that	O
kissed	O
her	O
hand	O
I	O
could	O
actually	O
see	O
them	O
together	O

RT	O
@GuWapNigga_	O
:	O
In	O
the	O
beginning	O
you	O
think	O
its	O
forever	O
.	O

China's	B-place
Struggle	O
to	O
Forget	O
,	O
via	O
@nytimes	O
http://t.co/WzEO6Z1sAa	O

RT	O
@DavidEDrew	O
:	O
Sad	O
to	O
hear	O
the	O
news	O
about	O
Bob	B-person
Crow	I-person
.	O
Always	O
there	O
for	O
his	O
members	O
and	O
passionately	O
believed	O
in	O
public	O
service	O
.	O

@Nashgrier	O
follow	O
me	O
pleaaaase	O
nashh	O

should've	O
brung	O
that	O
nude	O
polish	O
from	O
school	O
.	O

Canelo	B-person
would	O
have	O
almost	O
certainly	O
won	O
the	O
fight	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
powers	O
that	O
be	O
do	O
him	O
no	O
favours	O
with	O
acts	O
like	O
these	O
.	O

@AMovingCastle	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
fed	O
all	O
the	O
crayons	O
to	O
her	O
already	O
what	O
would	O
waiting	O
do	O
for	O
yOHHHHHHHHHH	O

@feline_rouge	O
HORRIFIC	O
,	O
ISN'T	O
IT	O
.	O

@Andurhey	O
ganyan	O
magsmile	O
ang	O
walang	O
problema	O
eh	O
haha	O
:)	O

#Terkini	O
:	O
Belanda	O
ingin	O
lebih	O
berperan	O
bangun	O
ekonomi	O
Indonesia	O
http://t.co/SyTJmro8vU	O

Miley	B-person
Cyrus	I-person
about	O
the	O
self	O
pity	O
at	O
#	O
1	O
http://t.co/OTf5pRCyTj	O
#MileyUncensored	O

RT	O
@_ziamsaywut_	O
:	O
harry	B-person
and	O
lux	B-person
then	O
and	O
now	O
:	O
'	O
)	O
#Vote1DUK	O
#KCA	O
http://t.co/sKTeyyP7wW	O

Watch	O
'	O
Blue	O
is	O
the	O
warmest	O
colour	O
'	O
if	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
discover	O
what	O
you're	O
into	O
sexually	O
.	O
#nonewsforme	O
Also	O
:	O
don't	O
watch	O
it	O
with	O
your	O
grandma	O
.	O

My	O
cousin	O
just	O
moved	O
in	O
with	O
us	O
till	O
the	O
summer	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

RT	O
@Rarahmaajeng	O
:	O
Selamat	O
ulangtahun	O
vega	O
{	O
}	O
@urayvega	O

@RunningAround42	O
Wahoo	O
!	O
We're	O
cheering	O
you	O
on	O
.	O
See	O
you	O
in	O
September	O
at	O
the	O
start	O
line	O
(	O
and	O
the	O
finish	O
line	O
!	O
)	O
#ArmyRun	O

@udit_agarwal	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
action	O
items	O
lie	O
at	O
the	O
individuals	O
end	O
.	O
.	O
And	O
yes	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
job	O
which	O
fits	O
into	O
that	O
aspiration	O
,	O
we	O
talk	O
again	O

You	O
can't	O
buy	O
#selfrespect	O

they	O
shouldn't	O
had	O
filmed	O
the	O
bgc12	B-product
reunion	I-product
.	O
.	O
.	O
there	O
was	O
literally	O
not	O
point	O
in	O
doing	O
it	O
that	O
early	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

RT	O
@check_tha_stats	O
:	O
Damn	O
u	O
gave	O
up	O
mcdonalds	B-organization
for	O
this	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
#shame	O
"	O
@CollegeBoyNick	O
:	O
#ToeSuckingHours	O
"	O

#debt	O
:	O
Lowest	O
number	O
of	O
home	O
repossessions	O
in	O
three	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/pf51VVz09u	O

@Michael5SOS	O
whats	O
ur	O
fave	O
game	O
to	O
play	O

4	O
/	O
26	O
:	O
Discover	O
Goddard	O
Day	O
in	O
#VT	O
for	O
anyone	O
interested	O
in	O
low	O
-	O
residency	O
BA	O
,	O
BFA	O
,	O
MA	O
and	O
MFA	O
degrees	O
.	O
RSVP	O
http://t.co/GeQruGpCIl	O

Good	O
morning	O
everyone	O
!	O
It's	O
Thursday	O
~	O
Time	O
to	O
get	O
motivated	O
and	O
let's	O
make	O
today	O
a	O
good	O
day	O
:)	O

5	O
ways	O
to	O
help	O
you	O
pay	O
your	O
council	O
tax	O
http://t.co/Nn7Bm6zDf4	O

@minnielaulau	O
UK	B-place
returns	O
can	O
take	O
10	O
working	O
days	O
,	O
so	O
please	O
allow	O
this	O
time	O
.	O

The	O
duet	O
of	O
"	O
One	B-product
For	I-product
My	I-product
Baby	I-product
"	O
by	O
Tony	B-person
Bennett	I-person
&	O
amp	O
;	O
John	B-person
Mayer	I-person
is	O
perfect	O
.	O
Been	O
listening	O
to	O
this	O
song	O
since	O
the	O
moment	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
about	O
this	O
!	O

RT	O
@Xtel007	O
:	O
Great	O
.	O
Now	O
Quinn's	B-person
never	O
dying	O
.	O

@HasheemTheDream	O
thanks	O
for	O
highfiveing	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
thunder	O
tunnel	O
!	O
totally	O
made	O
my	O
night	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O

@mohamadilyas3	O
sesak	O
nafas	O
i	O
guess	O

RT	O
@edbrisson	O
:	O
My	O
ECCC	O
schedule	O
:	O
http://t.co/jglVUjZBK1	O

RT	O
@lifesandcastle	O
:	O
Swarovski	B-product
Crystal	I-product
Tennis	I-product
Bracelet	I-product
from	O
Sparkle	B-organization
Plenty	I-organization
+	O
Giveaway	O
http://t.co/4B5Wk7kJlg	O
via	O
@TwoClassyChics	O

Apr	O
2007	O
:	O
Plastic	O
surgery	O
in	O
Lebanon	B-place
#Lebanon	O
http://t.co/1F42806QF8	O

+	O
TAKING	O
AWAY	O
ALL	O
OF	O
HER	O
PLANS	O
FOR	O
SPRING	O
BREAK	O
SHE	O
IS	O
IN	O
SEVENTH	O
GRADE	O
YOU	O
DONT	O
FUCKING	O
DO	O
THAT	O
TO	O
A	O
THIRTEEN	O
YEAR	O
OLD	O

Who	O
r	O
u	O
and	O
y	O
did	O
u	O
rt	O
my	O
selfie	O

@GaugeMalamute	O
It's	O
so	O
early	O
though	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
I	O
couldn't	O
handle	O
that	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

Jar	B-product
of	I-product
Hearts	I-product
-	O
Christina	B-person
Perri	I-person
Lyrics	O
:	O
http://t.co/TEwGUvTh61	O
via	O
@youtube	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
333333333333	O

Lol	O
O	O
grant	O
?	O
"	O
@Neezylay	O
:	O
Lol	O
:)	O
"	O
@JOJO_khb29	O
:	O
HeyBoo	O
"	O
@Neezylay	O
:	O
Won't	O
laugh	O
at	O
oomf's	O
jokes	O
no	O
more	O
(	O
.	O
_	O
.	O
"	O

Hoy	O
a	O
darle	O
tune	O
up	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
bonito	O
dia	O
.	O
http://t.co/UA2gTqSW3y	O

@dreams_ofyou	O
And	O
thank	O
you	O
!	O
Enjoy	O
your	O
day	O
as	O
well	O
.	O
:)	O

@WindoftheStars	O
Well	O
you	O
have	O
that	O
.	O
All	O
repairs	O
have	O
60	O
day	O
warranties	O
.	O

@OregonPhilsphan	O
Has	O
it	O
really	O
been	O
that	O
long	O
?	O
I	O
remember	O
laughing	O
at	O
how	O
stupid	O
they	O
all	O
were	O
.	O

It's	O
so	O
quiet	O
here	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
literally	O
hear	O
yourself	O
think	O
.	O
It's	O
refreshing	O
being	O
away	O
from	O
all	O
the	O
noise	O
.	O

@PolysporinCA	O
#SpringBrings	O
can't	O
wait	O
to	O
paint	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
house	O

@Shaister	O
Its	O
dead	O
.	O
I'd	O
have	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
.	O

WHAT	O
RT	O
@hyukarmpits	O
:	O
AT	O
THE	O
START	O
OF	O
HYUK	O
RAP	O
PART	O
THEY	O
BOTH	O
WENT	O
TO	O
EACH	O
OTHER	O
AND	O
HYUK	O
SHOWED	O
HIS	O
SHOULDER	O
TO	O
HAE	O

RT	O
@matteoruano	O
:	O
Bout	O
to	O
hit	O
the	O
gym	O
with	O
some	O
#giggs	O
@mrBennyBanks	O
and	O
real	O
music	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
GRIME	O
!	O

most	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
i	O
have	O
bookmarked	O
are	O
about	O
phanfiction	O

What	O
a	O
save	O
by	O
Moran	B-person
on	O
Nathan	B-person
Bastian	I-person
!	O
1	O
-	O
1	O
with	O
10	O
:	O
24	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
2nd	O
period	O
.	O

RT	O
@FxTxxn	O
:	O
Sampai	O
jatuh	O
phone	O
ak	O
gelak	O
punya	O
pasal	O
.	O
Benti	O
lah	O
woi	O
.	O
Penat	O
dah	O
nie	O
xD	O
hm	O
hahhahha	O

Creepy	O
nung	O
dolls	O
,	O
okay	O
.	O
:(	O
:(	O
:(	O

529	O
people	O
sentences	O
to	O
death	O
in	O
#Egypt	B-place
for	O
killing	O
a	O
police	O
officer	O
:	O
http://t.co/48UCBDjBDf	O

We're	O
showing	O
our	O
fans	O
some	O
#love	O
today	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
#yoga	O
#mat	O
#bag	O
by	O
@olovesm	O
#giveaway	O
-	O
-	O
http://t.co/cmtRyesQMa	O
#healthy	O
#skin	O

I	O
don't	O
know	O
how	O
else	O
to	O
sum	O
it	O
up	O
Cause	O
words	O
ain't	O
good	O
enough	O
,	O
There's	O
no	O
way	O
I	O
can	O
explain	O
your	O
love	O
.	O
@zaynmalik	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
follow	O
me	O
6283	O

RT	O
@africvan	O
:	O
that	O
moment	O
when	O
your	O
so	O
full	O
you	O
don't	O
even	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
life	O
anymore	O
.	O

Struggling	O
to	O
roll	O
this	O
blunt	O

Hope	O
my	O
future	O
students	O
don't	O
put	O
too	O
much	O
effort	O
into	O
tracking	O
down	O
the	O
mile	O
-	O
wide	O
trail	O
of	O
swears	O
and	O
I've	O
left	O
across	O
the	O
internet	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

@reggiehayes1	O
is	O
at	O
it	O
again	O
with	O
more	O
Cheap	O
Shots	O
,	O
targeting	O
IU	O
alum	O
,	O
the	O
Ire	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
Bill	B-person
Belichick	I-person
and	O
this	O
:	O
http://t.co/O0F4rpvMqM	O

teapotniall	O
YOUR	O
WHOLE	O
LAYOUT	O
AND	O
ACCOUNT	O
IS	O
PERECT	O
:D	O
i	O
love	O
you	O
and	O
our	O
mutual	O
so	O
much	O
:)	O
we	O
should	O
talk	O
more	O
hehe	O
ily	O

RT	O
@G4Gitonga	O
:	O
#EPL	O
'	O
Big	O
'	O
Games	O
Chelsea	B-organization
Arsenal	B-organization
MUFC	B-organization
MCFC	B-organization
Arsenal	B-organization
MCFC	B-organization
LFC	B-organization
Tottenham	B-organization
Everton	B-organization
Arsenal	B-organization
LFC	B-organization
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/cmFT6lbzqK	O

"	O
The	O
only	O
real	O
alternative	O
to	O
feminism	O
is	O
masochism	O
"	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
Gloria	B-person
Steinem	I-person

@b0ujib00ty	O
they're	O
literally	O
stupid	O

@astu_xo	O
Catch	O
me	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
smarty	O
pants	O
immediatelyyyy	O

There	O
were	O
more	O
*	O
inhuman	O
*	O
heroes	O
(	O
robots	O
,	O
aliens	O
)	O
in	O
hero	O
video	O
montage	O
than	O
women	O
heroes	O
.	O
#Oscars	O

This	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
significant	O
and	O
high	O
impact	O
winter	O
storm	O
moving	O
through	O
tonight	O
/	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
don't	O
think	O
I	O
can	O
describe	O
it	O
another	O
way	O
.	O

Harini	O
en	O
wechat	O
semua	O
dengan	O
budak	O
baru	O
bangun	O
tidur	O
.	O
Apelah	O
nasib	O
semua	O
mamai	O
.	O
Macam	O
macam	O
typo	O
sakit	O
perut	O
aku	O
gelak	O
sorang2	O
.	O

I'm	O
not	O
even	O
going	O
to	O
address	O
what	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
attention	O
.	O

Buzz	O
for	O
Milwaukee	B-place
entertainment	O
choices	O
:	O
http://t.co/ASvWQPcFou	O
-	O
with	O
latest	O
mentions	O
by	O
@MKEArtsBoard	O
,	O
@MythicistMKE	O
,	O
@HandyNewsNotes	O

Tp	O
klo	O
tua	O
itu	O
bisa	O
masak	O
jg	O
gak	O
Jeng	O
?	O
@YuNnieQ	O
:	O
Lebih	O
tua	O
bukan	O
berarti	O
lebih	O
bener	O
x	O
"	O

@Beautebitch_	O
I	O
left	O
at	O
5	O
.	O
30	O
!	O
Lol	O

@Mr_Carterr	O
pleaseeeeeeeeeeeeeeee	O
follow	O
me	O
12	O

RT	O
@HeadlinesXx	O
:	O
#Np	O
Radioactive	B-product
Imagine	O
Dragons	O
/	O
Kendrick	B-person
Lamar	I-person

@sleeplessbooks	O
yeah	O
but	O
I'd	O
rather	O
just	O
work	O
on	O
paying	O
it	O
off	O
now	O
since	O
I	O
don't	O
need	O
the	O
extra	O
money	O
and	O
my	O
paycheck	O
does	O
cover	O
it	O
.	O

eu	O
fiz	O
uma	O
comida	O
que	O
ta	O
meio	O
perfeita	O

@mollsmaix	O
oh	O
moll	O
lmfao	O
noooo	O

RT	O
@jackieproblems	O
:	O
Sleeping	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
my	O
life	O
away	O
.	O
Bye	O
.	O
http://t.co/OaR84KnqdI	O

@meaaaagy	O
you're	O
probably	O
the	O
only	O
one	O
tweeting	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

Edible	B-organization
Feast	I-organization
picks	O
up	O
our	O
spring	O
issue	O
story	O
on	O
the	O
Rasberry	O
twins	O
and	O
their	O
twin	O
restaurants	O
in	O
Ketchum	B-place
and	O
Hailey	B-place
.	O
http://t.co/Sl73EaqasR	O

Nail	O
salon	O
tomorrow	O
,	O
much	O
needed	O
!	O

@GoodbyeKoch	O
The	O
Racist	O
hate	O
mongers	O
manipulated	O
by	O
the	O
Greedy	O
2	O
a	O
point	O
where	O
their	O
combined	O
Cesspool	O
of	O
H8	O
is	O
dangerous	O

In	O
fiction	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
a	O
lot	O
of	O
teens	O
who	O
get	O
really	O
horrendous	O
hangovers	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
they	O
consume	O
alcohol	O
,	O
which	O
doesn't	O
match	O
my	O
experience	O
.	O

Rowan	B-person
:	O
"	O
The	O
pilot	O
depicts	O
tense	O
adult	O
political	O
struggle	O
in	O
the	O
sky	O
and	O
attractive	O
teens	O
in	O
a	O
coming	O
-	O
of	O
-	O
age	O
drama	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
"	O
(	O
1	O
/	O
x	O
)	O
#The100	O

@daydreamjack	O
@edshewalk	O
@heartfeItstyles	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
other	O
people	O
and	O
then	O
i	O
said	O
harry	B-person
can	O
i	O
have	O
a	O
kissing	O
picture	O
and	O
he	O
looked	O
at	O

ever	O
get	O
them	O
days	O
where	O
you	O
just	O
don't	O
even	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
tweet	O

connor	O
love	O
me	O
please	O

Son	O
I	O
really	O
can't	O
have	O
a	O
conversation	O
and	O
not	O
get	O
yelled	O
at	O
.	O
.	O

MarkTwain	B-person
"	O
What	O
gets	O
us	O
into	O
trouble	O
is	O
not	O
what	O
we	O
don't	O
know	O
;	O
it's	O
what	O
we	O
know	O
for	O
sure	O
that	O
just	O
ain't	O
so	O
"	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
via	O
foxnewsLIES	O
#Inners	O

I	O
hate	O
overthinking	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

@officialR5	O
#FAMGetsLouder	B-organization
Can	O
I	O
get	O
a	O
"	O
Hell	O
Yeah	O
"	O
?	O
?	O

You	O
know	O
what	O
?	O
FUCK	O
DUKE	B-person

RT	O
@Kiss_My_Bumper	O
:	O
I've	O
made	O
so	O
many	O
sacrifices	O
to	O
get	O
where	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
turning	O
back	O
isn't	O
an	O
option	O
.	O

@EcchaMaslohi	O
hahahahahah	O
!	O
Yes	O
that's	O
true	O
.	O
.	O
Insya	O
'	O
allah	O
:)	O

Homemade	O
chocolate	O
Oreo	B-product
ice	O
cream	O
.	O
#happyhappyhappy	O
#100happydays	O
#day7	O
http://t.co/VSpaCqfp99	O

RT	O
@ERahmanPhoto	O
:	O
Signs	O
of	O
spring	O
!	O
#flowers	O
#trees	O
#nature	O
#photography	O
http://t.co/8nlryYEv03	O

On	O
#Raw	B-product
@TripleH	O
raised	O
the	O
stakes	O
for	O
@WrestleMania	O
higher	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
the	O
#YESMovement	B-other
came	O
to	O
a	O
screeching	O
halt	O
!	O
RESULTS	O
:	O
http://t.co/vd6AOBMNQV	O

@_daintyd0ll	O
yeah	O
I	O
see	O
what	O
you	O
mean	O
.	O
A	O
40yr	O
old	O
named	O
Archie	B-person
doesn't	O
have	O
good	O
connotations	O

Heading	O
down	O
to	O
Hull	B-place
Street	I-place
Library	I-place
#RVA	O
.	O
Tutoring	O
an	O
adult	O
going	O
back	O
to	O
school	O
.	O
#Dontquit	O

@SwingAwaySports	O
@Bharper3407	O
Dude	O
,	O
I'm	O
surprised	O
that	O
the	O
swing	O
away	O
is	O
still	O
in	O
tacked	O
!	O
Seriously	O
Jacked	O
!	O
http://t.co/fKv9d91kpL	O

@vxnssx_	O
ni	O
V	O
yg	O
I	O
Kenal	O
ke	O
?	O

@r50UL	O
I	O
just	O
can't	O
find	O
your	O
@	O
hahaha	O
,	O
ffs	O

In	O
four	O
to	O
eight	O
years	O
I'll	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
say	O
I	O
became	O
an	O
engineer	O
and	O
smoked	O
weed	O
anyone	O
can	O
be	O
successful	O

@rauhlallday	O
keep	O
going	O
:)	O
:)	O
it	O
will	O
happen	O
babe	O
!	O

Warning	O
:	O
may	O
cause	O
fights	O
to	O
break	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
Deep	B-product
Space	I-product
Station	O
K7	O
bar	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/nbov4fj651	O

@RickyPDillon	O
HI	O
RICKY	B-person
!	O
PLEASE	O
FOLLOW	O
ME	O
?	O
I	O
LOVE	O
YOU	O
SO	O
MUCH	O
YOURE	O
AMAZING	O
#WatchRickysNewVideo	O
x49	O

Ain't	O
been	O
out	O
all	O
spring	O
break	O
,	O
I'm	O
a	O
enjoy	O
myself	O
tonight	O

Ilgauskas	B-person
to	O
have	O
jersey	O
retired	O
by	O
Cavs	B-organization
-	O
The	O
seventh	O
player	O
in	O
team	O
history	O
to	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/hV4DzwbQVl	O
#BobbyBingoSmith	O
#NateThurmond	O

I'm	O
a	O
Pessimist	O
,	O
sue	O
me	O
.	O
damn	O
.	O

@Michael5SOS	O
WHATS	O
YOUR	O
FAVOURITE	O
SONG	O
FROM	O
FROZEN	B-product
?	O

RT	O
@Fifteentoone	O
:	O
Question	O
or	O
nominate	O
?	O
#LBCdebate	O

.	O
@gold248131	O
I	O
have	O
asked	O
you	O
several	O
questions	O
already	O
.	O
You	O
want	O
more	O
,	O
okay	O
I'll	O
play	O
this	O
game	O

@xoAshMarieMusic	O
haha	O
nice	O
half	O
way	O
ther	O
lolz	O

Birthday	O
in	O
May.	O
Just	O
wait	O
on	O
it	O
#GeminisWeAre	O
#May25th	O

Gaush	O
nunggu	O
agstus	O
:D	O
RT	O
@milatania1	O
:	O
@charlyantii_vht	O
blom	O
agustus	O
jg	O
merdeka	O
dolo	O
bahaha	O

You	O
guys	O
really	O
like	O
those	O
lebron	B-person
and	O
kd	O
elites	O
or	O
nah	O
?	O

@Oreoismydream	O
@Fyzixs	O
ewww	O
a	O
girl	O
sent	O
me	O
Kik	O
message	O
.	O
-	O
.	O

Mon	O
,	O
24	O
Mar	O
5	O
:	O
00pm	O
-	O
Farr	O
Point	O
wave	O
farm	O
public	O
consultation	O
events	O
:	O
Pelamis	B-organization
Wave	I-organization
Power	I-organization
are	O
holding	O
a	O
series	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/gd4tilLP4W	O

The	O
Friendly	O
Confines	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
Wrigley	B-place
Field	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/mSiOcjVy0k	O

@3sixty5days	O
serious	O
question	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
soil	O
yourself	O
interviewing	O
Chris	B-person
Evans	I-person
?	O
Because	O
,	O
daaaaayum	O
.	O
I	O
can't	O
.	O

@dantre23	O
I've	O
been	O
okay	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
you	O
?	O

RT	O
@LeahKitsune	O
:	O
@baconsplooge	O
awh	O
you're	O
hella	O
pretty	O
too	O

NEW	O
ALIEN	O
SIGNAL	O
FROM	O
HABITABLE	O
STAR	O
DISCOVERED	O
!	O
3	O
/	O
4	O
/	O
2014	O
SETI	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
DISCLOSURE	O
http://t.co/bfTkq3klsa	O

@NoorHG_	O
the	O
only	O
reason	O
that	O
I	O
keep	O
my	O
account	O
is	O
cuz	O
of	O
it's	O
necessity	O
nowadays	O
.	O
In	O
order	O
to	O
use	O
this	O
app	O
,	O
please	O
sign	O
in	O
with	O
your	O
FB	O

RT	O
@americanamma	O
:	O
Huge	O
sale	O
happening	O
at	O
http://t.co/K5RVHMgpXp	O
.	O
Check	O
it	O
out	O
!	O
@PAIGEVANZANT	O
@TeciaTorres	O
@karatehottiemma	O

RT	O
@Zel_PlayTooMuch	O
:	O
You	O
can't	O
not	O
be	O
a	O
fan	O
of	O
@RichHomieQuan	O

@TheSublime	O
same	O
.	O
They're	O
horrifying	O
honestly	O
.	O

MICHAEL	B-person
IM	O
SORRY	O
I	O
ATE	O
YOUR	O
COOKIES	O

Just	O
wanted	O
to	O
thank	O
u	O
@TYRAATKINS	O
for	O
everything	O
!	O
Love	O
being	O
"	O
a	O
whole	O
unit	O
"	O
with	O
u	O
!	O
#OUAT	B-product

THE	O
RRCG	B-organization
bus	O
that	O
overturned	O
at	O
the	O
South	B-place
Luzon	I-place
Expressway	O
.	O
(	O
Photo	O
courtesy	O
of	O
Krizzia	B-person
Perez	I-person
)	O
Read	O
more	O
:	O
http	O
:	O
http://t.co/y5evjNUYAc	O

Change	O
of	O
pace	O
/	O
location	O
-	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
beautiful	O
Balkan	B-place
voices	O
:	O
Esma	B-person
Redzepova	I-person
-	O
Gelem	O
,	O
gelem	O
http://t.co/39730xYfib	O

Two	O
kinds	O
of	O
#Oscars	B-other
on	O
my	O
timeline	O
today	O
.	O
Both	O
have	O
drama	O
,	O
both	O
have	O
a	O
judge	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
wish	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
never	O
happened	O

@Michael4SOS	O
mine	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
that	O
and	O
i	O
closed	O
itunes	B-product
and	O
then	O
opened	O
it	O
again	O
but	O
iam	O
not	O
sure	O
that	O
work	O
for	O
me	O

ANONG	O
TAWAG	O
SA	O
BASANG	O
ISDA	O
?	O
EDI	O
HITO	O
BAKIT	O
?	O
HITO	O
AKO	O
BASANG	O
BASA	O
SA	O
ULAN	O

RT	O
@JustTruth_90	O
:	O
@T_Larkington	O
shirts	O
tough	O
.	O
Im	O
a	O
def	O
ordering	O
something	O
else	O
in	O
a	O
couple	O
weeks	O

Me	O
doy	O
cuenta	O
si	O
RT	O
@denisseheredia_	O
:	O
Amo	O
el	O
pollo	O

@DrSLDR	O
yes	O
most	O
likely	O
.	O
If	O
worst	O
comes	O
to	O
worst	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
your	O
mother	O
!	O

FAG	O
!	O
Oh	O
wait	O
,	O
it	O
already	O
says	O
that	O
.	O
http://t.co/vW7UO09jO6	O

@ZionsAngel125	O
@MiaLis79	O
@willchamplin	O
Yes	O
he	O
is	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
is	O
good	O
,	O
means	O
his	O
music	O
carrer	O
is	O
going	O
on	O
:)	O

Finally	O
got	O
some	O
clarity	O
on	O
Ember	B-product
.	O
Object	O
.	O
extend	O
(	O
)	O
versus	O
App	O
.	O
Thing	O
.	O
reopenClass	O
(	O
)	O
-	O
-	O
http://t.co/tBRDuM3x5w	O

LOL	O
!	O
Mel	B-person
is	O
a	O
bit	O
selfish	O
about	O
her	O
kidneys	O
!	O
Ryder	B-person
better	O
watch	O
out	O
for	O
himself	O
!	O
#MelissaandJoey	O
http://t.co/ZhiaWC6OAn	O

RT	O
@DBKardashian	O
:	O
Why	O
do	O
women	O
get	O
tongue	O
Rings	O
if	O
it's	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
freak	O
?	O

@TehEmoPenguin	O
You	O
don't	O
have	O
an	O
Xbox	B-product
One	I-product
?	O
!	O
XD	O

@jennxpenny	O
@lordemusic	O
When	O
you're	O
in	O
the	O
Celebrity	B-organization
Club	O
everyone	O
will	O
look	O
up	O
to	O
you	O

The	O
New	O
York	O
Times	O
@nytimes	O
digs	O
deep	O
inside	O
the	O
new	O
#FarmBill	O
and	O
finds	O
emphasis	O
on	O
#healthy	O
foods	O
.	O
http://t.co/P6w3N1GCr8	O

@GearsAndCogs	O
Sighs	O
softly	O
,	O
"	O
Jakob	B-person
?	O
Remember	O
my	O
pillows	O
forts	O
I	O
always	O
used	O
to	O
make	O
?	O
"	O

Where	O
is	O
my	O
mom	O
with	O
my	O
Burger	B-organization
King	I-organization

@MrVananda	O
isidala	O
sam	O
sithengele	O
i	O
cheri	O
yakhe	O
i	O
restaurant	O
pha	O
e	O
town	O
,	O
kubi	O
.	O
Kumnyama	O
.	O

magi	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
kau	O
mmbuatku	O
begadang	O
u	O
.	O
u	O

michael	B-person
clifford	I-person
michael	B-person
clifford	I-person
michael	B-person
clifford	I-person
michael	B-person
clifford	I-person
michael	B-person
clifford	I-person

Alhamdulillah	O
seneng	O
liat	O
fotonya	O
:	O
)	O
semoga	O
kak	O
andah	O
sering2	O
pulang	O
nengokin	O
orangtuanya	O

Via	O
@TheNextWeb	O
Paper	O
by	O
FiftyThree	O
gets	O
a	O
redesign	O
with	O
new	O
controls	O
and	O
drawing	O
features	O
:	O
iPad	B-product
drawing	O
app	O
P	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/GP2TsEXYLA	O

This	O
just	O
in	O
!	O
#vinyl	O
#records	O
#soundtracks	O
#80s	O
#musicals	O
#opera	O
#classics	O
http://t.co/ZrZyHS6H0y	O

Move	O
to	O
sell	O
-	O
off	O
Tesco	B-organization
store	O
in	O
North	B-place
Lincolnshire	I-place
welcomed	O
-	O
Scunthorpe	B-organization
Telegraph	I-organization
http://t.co/X0Azhe0PFR	O
#Lincolnshire	O

@Lee_ShazzyD	O
heh	O
hyung	O
u	O
are	O
17	O
alr	O
go	O
audition	O
and	O
yolo	O
!	O
!	O
:D	O

Can	O
you	O
guys	O
go	O
and	O
follow	O
my	O
personal	O
@JoshUJWorld	O
I'll	O
follow	O
back	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
#ImTheRealJoshCuthbert	O

@AdelaineMorin	O
Please	O
accept	O
my	O
Snapchat	B-product
request	O
!	O
!	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
3	O

RT	O
@BYElaserland	O
:	O
@BeforeYouExit	O
but	O
Riley's	B-person
at	O
the	O
gym	O

@ctoombs	O
this	O
is	O
incredible	O
.	O
My	O
new	O
travel	O
list	O
.	O
Toombs	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
you	O
the	O
best	O
.	O

Sies	O
maan	O
:	O
/	O
"	O
@__Senz	O
:	O
@Taki_Sim	O
:	O
So	O
this	O
girls	O
hair	O
grew	O
mould	O
after	O
keeping	O
her	O
weave	O
in	O
for	O
6months	O
-	O
lawwwd	O
:	O
/	O
"	O
http://t.co/cjqi8p8w6o	O

ICYMI	O
:	O
Feral	O
two	O
-	O
piece	O
Royal	O
Blood	O
chat	O
to	O
Clash	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/bGo5LF2JyF	O

@TayBlack84	O
Man	O
!	O
One	O
day	O
,	O
Tay	O
!	O
One	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
French	O
toast	O
will	O
be	O
ours	O
!	O

do	O
you	O
ever	O
get	O
period	O
cramps	O
and	O
then	O
realise	O
you're	O
not	O
on	O
your	O
period	O
and	O
you're	O
just	O
like	O
wait	O
wtf	O

@1Obefiend	O
apologies	O
if	O
u	O
r	O
offended	O
;	O
)	O

RT	O
@BRADLEYSIPMSON	O
:	O
WHY	O
CANT	O
I	O
JUST	O
HAVE	O
5	O
/	O
5	O

RT	O
@J_Squit	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
ain't	O
win	O
an	O
Oscar	O
Leo	B-person
but	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/IDD20zPi37	O

RT	O
@roseGoldSOHO	O
:	O
I	O
dnt	O
like	O
nobody	O
right	O
now	O

@NateDogg_254	O
that's	O
love	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
I	O
got	O
you	O
bro	O

ECU	O
starters	O
:	O
Akeem	B-person
Richmond	I-person
,	O
Caleb	B-person
White	I-person
,	O
Antonio	B-person
Robinson	I-person
,	O
Paris	B-person
Roberts	I-person
-	I-person
Campbell	I-person
and	O
Michael	B-person
Zangari	I-person
.	O

follow	O
my	O
instagram	B-product
i'll	O
follow	O
back	O
http://t.co/5H8s9pjIrb	O

Not	O
watching	O
#bbcqt	O
.	O
Can't	O
.	O
Can't	O
.	O
No.	O

@lukmanthree	O
kalau	O
kerjaan	O
udah	O
selesai	O
mau	O
nih	O
hehe	O
.	O
Kalo	O
gw	O
jadi	O
,	O
nanti	O
ketemu	O
ya	O
~	O

That's	O
how	O
We	O
got	O
the	O
kkkteapublicans	O
http://t.co/hpLKU2E7oT	O

About	O
to	O
watch	O
this	O
DVD	O
to	O
get	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
mood	O
for	O
Friday	O
#franticfour	O
#quo	O
http://t.co/0mxyOo4b8y	O

@liamthenry	O
yep	O
,	O
that'll	O
work	O
as	O
well	O
!	O

@CharlotteBeerWk	O
Tickets	O
for	O
3	O
/	O
22	O
Public	O
Brew	O
Tour	O
only	O
$	O
55	O
with	O
coupon	O
code	O
1777VC10	O
please	O
RT	O

@InsignisMargo	O
Don't	O
you	O
dare	O
.	O
Return	O
to	O
S2	O
now	O
.	O
Or	O
I	O
will	O
spoiler	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
.	O

@TheMeganDuffy	O
Damn	O
that's	O
a	O
good	O
rule	O
to	O
live	O
by	O

@ManilaJLover	O
@JLo	O
omg	O
I've	O
been	O
looking	O
for	O
that	O
everywhere	O
!	O
!	O

RT	O
@thamiresgracio	O
:	O
Clara	B-person
,	O
Vanessa	B-person
e	O
Angela	B-person
na	O
final	O
.	O
Estou	O
cagando	O
levemente	O
.	O

RT	O
@scooterbraun	O
:	O
beautiful	O
sunday	B-other

Reminder	O
to	O
come	O
see	O
us	O
at	O
booth	O
8212	O
@expowest	O
this	O
weekend	O
!	O
#newavitae	O
#instantgo	O
#caffeinewater	O

Hidup	O
d	O
darat	O
dan	O
d	O
aer	O
RT	O
@theredranger48	O
:	O
Ekan	O
Paus	O
foto	O
bareng	O
Ikan	O
Paus	O
http://t.co/ha9sY54NOC	O

Head	O
,	O
sex	O
outside	O
or	O
in	O
a	O
car	O
doesn't	O
make	O
you	O
a	O
freak	O
in	O
my	O
eyes	O
.	O

I'm	O
tight	O
RT	O
@Kimberlychanel_	O
:	O
Lmfaooooo	O
how	O
Tiana	B-person
won	O

It's	O
that	O
time	O
LOL	O
-	O
http://t.co/6qhTUH7uQp	O
http://t.co/sADZs05dPW	O

RT	O
@Sophia2293	O
:	O
#YESPimpmySummerBall	O
Warwick	B-place
!	O
!	O
!	O

Ever	O
since	O
spring	O
started	O
,	O
I've	O
noticed	O
people	O
get	O
more	O
aggressive	O
.	O

BABY	O
YOU	O
COULD	O
DRIVE	O
MY	O
CAR	O

What	O
the	O
hell	O
was	O
yall	O
calling	O
Garfield	B-person
before	O
?	O

@haeriminan	O
@AdriandaRaka	O
@ceecilla	O
@ayya94	O
@cloudsyifa	O
@raeneuls	O
/	O
tertawa	O
jahat	O
/	O
wakakakakakakakakak	O

RT	O
@RestaurantMagUK	O
:	O
Our	O
final	O
award	O
for	O
Best	O
Group	O
Chef	O
(	O
Restaurants	O
)	O
goes	O
to	O
the	O
Hakkasan	B-organization
Group's	I-organization
Graham	B-person
Hornigold	I-person
#DevChefs	O

I	O
started	O
my	O
period	O
yesterday	O
.	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
our	O
vacation	O
.	O
sat	O
in	O
a	O
car	O
for	O
8	O
hours	O
.	O
goddammit	O
mother	O
nature	O

pq	O
todas	O
as	O
minas	O
de	O
rbd	O
tem	O
cara	O
de	O
atriz	O
porno	O

She	O
listed	O
damn	O
near	O
every	O
number	O

@marshasarung	O
@rel8rumi	O
@agtsparsella	O
udah	O
jadian	O
?	O
yey	O
finally	O
jadi	O
jugaaaa	O
!	O
peje	O
yayayaya	O
.	O

The	O
greatest	O
comment	O
I've	O
ever	O
gotten	O
:	O
http://t.co/VVhv1G3Q0s	O

I	O
think	O
I	O
broke	O
my	O
snapchat	O
this	O
morning	O
#1hour30mincommute	O
#traffic	O
#accidents	O
#bored	O

That	O
just	O
made	O
me	O
think	O
real	O
deep	O
!	O

No	O
#splody	O
cats	O
-	O
-	O
RT	O
@kgoradio	O
Early	O
warfare	O
manual	O
urges	O
military	O
commanders	O
to	O
strap	O
explosives	O
to	O
#cats	O
or	O
birds	O
.	O
http://t.co/h1ekeLGCpx	O

@iObey_donuts	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
idea	O
Omg	O
sorry	O

QC	O
OFFICER	O
(	O
QUALITY	O
CONTROL	O
OFFICER	O
)	O
-	O
INTER	O
ANEKA	O
LESTARI	O
KIMIA	O
,	O
PT	O
:	O
Rp3	O
,	O
000k	O
-	O
Rp4	O
,	O
000k	O
,	O
3	O
yr	O
of	O
exp	O
,	O
posted	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/lbvT3ynsWw	O

@UnrealVinny40	O
Hello	O
,	O
person	O
.	O
I	O
don't	O
know	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
guess	O
this	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
fight	O
back	O
?	O
Anyways	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
your	O
reason	O
and	O
I'll	O
give	O
you	O
mine	O
.	O

@spankyjackson1	O
give	O
me	O
Clowney	B-person
,	O
Teddy	B-person
,	O
or	O
Mack	B-person
/	O
Barr	B-person
,	O
or	O
Sammy	B-person
.	O

RT	O
@bellaberisic	O
:	O
Things	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
different	O

Got	O
a	O
$	O
50	O
free	O
bet	O
at	O
Bovada	B-organization
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
France	B-place
to	O
win	O
the	O
World	O
Cup	O
at	O
20	O
-	O
1	O
.	O
*	O
sparks	O
up	O
a	O
Gauloise	O
*	O
Money	O
is	O
meaningless	O
,	O
much	O
like	O
life	O
.	O

@elotente	O
what	O
about	O
the	O
smell	O
of	O
cum	O
in	O
your	O
beard	O
all	O
day	O
moron	O

I	O
gave	O
u	O
money	O
for	O
brazilian	O
hair	O
then	O
u	O
come	O
home	O
with	O
Patewo	O
?	O
Are	O
u	O
mad	O
!	O
!	O

Post	O
Traumatic	O
Sex	O
Dicksorder	O

@VTgal35	O
Thanks	O
for	O
FF	O
!	O
#BruinsFam	O

Hahaha	O
-	O
,	O
-	O
"	O
@adyzhamboel	O
:	O
*	O
bukacelana	O
*	O
RT	O
@neng_shana	O
:	O
Udh	O
ga	O
ada	O
yg	O
bangun	O
nih	O
?	O
"	O

I	O
just	O
got	O
a	O
phone	O
call	O
from	O
Texas	B-place
,	O
USA	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

oh	O
hey	O
remember	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
kinda	O
cute	O
http://t.co/tR4699vBl8	O

@sam_ashleyallen	O
@OhhhDilara	O
yew	O
protect	O
me	O
too	O
Sam	B-person
BAHAHAHAHA	O

RT	O
@Uber_BLR	O
:	O
@StylishByNature	O
quite	O
a	O
launch	O
!	O
Well	O
done	O
guys	O
!	O
#UberApproved	B-organization
#KazoWoman	B-product
http://t.co/TxHSGaAcQ3	O

Look	O
what	O
I	O
got	O
today	O
!	O
@seventeenmag	O
@annshoket	O
@msleamichele	O
#17Lea	O
beautiful	O
cover	O
!	O
http://t.co/sLQrXk3tP1	O

#VoteUKArianators	O
#KCA	O
RT	O
RT	O
RT	O
RT	O
xx	O

@LizzieLizzzz	O
Everybody	O
does	O
,	O
lol	O
.	O
She's	O
depressing	O
.	O

@kariner08303690	O
kdjhafskjadhsfkhadskfj	O
ai	O
mds	O
,	O
obregadaaaaaaaaa	O

#Repost	O
from	O
@Sgtb903	O
LET'S	O
GO	O
!	O
LOL	O
http://t.co/bhH4diWuQ3	O

How	O
to	O
limit	O
future	O
floods	O
in	O
Somerset	B-place
and	O
the	O
cost	O
.	O
Exclusive	O
report	O
coming	O
up	O
#bbcnews	O

RT	O
@LovingDYaria	O
:	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
so	O
much	O
that	O
I'm	O
starting	O
to	O
hate	O
you	O

Dude	O
,	O
I	O
like	O
you	O
,	O
like	O
,	O
like	O
-	O
like	O
you	O
.	O
Like	O
,	O
I	O
can't	O
explain	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
like	O
youu	O
.	O

@Doggonelover_	O
t	O
'	O
as	O
fait	O
qqchose	O
pr	O
qu	O
'	O
elle	O
le	O
prenne	O
ws	O

Enjoyed	O
a	O
spring	O
hike	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
Taking	O
a	O
moment	O
to	O
cloud	O
watch	O
and	O
witness	O
crepuscular	O
rays	O
beam	O
over	O
the	O
valley	O
.	O

@_britraines	O
ooooh	O
how	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
was	O
where	O
you're	O
at	O
right	O
now	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
Lol	O

@KevinAllenSmith	O
You	O
think	O
so	O
?	O
Maybe	O
for	O
non	O
and	O
new	O
craft	O
drinkers	O
.	O
Of	O
course	O
,	O
this	O
craft	O
bar	O
also	O
omitted	O
approximately	O
60	O
+	O
others	O
.	O

@StephaniMorales	O
Grit	O
is	O
a	O
differentiator	O
even	O
when	O
comparing	O
students	O
from	O
different	O
backgrounds	O
.	O

RT	O
@CitraHanna	O
:	O
@SalsaChacaB	O
lebih	O
enak	O
lagi	O
kalo	O
saling	O
ngerti	O
cap	O
.	O

all	O
duke	B-organization
fans	O
gunna	O
be	O
on	O
suicide	O
watch	O

Looking	O
for	O
a	O
DJ	O
to	O
partner	O
with	O
for	O
an	O
upcoming	O
event	O
.	O
No	O
equipment	O
necessary	O
.	O
Interested	O
?	O
Contact	O
Miami	O
@	O
yelp	O
.	O
com	O
.	O

If	O
you	O
have	O
my	O
number	O
in	O
your	O
phone	O
please	O
text	O
me	O
your	O
name	O
please	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
contacts	O
!	O
!	O
THANK	O
YOU	O

Treat	O
yourself	O
this	O
#weekend	O
with	O
a	O
seriously	O
sweet	O
#recipe	O
by	O
Heinz	B-person
Beck	I-person
@BeckHeinz	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/nZq4I62kmu	O
http://t.co/3YQN0Vhr4c	O

Why	O
can't	O
the	O
scene	O
wit	O
Jesse	B-person
driving	O
around	O
throwing	O
rackz	O
out	O
the	O
window	O
be	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
life	O

@CaroleRadziwill	O
is	O
my	O
#GirlCrush	O
.	O
#RHONY	B-person

@KingLouis2105	O
ha	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
don't	O
have	O
to	O
pay	O
you	O
out	O
.	O

RT	O
@kenmato	O
:	O
Anba	B-person
was	O
destined	O
to	O
say	O
that	O

It	O
endless	O
.	O
In	O
Guardian	O
@mollycrabapple	O
makes	O
the	O
startlingly	O
mendacious	O
claim	O
that	O
Guantanamo	B-place
captives	O
are	O
being	O
held	O
as	O
prisoners	O
of	O
war	O
.	O

Let's	O
go	O
Rainies	O
,	O
let's	O
go	O
!	O
