"	O
Gang	O
Ties	O
"	O
is	O
such	O
a	O
loose	O
term	O
.	O
Of	O
course	O
we	O
all	O
got	O
"	O
ties	O
"	O
.	O
Just	O
like	O
you	O
got	O
"	O
ties	O
"	O
wit	O
yo	O
muthafuckin	O
neighbor	O
in	O
the	O
suburbs	O
.	O

Best	O
time	O
of	O
year	O
.	O
Spring	O
Training	O
,	O
NHL	B-organization
Trade	O
Deadline	O
,	O
NHL	O
Playoffs	O
soon	O
,	O
NCAA	B-organization
BBall	O
,	O
March	O
Madness	O
,	O
Daylight	O
Savings	O

Ross	B-person
Cleaned	O
Diddy	B-person
Ass	O
In	O
3	O
Mins	O
For	O
A	O
Million	O
#Motivation	O

RT	O
@YouMadeThat	O
:	O
I	O
Know	O
When	O
People	O
Twatching	O
Me	O

@VTgal35	O
Thanks	O
for	O
FF	O
!	O
#BruinsFam	O

#NowPlaying	O
Kool	B-product
Thing	I-product
by	O
Sonic	B-product
Youth	I-product
on	O
@3RRRFM	O

@avery_veilleux	O
bahahahahaha	O
omg	O
did	O
you	O
did	O

@lucyhalelovex	O
YA	O
SHOULDA	O
PLANNED	O
A	O
TRIP	O
FOR	O
AT	O
LEAST	O
ONE	O
TIME	O
THIS	O
SUMMER	O
-	O
.	O
-	O

@CultOfBigE	O
p	O
.	O
s	O
.	O
If	O
she	O
don't	O
know	O
who	O
loves	O
orange	O
soda	O
,	O
she	O
too	O
young	O
for	O
you	O
bruh	O
;	O
p	O

@Last_King04	O
lmfao	O
,	O
dont	O
start	O
with	O
me	O

@TheXDExperience	O
I	O
wouldn't	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
though	O

@JustJoshinYu	O
Solar	O
power	O
nut	O
?	O
Check	O
out	O
:	O
@SolarReserve	O

@dancedance013	O
omg	O
thank	O
you	O
i	O
am	O
so	O
bad	O
at	O
this	O

Congratulations	O
to	O
@SineadCostelloe	O
for	O
being	O
picked	O
to	O
perform	O
at	O
@TriForceEvents	O
@MonologueSlamUK	O
at	O
@stratfordeast	O
April	O
14	O
#Talent	O

Finally	O
got	O
my	O
shirt	O
from	O
Mr.	O
@loyaltyxvalues	O
@lvfreshkid	O
thank	O
you	O
bro	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
rocked	O
at	O
#SXSW	O
http://t.co/BlbVb6hf8i	O

@magicarpetzarry	O
@manhattanzayn	O
its	O
been	O
a	O
while	O
since	O
i	O
saw	O
thee	O
words	O
on	O
my	O
tl	O

@Platform_Zero	O
Pleased	O
it	O
wasn't	O
leaking	O
gore	O
everywhere	O
!	O

RT	O
@Creoleian	O
:	O
@Brooke2Fetch	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
33333	O
damn	O
beautiful	O

AC's	B-place
Revel	B-organization
Casino	I-organization
:	O
The	O
$	O
300M	O
pension	O
gamble	O
http://t.co/MC7aPCvxe7	O
via	O
@AsburyParkPress	O

While	O
u	O
stalking	O
my	O
IG	O
don't	O
make	O
a	O
mistake	O
and	O
like	O
my	O
pic	O
and	O
delete	O
the	O
like	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
my	O
phone	B-product
tells	O
me	O
yo	O
ass	O
been	O
here	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
smh	O
dumb	O
ass	O

RT	O
@BouldaCrest_P	O
:	O
A	O
real	O
man	O
bring	O
his	O
funds	O
to	O
the	O
table	O

@iSandile	O
what	O
do	O
u	O
mean	O
by	O
read	O
?	O

@klace32	O
Please	O
try	O
uninstalling	O
the	O
app	O
from	O
apple	B-product
TV	I-product
and	O
reinstalling	O
it	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
laptop	O
a	O
PC	O
or	O
Mac	B-product
?	O
^	O
RA	O

this	O
made	O
my	O
day	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
3333	O
http://t.co/HsDlys8cgy	O

daqui	O
a	O
pouco	O
o	O
justin	O
tatua	O
na	O
testa	O
"	O
download	O
shots	O
"	O

Interesting	O
Sunday	O
reading	O
about	O
the	O
future	O
of	O
brain	O
implants	O
in	O
the	O
WSJ	O
.	O
http://t.co/AjblMTqWZJ	O

update	O
:	O
i	O
think	O
i	O
broke	O
my	O
shoulder	O
bc	O
i	O
was	O
making	O
a	O
vine	O
and	O
i	O
just	O

@queenchesters	O
tommy	B-person
merlyn	I-person
is	O
dead	O

@Shehroz_Usman	O
it	O
really	O
screwed	O
me	O
up	O
?	O
Masla	O
kia	O
hua	O
?	O

.	O
@A_M_Perez	O
@Ian2813	O
I'll	O
introduce	O
you	O
to	O
some	O
like	O
-	O
minded	O
friends	O
.	O
Two	O
more	O
you	O
should	O
follow	O
:	O
@2ASTRONG	O
and	O
@MarkG0077	O
#2aStrong	O

Jaysus	B-person
,	O
the	O
Queen	O
will	O
have	O
a	O
pain	O
in	O
her	O
arse	O
listening	O
to	O
Louis	B-person
Walsh	I-person
in	O
the	O
palace	O
.	O
#justsaying	O

IDK	O
HOW	O
IM	O
AT	O
A	O
BAR	O
LOL	O

RT	O
@LatestDigitals	O
:	O
#Robot	O
cloud	O
-	O
based	O
"	O
brain	O
"	O
to	O
be	O
tested	O
!	O
@TUe_news	O
@RoboEarthorg	O
http://t.co/bkl3j1oMXy	O
http://t.co/Y4ldWPPr0A	O

T	B-product
R	I-product
E	I-product
E	I-product
L	I-product
I	I-product
F	I-product
E	I-product
by	O
Timothy	B-person
Poulton	I-person
http://t.co/cs629gvNN4	O

Weh	O
aba	O
*	O
smh	O
*	O
"	O
@JazzMadoda	O
:	O
Yeah	O
#BafanaBafana	O
yenza	O
iifratsi	O
vele	O
"	O
@Xhosa_Queen	O
:	O
Leme	O
watch	O
khumbulekhaya	O
!	O
"	O
"	O

RT	O
@TheAngryElk	O
:	O
I	O
don't	O
understand	O
why	O
people	O
are	O
in	O
a	O
rush	O
to	O
get	O
married	O
/	O
have	O
kids	O
/	O
graduate	O
college	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
WANT	O
more	O
responsibility	O
?	O

CAN	O
WE	O
SEE	O
ARMIN	B-person
THO	O
I	O
WANT	O
SOME	O
TRANCE	O
.	O
.	O
A	B-product
.	I-product
S	I-product
.	I-product
O	I-product
.	I-product
T	I-product

Coffee	O
with	O
honey	O
is	O
so	O
delicious	O

@mejeffb	O
Ha	O
!	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
imagine	O
what	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
his	O
mind	O
.	O
Poor	O
guy	O
.	O

@HollyIsely	O
Both	O
good	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
COAS	O
is	O
better	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
awesome	O
.	O

@FathanAlFitris	O
Coba	O
refresh	O
atau	O
CTRL	O
+	O
F5	O
Semoga	O
dapat	O
membantu	O
.	O
Thanks	O

Me	O
Sef	O
Go	O
F	O
*	O
ck	O
RT	O
@Abnormal_pikin	O
:	O
What's	O
the	O
meaning	O
of	O
"	O
EMINADO	O
?	O
"	O
#FrankEdwardsAway_	O

@DejongeB	O
@ruben_vanlent	O
Aan	O
die	O
vrienden	O
/	O
omstandigheden	O
kan	O
je	O
zelf	O
iets	O
doen	O
,	O
maar	O
niet	O
zo	O
veel	O
als	O
men	O
ons	O
wil	O
doen	O
geloven	O
.	O

MICHAEL	B-person
IM	O
SORRY	O
I	O
ATE	O
YOUR	O
COOKIES	O

#shufflezebra	O
@	O
#Smirnoff	O
#PartyAnimals	O
@fwdmusiq	O
#privateparty	O
#Awesome	O
#lights	O
#music	O
#like	O
http://t.co/HcBUsiqTXb	O

12jam	O
mnju	O
luwu	O
utara	O
dri	O
mkassar	O
.	O
.	O
tpi	O
prjlnanku	O
blm	O
brakhir	O
dstu	O
.	O
.	O

FACT	O
OF	O
THE	O
DAY	O
:	O
EVERY	O
female	O
is	O
"	O
THAT	O
TYPE	O
OF	O
FEMALE	O
"	O

@TairuPANdA	O
The	O
autocoruise	O
;	O
I'll	O
try	O
to	O
dive	O
into	O
the	O
pool	O
but	O
I	O
might	O
end	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
giant	O
jello	O

RT	O
@RyanUptonMusic	O
:	O
V	B-other
Festival	I-other
line	O
up	O
is	O
so	O
sickkk	O
!	O

@panzerskank	O
@Kaubocks	O
Panzer	O
should	O
never	O
watch	O
Arrested	O
Development	O
.	O

@moorehn	O
\	O
\	O
\	O
o	O
/	O
/	O
/	O
There	O
you	O
go	O
!	O
:)	O
Congrats	O
!	O
:)	O
Desormais	O
,	O
on	O
peut	O
se	O
parler	O
en	O
Francais	O
!	O

What	O
towns	O
are	O
nice	O
near	O
Harry	B-person
Potter	I-person
world	O
?	O

RT	O
@NickHima	O
:	O
Tu	O
orang	O
mandinya	O
lama	O
banget	O
,	O
bisa	O
telat	O
aku	O
!	O
Damn	O
!	O

Everything	O
is	O
pink	O
in	O
Venus	B-product
.	O
.	O
.	O
Listen	O
to	O
my	O
song	O
"	O
Venus	B-product
"	O
off	O
my	O
EP	O
Unidentified	B-product
!	O
http://t.co/WvVeuwJG4H	O

@MdShahzad	O
so	O
now	O
its	O
Merc	O
then	O
1s	O
after	O
is	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
grid	O
,	O
Starting	O
with	O
barfeela	O
insaan	O
.	O

@CraftCute	O
i	O
rlly	O
hate	O
cowboyspace	O
,	O
sry	O
for	O
scolding	O
someone	O
in	O
front	O
u	O
babe	O
:	O
(	O
but	O
i	O
really	O
hate	O
him	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

@fadedbIuejeans	O
u	O
have	O
mine	O
rite	O
or	O
no	O

Onehunga	B-organization
Sports	I-organization
open	O
the	O
scoring	O
against	O
Glenfield	B-organization
Rovers	I-organization
#ACFCyouth	O

@AdamCimorelli	O
ooh	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
whoo	O
knew	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
O	O
&	O
gt	O
;	O
O	O

I	O
been	O
in	O
tub	O
so	O
many	O
times	O

Slide	O
my	O
panties	O
to	O
the	O
side	O
and	O
eat	O
me	O
like	O
you're	O
dying	O
of	O
starvation	O
.	O
Then	O
I'll	O
let	O
you	O
quench	O
my	O
thirst	O
.	O

@AMReese	O
Definitely	O
not	O
being	O
a	O
completionist	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
do	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
just	O
said	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
side	O
quests	O
.	O
lol	O

according	O
to	O
an	O
original	O
memorandum	O
,	O
the	O
International	B-place
Space	I-place
Station	I-place
#ISS	I-place
was	O
intended	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
laboratory	O
,	O
#observatory	O
+	O
factory	O
in	O
#space	O
.	O

RT	O
@PurplWorm	O
:	O
[	O
WoTC	O
:	O
D	B-product
&	I-product
amp	I-product
;	I-product
D	I-product
]	O
Sinister	O
Citizens	O
of	O
Kormul	O
http://t.co/U0reMh37w8	O

RT	O
@cbregreen	O
:	O
Easy	O
as	O
1	O
-	O
2	O
-	O
3	O
:	O
3	O
step	O
#sustainability	O
ACTION	O
plan	O
for	O
business	O
leaders	O
http://t.co/H9AK60U4X6	O

Speculations	O
in	O
France	B-place
stated	O
#Arsenal	B-organization
could	O
sign	O
Marseille	O
GK	O
,	O
Steve	B-person
Mandanda	B-person
as	O
Fabianski's	B-person
replacement	O
in	O
the	O
summer	O
(	O
TalkSport	B-organization
)	O
.	O

How	O
do	O
I	O
go	O
on	O
private	O
help	O

@KissedByHemmo	O
hell	O
fucking	O
yeah	O
:)	O

@SkyHelpTeam	O
Former	O
O2	O
customer	O
.	O
I've	O
2	O
emails	O
.	O
One	O
saying	O
you're	O
sorry	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
go	O
and	O
another	O
welcoming	O
me	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
just	O
horrible	O
.	O

@Emcat93	O
Doesn't	O
feel	O
like	O
my	O
week	O
in	O
London	B-place
was	O
a	O
full	O
week	O
.	O
And	O
no	O
on	O
the	O
camera	O
.	O
It's	O
probably	O
in	O
my	O
big	O
bag	O
.	O

RT	O
@KingSTRT	O
:	O
@BenTheTrout	O
STOP	O
FUCKING	O
HITTING	O
CLIPS	O
ON	O
ME	O

Share	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
loving	O
Trunx	B-product
!	O
Trunx	B-product
:	O
Your	O
All	O
in	O
One	O
Photo	O
Solution	O
http://t.co/u9r4QcE7Jd	O

@andinaaliffiam	O
@keyzanyzky19	O
lu	O
kapan	O
ada	O
duitnya	O
ya	O
?	O
-	O
_	O
-	O

Twitter	B-organization
mentions	O
for	O
London	B-place
Bridge	I-place
:	O
http://t.co/uftFK6dMcS	O
-	O
RT	O
@jaypinxieMUA	O
URGENT	O
CALL	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
ex	O
students	O
free	O
tomorrow	O
?	O
my	O
amaz	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

I	O
AM	O
MEXICAN	B-other
WHY	O
DO	O
I	O
LOOK	O
ASIAN	B-other
FML	O
http://t.co/7BVHdT2YRh	O

@YouCantFindMe19	O
Alex	B-person
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
We	O
can't	O
be	O
friends	O
.	O
Or	O
even	O
acquaintances	O
tbh	O

@gdsteam	O
Hi	O
Are	O
the	O
cards	O
featured	O
in	O
your	O
user	O
research	O
video	O
avaiable	O
online	O
?	O
They	O
look	O
really	O
useful	O
.	O

I	O
see	O
why	O
y	O
'	O
all	O
are	O
upset	O
.	O
Dah	O
well	O
!	O

The	B-product
Bryce	I-product
Cotton	I-product
show	I-product

Watch	O
Bangerz	B-product
Tour	I-product
VEVO	I-product
Exposed	I-product
http://t.co/nutwjTeynK	O

Ryan's	B-person
tweet	O
has	O
me	O
crying	O

RT	O
@worldwatchman	O
:	O
S0	O
News	O
March	O
27	O
,	O
2014	O
:	O
Major	O
News	O
,	O
U	O
-	O
Yen	O
Update	O
,	O
Spaceweather	O
-	O
YouTube	O
http://t.co/M5lHN9DwJ7	O

Wonderful	O
to	O
meet	O
with	O
our	O
Malaysian	O
Alumni	O
Chapter	O
at	O
USQ	B-other
Graduation	I-other
ceremony	I-other
in	O
KL	B-place
http://t.co/0amyMImJGR	O

@itsallstyletome	O
@Academy_NET	O
It	O
was	O
great	O
meeting	O
you	O
!	O
Hope	O
you	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
time	O
:)	O

Nice	O
to	O
meet	O
you	O
!	O
!	O
RT	O
@Lomara	O
:	O
Oh	O
hey	O
,	O
the	O
@NeptuneRising	O
ladies	O
are	O
right	O
behind	O
us	O
!	O

Do	O
you	O
know	O
?	O
Citigroup's	B-organization
Mexico	O
Unit	O
Hit	O
by	O
Subpoenas	O
http://t.co/PRX5eomgWT	O

This	O
City	O
side	O
are	O
a	O
class	O
act	O
.	O
Totally	O
dominating	O
Arsenal	B-organization
.	O
#ARSvMCI	O

happy	O
happy	O
birthday	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
ultimate	O
favorites	O
@trincaaa	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
love	O
you	O
forever	O
!	O
hope	O
you	O
liked	O
the	O
surprise	O
hehehe	O

@Eubankwarrior	O
great	O
meeting	O
u	O
this	O
morn	O
Chris	B-person
.	O
Really	O
enjoyed	O
our	O
chat	O
http://t.co/v9IIv4jaoE	O

@kelleysohara	O
hakuna	O
matata	O
,	O
the	O
problem	O
free	O
floss	O
ya	O
teeth	O

That	O
class	O
sessions	O
as	O
amazing	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
Passed	O
with	O
flying	O
colors	O
even	O
though	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
rough	O
at	O
first	O
.	O

@JamesPoole_	O
n	O
'	O
aww	O
you	O
should	O
know	O
you	O
ain't	O
gonna	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
any	O
of	O
us	O
lot	O
X	O

wHAT	O
THE	O
FUCK	O
PREV	O
RT	O
I	O
ALMOST	O
PUKED	O

@woodgreg	O
ohh	O
ouch	O
!	O
Yeah	O
was	O
worried	O
about	O
falling	O
off	O
in	O
some	O
areas	O

#NewMusic	O
Pick	O
up	O
Gospel	O
artist	O
@gscottco	O
NEW	O
single	O
"	O
Any	B-product
Day	I-product
Now	I-product
"	O
on	O
iTunes	O
TODAY	O
at	O
https://t.co/kBO2eEozI5	O
#GoodMusic	O

@Fizahat__	O
Tough	O
tha	O
jiski	O
wajah	O
se	O
jo	O
aata	O
tha	O
woh	O
bhi	O
galat	O
kardia	O
:P	O
Chalo	O
good	O
for	O
you	O
:)	O

Looking	O
for	O
a	O
Creative	O
Recruiter	O
,	O
Marketing	O
at	O
Google	B-organization
(	O
Mountain	B-place
View	I-place
,	I-place
CA	I-place
)	O
http://t.co/URA61rPaMQ	O
#jobs	O

Dun	B-person
had	O
alot	O
of	O
setbacks	O
snd	O
i	O
came	O
back	O
from	O
em	O
all	O
.	O
This	O
one	O
ain't	O
no	O
different	O
.	O

Everyone	O
give	O
@purdykyla99	O
a	O
follow	O
!	O
She's	O
new	O
and	O
needs	O
some	O
love	O
!	O

Pemanasan	O
dulu	O
sebelum	O
tampil	O
.	O
Happy	O
AE	O
!	O
#AllEnglandSSP	O
http://t.co/3TtEhW5ZoM	O

@cavaughn	O
from	O
an	O
article	O
posted	O
on	O
HuffPo	B-organization

The	O
girl	O
died	O
two	O
days	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
the	O
respect	O
for	O
her	O
family	O
?	O

I'm	O
talking	O
to	O
this	O
guy	O
from	O
Germany	B-place
who's	O
very	O
very	O
literate	O

@CarmexPh	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
tube	O
from	O
Suesh	O
!	O
:)	O
thank	O
you	O
so	O
much	O
!	O

Understanding	O
Exposure	O
Compensation	O
http://t.co/xMgv9ze0tr	O
Online	O
#Photography	O
Classes	O

nao	O
tente	O
roubar	O
o	O
que	O
eh	O
meu	O

rt	O
it	O
your	O
a	O
larry	B-person
shipper	I-person
fav	O
if	O
your	O
not	O

This	O
week's	O
Communitech	B-organization
Grow	O
Factor	O
#LinksWeLove	O
blog	O
is	O
out	O
!	O
#TGIF	O
http://t.co/z66ZR5XECp	O

Beverly	B-person
McAllister	I-person
Parker	I-person
is	O
remembered	O
as	O
a	O
faithful	O
friend	O
to	O
SNU	B-organization
.	O
http://t.co/Qac1umVYK0	O

"	O
It	O
touches	O
the	O
spirit	O
of	O
those	O
who	O
hear	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
and	O
they	O
are	O
changed	O
!	O
"	O

S	O
/	O
o	O
to	O
the	O
main	O
.	O
Always	O
been	O
there	O
since	O
day	O
one	O
@TheTorilynn	O

WUT	O
-	O
&	O
gt	O
;	O
Social	O
media	O
wedding	O
concierge	O
will	O
live	O
-	O
tweet	O
your	O
big	O
day	O
for	O
$	O
3	O
,	O
000	O
-	O
Your	O
Community	O
http://t.co/H6jHZesN54	O

I	O
FEEL	O
LIKE	O
SOMETHING'S	O
CRAWLING	O
UP	O
MY	O
NECK	O

RT	O
@drangiec	O
:	O
Vote	O
YES	O
for	O
PHSD's	B-organization
safety	O
and	O
FLiP	O
initiative	O
on	O
April	O
8th	O
!	O
http://t.co/DzZvLRb0h7	O

Ladies	O
seating	O
only	O
behind	O
Bishop's	B-person
net	O
.	O
http://t.co/VSPEZqfUcy	O

RT	O
@RnR_only	O
:	O
Bryan	B-person
Adams	I-person
-	O
Run	B-product
To	I-product
You	I-product
:	O
http://t.co/7FlbGaJtKo	O
via	O
@YouTube	O

ohp	O
wait	O
now	O
I'm	O
sad	O

If	O
Qatar	B-place
doesn't	O
clean	O
up	O
its	O
act	O
on	O
workers	O
'	O
conditions	O
,	O
it	O
shouldn't	O
host	O
the	O
2022	O
World	O
Cup	O
,	O
says	O
@ChrisWMP	O
http://t.co/IgdnXKFdsP	O

@srkvishu	O
@iburhan26	O
@srksknight	O
waah	O
!	O
kya	O
bola	O
yaar	O
.	O
.	O

@ROxanne_Shaunte	O
what	O
if	O
i	O
dont	O
wanna	O
leave	O
?	O

@danielgarofali	O
id	O
buy	O
your	O
sweatshirt	O
but	O
you	O
only	O
have	O
a	O
size	O
large	O
and	O
xlarge	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
I	O
ain't	O
no	O
@JigglyCaliente	O
#rupaulsdragrace	O

Ribs	O
for	O
my	O
lil	O
brother	O

RT	O
@flowerc5683	O
:	O
Don't	O
promise	O
when	O
you're	O
happy	O
,	O
don't	O
reply	O
when	O
you're	O
mad	O
,	O
and	O
don't	O
decide	O
wen	O
you're	O
sad	O
.	O

RT	O
@irasyaxo	O
:	O
@hariszack	O
hahahaha	O
lucky	O
u	O
got	O
the	O
correct	O
person	O

Deasia	B-person
&	O
amp	O
;	O
Mamah	B-person
Missing	O
All	O
The	O
Parties	O
.	O
Lsh	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
Nana	B-person
Missing	O
The	O
Fun	O
.	O

We	O
are	O
never	O
beaten	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
never	O
give	O
up	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
Unless	O
we	O
choose	O
so	O
.	O
#believe	O
http://t.co/Ams9YJsyWV	O

RT	O
@UkhtiMar_	O
:	O
"	O
Kadang	O
kala	O
perasaan	O
itu	O
mudah	O
berubah	O
dalam	O
sekelip	O
mata	O
.	O
Mungkin	O
kerana	O
Allah	O
telah	O
menggerakkan	O
hatinya	O
.	O
"	O
Hm	O

ANONG	O
TAWAG	O
SA	O
BASANG	O
ISDA	O
?	O
EDI	O
HITO	O
BAKIT	O
?	O
HITO	O
AKO	O
BASANG	O
BASA	O
SA	O
ULAN	O

RT	O
@roamin	O
:	O
Wednesday	O
Flipped	O
http://t.co/N3mpzlkbZZ	O

She	O
said	O
"	O
baby	O
I	O
got	O
one	O
rule	O
:	O
I'm	O
the	O
king	O
and	O
you	O
my	O
queen	O
"	O
#teamlesbian	O

"	O
I	O
work	O
too	O
hard	O
.	O
"	O
#forewordstory	O
http://t.co/9RB860gzjW	O

General	B-organization
Electric	I-organization
:	O
The	O
Risk	O
Is	O
Not	O
Worth	O
The	O
Reward	O
http://t.co/7OjfdJxEoA	O
#econ	O
#mises	O
#keynes	B-person

Helpful	O
@ImpactSP2	O
analysis	O
of	O
ntl	O
#ece	O
sector	O
.	O
http://t.co/Zx1zXMKz1U	O
.	O
Tip	O
of	O
the	O
hat	O
@ClyonsSFC	O

Finally	O
getting	O
around	O
to	O
watching	O
The	B-product
#Sopranos	I-product
.	O
I	O
cant	O
believe	O
it	O
took	O
me	O
this	O
long	O

let's	O
play	O
a	O
game	O
called	O
spot	O
the	O
couple	O
hint	O
:	O
harry	B-person
and	O
louis	B-person
http://t.co/l4KVyFdLn4	O

Eh	O
iya	O
ini	O
tanggal	O
9	O
bulan	O
Maret	O
2014	O
kan	O
?	O
Hari	O
ini	O
Happy	O
Failednya	O
Reza	O
sama	O
Thella	O
yah	O
:)	O
@mrezanugrah	O
@ratusweethella	O

The	O
only	O
fat	O
things	O
that	O
Liam	B-person
has	O
is	O
his	O
dick	O
,	O
wallet	O
and	O
heart	O
bye	O

After	O
updated	O
twice	O
what	O
the	O
heck	O
bye	O
homework	O

These	O
are	O
just	O
too	O
many	O
good	O
terrifying	O
two	O
sentence	O
horror	O
stories	O
here	O
:	O
http://t.co/UutRhk0vDx	O

Go	O
home	O
dude	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
cookies	O
for	O
you	O

Use	O
the	O
hashtag	O
#AtMiddleton	B-product
before	O
our	O
April	O
1st	O
Bluray	O
/	O
DVD	O
release	O
date	O
and	O
you	O
could	O
win	O
an	O
At	O
Middleton	O
t	O
-	O
shirt	O
used	O
in	O
the	O
movie	O
.	O

#ASADistrictDay	O
goal	O
was	O
$	O
2700	O
for	O
District	O
5	O
.	O
Today	O
this	O
amazing	O
district	O
raised	O
$	O
6518	O
.	O
13	O
for	O
the	O
@ASAFoundation	O
-	O
amazing	O
!	O
!	O

Looking	O
forward	O
to	O
spring	O
break	O
its	O
much	O
needed	O
!	O
!	O
!	O

RT	O
@Mal__Black	O
:	O
North	B-place
Philly	I-place
is	O
my	O
motherland	O

@Dess_NotRight	O
I	O
did	O
you	O
never	O
replied	O
.	O

@SmoshArianaPie	O
no	O
u	O
dont	O
u	O
love	O
ppl	O
i	O
means	O
u	O
love	O
eating	O
ppl	O
oops	O

RT	O
@_NintendoGod	O
:	O
@BigGucciMaster	O
smfh	O
they	O
be	O
running	O
out	O

Horrible	O
Histories	O
:	O
the	O
300	O
Spartans	O
;	O
Battle	O
of	O
Thermopylae	B-place
http://t.co/fgjwsvFU8O	O

RT	O
@sxsw	O
:	O
Kick	O
back	O
at	O
the	O
Dailymotion	B-organization
Happy	O
Hour	O
,	O
5	O
-	O
7pm	O
at	O
The	O
Hideout	O
.	O
#SXSWFilm	O
http://t.co/O2l1VIY4gH	O

A	O
good	O
way	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
mess	O
in	O
#Crimea	B-place
by	O
@fareedzakaria	O
:	O
http://t.co/nTfE97tq47	O

I	O
HOPE	O
EVERYONE	O
HAVE	O
FUN	O
WHO	O
ARE	O
GOING	O
TO	O
THE	O
GIG	O
TONIGHTTTT	O

Oomf	O
steals	O
so	O
many	O
of	O
my	O
tweets	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

http://t.co/HaLs0ouIaQ	O
PLEASE	O
LOOK	O
AT	O
THE	O
POEM	O

I	O
liked	O
a	O
@YouTube	O
video	O
http://t.co/w36fQNmfEx	O
Elgato	B-product
Game	O
Capture	O
HD	O
Giveaway	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
[	O
STILL	O
UP	O
!	O
]	O

@freedika	O
@ParanoyerTweets	O
komisch	O
.	O
fand	O
den	O
sehr	O
gut	O
.	O
sogar	O
als	O
zombie	O
-	O
purist	O
.	O
http://t.co/ZxkdtB4PBx	O

Stupa	O
udah	O
jd	O
blom	O
Ian	O
?	O
RT	O
@Septiyans	O
:	O
Selamat	O
malam	O
buat	O
kamu	O
yg	O
selalu	O
bisa	O
membuat	O
lengkung	O
senyum	O
terus	O
terpancar	O
dari	O
dalam	O
sanubari	O
:)	O

@cliffordgasm	O
@sleepyheadlarry	O
AWK	O
THANKYOU	O
I	O
LOVE	O
YOUUU	O

Full	O
album	O
stream	O
:	O
The	B-product
Attendants	I-product
(	O
French	O
punk	O
)	O
-	O
"	O
Metropol	B-product
Agencies	I-product
"	O
http://t.co/BMJPwkUFJL	O

wtf	O
my	O
hair	O
is	O
still	O
wet	O
from	O
last	O
night	O

With	O
the	O
doctor	O
at	O
71Gramercy	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
Mercator	O
model	O
Mark	B-person
Agas	I-person
:-)	O
@katdecastro	O
http://t.co/DKa2UUPOV7	O

@PaulLemmen	O
@LibraryGryffon	O
@PalatinePundit	O
@newagerain	O
he's	O
never	O
addressed	O
those	O
damning	O
headers	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
can't	O
.	O

Pumped	O
for	O
browner	B-person
.	O
Chad	B-person
and	O
I	O
agree	O
on	O
it	O
.	O

#BuffaloWildWings	B-place
#Sippy	O
#InstaFood	O
#FoodPorn	O
#KansasJayhawks	O
#Wavy	O
#Hungry	O
#Instagram	O
#HashTagKing	O
http://t.co/8JCaKcBTjs	O

RT	O
@DucoteElaine	O
:	O
"	O
@TwonTrxllo	O
:	O
Quote	O
this	O
with	O
a	O
pretty	O
ass	O
selfie	O
of	O
you	O
"	O
http://t.co/wilbc3PXYK	O

@VansCffTheWall	O
cAN	O
I	O
HELP	O
ME	O
THE	O
PAPI	O
MAMI	O

I	O
know	O
nae	B-person
neezy	I-person
better	O
get	O
on	O
my	O
Twitter	B-organization
!	O
#jadeTweet	O

@DurhamPoliceK9	O
aw	O
sad	O
but	O
what	O
a	O
great	O
long	O
life	O
he	O
had	O
#rip	O

Finally	O
DelPo	B-person
makes	O
a	O
sensible	O
decision	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

Lets	O
Trend	O
It	O
&	O
gt	O
;	O
@infibeam	O
#S5OnInfibeam	O
#S5OnInfibeam	O
#S5OnInfibeam	O
#S5OnInfibeam	O
#S5OnInfibeam	O
#S5OnInfibeam	O
#S5OnInfibeam	O
:	O
)	O
:	O
)	O
:	O
)	O
:)	O

@Meetasengupta	O
festivals	O
?	O
The	O
new	O
year	O
is	O
soon	O
for	O
most	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
Exams	O
.	O
I	O
see	O
anguished	O
exam	O
tweets	O
on	O
my	O
TL	O
:)	O
@IndianThisWeek	O

@Blitzkriegg_	O
@Shohzad	O
not	O
even	O
your	O
house	O
number	O
?	O

Indra	O
bapok	O
?	O
Omaiigod	O
!	O
HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA	O
!	O

vou	O
mudar	O
meu	O
design	O
pelo	O
iphone	O
mesmo	O

"	O
@hookazayn	O
:	O
FATIMA	B-person
IM	O
AT	O
SCHOOL	O
SERIOUSLY	O
"	O
IM	O
SORRY	O

Being	O
to	O
friendly	O
with	O
everything	O
#fake	O

RT	O
@PSHEsolutions	O
:	O
Excellent	O
:	O
@johntomsett	O
:	O
On	O
a	O
sunny	O
day	O
in	O
York	B-place
,	O
"	O
Why	O
putting	O
your	O
family	O
first	O
matters	O
.	O
"	O
http://t.co/yEf9BsWzJb	O

Yooooo	O
hit	O
my	O
DM	O
if	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
parties	O
for	O
tonight	O
.	O

@JayTheMustache	O
queriassss	O
:	O
$	O
$	O
$	O
$	O
$	O
$	O
$	O
$	O
$	O

Hopefully	O
Half	B-product
-	I-product
Life	I-product
3	I-product
Will	O
Look	O
as	O
Good	O
as	O
its	O
Fan	O
Trailer	O
http://t.co/GuHhhy5gZS	O

This	O
heart	O
burn	O
be	O
having	O
me	O
fucking	O
some	O
tums	O
up	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
Lol	O

@GuaxinimGamer	O
voce	O
tem	O
que	O
resolver	O
se	O
vai	O
ser	O
um	O
guaxinim	O
ou	O
um	O
gatinho	O
kkk	O

@ssshanesse	O
that	O
shit	O
a	O
whole	O
process	O
you	O
got	O
to	O
make	O
sure	O
everything	O
place	O
in	O
the	O
right	O
order	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
Information	O
wrote	O
correctly	O

Foto	O
:	O
riverofbones	O
:	O
(	O
by	O
Anton	B-person
Stenander	I-person
)	O
http://t.co/yzV9veyrTO	O

Buat	O
yang	O
belum	O
terpilih	O
semangat	O
juga	O
ya	O
!	O
!	O
^	O
^	O

It's	O
a	O
great	O
run	O
when	O
your	O
booty	O
is	O
all	O
sweaty	O

CBHS	O
will	O
be	O
closed	O
again	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
March	O
4	O
.	O

a	O
red	O
voltou	O
pra	O
ouat	O
?	O
voei	O
com	O
ela	O
nesse	O
ep	O
kskmsjkslmsj	O

DSTV	B-organization
really	O
catering	O
to	O
lowest	O
common	O
denominator	O
.	O
Choices	O
tonight	O
:	O
Redneck	B-product
Island	I-product
,	O
Jerry	B-product
Springer	I-product
,	O
Jersey	B-product
Shore	I-product
,	O
Cheaters	B-product
.	O
#absolutekak	O

Best	O
place	O
to	O
post	O
dating	O
advice	O
questions	O
:	O
The	O
Attraction	O
Forums	O
,	O
largest	O
free	O
dating	O
advice	O
site	O
for	O
men	O
http://t.co/KXkFJdWyjI	O

Andy	B-person
Warhol	I-person
Close	O
Up	O
-	O
Bob	B-person
Colacello	I-person
Discusses	O
The	O
Elusive	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
Influential	O
Artist	O
.	O
http://t.co/Q4sOB32SG0	O

@Michael5SOS	O
is	O
luke	B-person
gonna	O
wear	O
the	O
tutu	O
on	O
tour	O
or	O
what	O

A	O
man	O
shouldn't	O
feel	O
lik	O
a	O
man	O
if	O
he	O
ok	O
wit	O
letting	O
a	O
female	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O

RT	O
@TallPaul612	O
:	O
We	O
could	O
just	O
go	O
out	O
back	O
and	O
dig	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
ground	O
like	O
them	O
ol	O
'	O
gete	O
-	O
anishinabeg	O
did	O

A	O
rose	O
for	O
everyone	O
The	O
Glow	O
of	O
a	O
White	O
Rose	O
http://t.co/FECvJQUZOj	O
#petchat	O

RT	O
@P9	O
:	O
@choosenine	O
@naveiajon	O
@adamovichporn	O
@guipnine	O
@p9movich	O
@orgasmovich	O
claro	O
amores	O
!	O
Amei	O
os	O
users	O
ahahahha	O

If	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
embarrass	O
myself	O
I'll	O
just	O
talk	O
to	O
you	O
in	O
person	O

Haphaaap	O
(	O
@	O
Fitness	O
One	O
)	O
http://t.co/geB2VIUhct	O

I'm	O
a	O
god	O
with	O
the	O
tac	O
45	O

so	O
he	O
just	O
took	O
illegal	O
drugs	O
instead	O
http://t.co/Bnn0Lu85XE	O

Belom	O
ngantuk	O
"	O
@PERFAKE_RPS	O
:	O
#yvrxask	O
kenapa	O
belom	O
tidur	O
?	O
"	O

RT	O
@AyeTahj	O
:	O
@Zimbabwe_	O
Kickback	O
tonight	O
,	O
come	O
thru	O
885	O
charter	O
club	O
dr	B-place
30043	O
Lawrenceville	B-place
,	O
ga	O

Me	O
and	O
my	O
lady	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
support	O
me	O
tonight	O
as	O
I	O
ministered	O
on	O
the	O
#O4cLive	O
experience	O
http://t.co/J2AhMKArnb	O

I've	O
only	O
looked	O
at	O
two	O
text	O
messages	O
the	O
past	O
couple	O
hours	O

@Michael5SOS	O
whats	O
ur	O
fave	O
game	O
to	O
play	O

@limchoylee	O
@bad_dominicana	O
awww	O
!	O
it	O
sounds	O
deeply	O
soul	O
-	O
nourishing	O
.	O
enjoy	O
for	O
both	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
and	O
IG	O
DAT	O
BISH	O
lol	O

I	O
will	O
have	O
latte	O
now	O
.	O
Just	O
kidding	O
a	O
small	O
pack	O
of	O
biscoots	O
and	O
chai	O
will	O
do	O
it	O
.	O

@stratf0rdfinest	O
@upwithkidrauhl	O
lmao	O
your	O
entitled	O
to	O
your	O
wrong	O
opinion	O
that's	O
fine	O

RT	O
@notthatjohnking	O
:	O
The	O
wind	O
beneath	O
your	O
seat	O
is	O
because	O
of	O
that	O
pizza	O
.	O
#Oscars	O

#tbt	O
to	O
shooting	O
with	O
@ethanjamesphoto	O
#blackandwhite	O
http://t.co/y6lVGvQdk3	O

IM	O
LAUGHING	O
SO	O
HARD	O
EVERYTHINGS	O
GETTING	O
DELETED	O
AND	O
EVERYONE	O
IS	O
FREAKING	O
OUT	O

{	O
Frowns	O
as	O
I	O
get	O
up	O
and	O
walk	O
to	O
the	O
couch	O
,	O
dropping	O
down	O
beside	O
@AdeptMartyr	O
}	O

I	O
still	O
have	O
this	O
overwhelming	O
nostalgia	O
for	O
New	B-place
York	I-place
though	O
,	O
shedding	O
my	O
skin	O
,	O
mourning	O
,	O
experiencing	O
a	O
free	O
kind	O
of	O
joy	O
,	O
loving	O

At	O
the	O
round	O
table	O
chopping	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
my	O
bro	O
malike	B-person
about	O
the	O
future	O

@kissme1Dimlegal	O
YEAH	O
THAT'S	O
ONE	O
OF	O
THEM	O
OMG	O
IS	O
THAT	O
THE	O
ONE	O
HE	O
WATCHED	O
?	O
?	O
?	O

@southqoreans	O
@azlinpls	O
@stroberinick	O
@naadpls	O
@aimiqtpie	O
i	O
miss	O
u	O
all	O
im	O
sorry	O
to	O
say	O
i've	O
drifted	O
from	O
the	O
exo	O
fandom	O
sigh	O

Thanks	O
so	O
much	O
for	O
recent	O
RTs	O
!	O
@Bernaguguk	O
@PollyWinters	O
@field_fare	O
@The_Lumberzach_	O
@AldoLeopoldFdn	O
@1brendamarie	O
@leeparisdaylee	O
@sac88	O

RT	O
@grimminal	O
:	O
@VegasCashFlow	O
lol	O
omg	O
did	O
that	O
just	O
happen	O
?	O

You	O
will	O
stay	O
alone	O
for	O
it	O
everytime	O
.	O
.	O

The	O
sabbs	O
are	O
at	O
#sionhill	O
promoting	O
the	O
#teachingsawards	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
nominated	O
yet	O
?	O
http://t.co/C2WDEi0DOU	O

Only	O
four	O
more	O
hours	O
until	O
CHAMBER	B-organization
ORCHESTRA	I-organization
KREMLIN	I-organization
.	O
Tickets	O
will	O
be	O
available	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
(	O
box	O
office	O
opens	O
at	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/OxE5BAsNYG	O

I	O
LOVCE	O
NIALL	O
SO	O
AMUCXB	O

@CotswoldsConcie	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
needed	O
-	O
one	O
plain	O
chocolate	O
digestive	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
Bliss	O
;	O
)	O

@cynthiaa_sp	O
ni	O
de	O
pedo	O
que	O
no	O
has	O
llegado	O
!	O
ddd	O
te	O
amo	O
,	O
ven	O
bitch	O

@penggilafilm	O
#GilaFilmKuis	O
tdk	O
usah	O
mention	O
mimin	O
kan	O
?	O
:)	O

@Butros73	O
Kendekol	O
1998	O
degil	O
15	O
Agustos	O
2000	O
'	O
dir	O

You	O
so	O
tite	O
,	O
b	O
RT	O
@OGMelo_	O
:	O
Add	O
lil	O
henn	O
to	O
my	O
chick	O
fil	O
a	O
tea	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
crank	O
these	O
tweets	O
out	O
.	O

Imagine	O
a	O
JCCC	O
with	O
@phirm	O
and	O
@hankgreen	O
together	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
high	O
-	O
5	O
:	O
a	O
cheerwave	O
.	O
like	O
Superman	O
simul	O
-	O
punching	O
Darkseid	O
.	O
But	O
happier	O
.	O

@ShawnnMendes	O
shawn	O
what's	O
wrong	O
:(	O

@ChloeBurton3	O
watchin	O
a	O
film	O
what	O
abart	O
u	O
love	O

@eiconellardlee	O
@KenChrisVPang	O
tara	O
arat	O
:(	O
(	O
(	O
haha	O

How	O
ya	O
doin	O
today	O
?	O
!	O
#loveyou	O

RT	O
@gogamecocks	O
:	O
Groundout	O
ends	O
the	O
Clemson	B-organization
half	O
of	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
Tigers	O
strand	O
one	O
after	O
the	O
leadoff	O
single	O
.	O
0	O
-	O
0	O

Events	O
:	O
@hustleGRL	O
CMW	O
Showcase	O
w	O
/	O
Naturally	O
Born	O
Strangers	O
@TreMission	O
@theairplaneboys	O
@AGameMedia	O
-	O
May	O
8	O
@	O
Tattoo	B-place
http://t.co/OCC3VN37AN	O

Thank	O
God	O
for	O
bottled	O
water	O
.	O

Sausage	O
Recipes	O
-	O
99	O
Cooking	O
#food	O
#foodies	O
#recipes	O
#delicious	O
#meals	O
#dinner	O
#dinnerideas	O
#mealid	O
http://t.co/uHgMCpJJOo	O

Lionel	B-person
Richie	I-person
.	O
RT	O
@BrokeJackJonson	O
:	O
Billy	B-person
Ocean	I-person
probably	O
had	O
the	O
illest	O
short	O
fro	O
of	O
the	O
80s	O
.	O

RT	O
@AlisonRobzx	O
:	O
@RowlandSara	O
@Am_Shem	O
@bhengu_nelisiwe	O
@Buang_03	O
@Dominicanits	O
@RIAWAHINE	O
Glad	O
to	O
hear	O
it	O
:)	O
wishing	O
u	O
a	O
fab	O
weekend	O
xoxo	O

A	O
guy	O
in	O
my	O
school	O
has	O
a	O
pink	O
one	O
direction	O
backpack	O
um	O

@MonikAstiadi	O
hahaha	O
,	O
suami	O
kKiki	O
lucuuuuu	O
,	O
gmn	O
tuh	O
reaksi	O
kalian	O
berdua	O
?	O

@Bronco_Mike251	O
@CJ_BroncosPFS	O
Paste	O
your	O
tweets	O
into	O
an	O
article	O
.	O
There	O
,	O
you	O
wrote	O
something	O
!	O
:)	O

@caphe_sua_da	O
no	O
,	O
it	O
just	O
requires	O
constant	O
readiness	O
and	O
/	O
or	O
better	O
supermarket	O
opening	O
hours	O
!	O

.	O
@narendramodi	O
should	O
use	O
more	O
English	O
words	O
while	O
speaking	O
in	O
Hindi	O
in	O
other	O
regional	O
states	O
like	O
AP	B-place
,	O
Ktaka	B-place
,	O
Kerala	B-place
and	O
TN	B-place
@buzzindelhi	O

@omerakcaa	O
@ademyavuza	O
hadi	O
ordan	O
fetoya	O
soyleyin	O
sizi	O
de	O
alsin	O
ruya	O
toplantilarina	O

RT	O
@__nasyaa	O
:	O
"	O
@OfficialShaqira	O
:	O
"	O
@__nasyaa	O
:	O
Aku	O
harap	O
kau	O
sentap	O
.	O
"	O
Dah	O
"	O
bagus	O
ah	O
:)	O

Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
feeling	O
when	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
throw	O
a	O
baby	O
because	O
she	O
/	O
he	O
is	O
too	O
adorablee	O

Memahami	O
Makna	O
Batin	O
Alquran	O
:	O
Lapis	O
-	O
Lapis	O
Pemahaman	O
(	O
2	O
)	O
#Berita	O
#Kabar	O

#FollowCam	O
Be	O
my	O
3	O
/	O
5	O
please	O
@luke_brooks	O
@danielsahyounie	O
@JaiBrooks1	O
14	O

RT	O
@ohmykinglouis	O
:	O
different	O
dick	O
everynignt	O

RT	O
@Kobe_Diamond	O
:	O
Okay	O
I	O
see	O
you	O
Ali	B-person
@a_wad65	O
http://t.co/sDFfmTlRCw	O

I	O
STARTED	O
TWERKING	O
WITH	O
MY	O
2	O
YEAR	O
OLD	O
SISTER	O
WHEN	O
JAI	B-person
FOLLOWED	O
ME	O
.	O
I	O
WAS	O
DANCING	O
AND	O
DNFFGHKDGDFGDFGDFDF	O

@TorlanyM	O
PS	O
:	O
that's	O
not	O
me	O
insulting	O
you	O
.	O
Just	O
saying	O
it	O
doesn't	O
really	O
matter	O
if	O
somebody	O
says	O
something	O
I	O
disagree	O
with	O

@janoskians	O
@luke_brooks	O
@JaiBrooks1	O
@BrooksBeau	O
@danielsahyounie	O
PLEASE	O
FOLLOW	O
ME	O
GUYS	O
ILYSM	O
!	O
x	O
57	O

RT	O
@NFLDraftReport	O
:	O
Per	O
@ChrisTrapasso	O
,	O
Indiana	B-organization
WR	I-organization
Cody	B-person
Latimer	I-person
will	O
make	O
a	O
pre	O
-	O
draft	O
visit	O
to	O
the	O
#Bills	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
a	O
source	O
.	O

@smackinyc	O
I'd	O
pay	O
for	O
a	O
Yellowcard	B-product
song	O
about	O
Bacon	O
.	O
Just	O
saying	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
;	O
)	O

RT	O
@Kimmey163	O
:	O
Lmao	O
I	O
just	O
tweeted	O
this	O
RT	O
@GAMsoHANDSOME	O
:	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
watch	O
12	B-product
years	I-product
of	I-product
slave	I-product
soooo	O
bad	O

@Harry_Styles	O
WHAT	O
DID	O
YOU	O
DO	O
TO	O
YOUR	O
HAIR	O
?	O
?	O
?	O
?	O
?	O
?	O
?	O
?	O
?	O
?	O

@coconono	O
Have	O
you	O
heard	O
Nostalgia	B-product
Ultra	I-product
?	O
It's	O
his	O
free	O
album	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
like	O
that	O
,	O
you	O
should	O
enjoy	O
Channel	B-product
Orange	I-product
.	O

Arizona	B-place
governor's	O
office	O
worked	O
on	O
'	O
religious	O
liberty	O
'	O
bill	O
language	O
before	O
veto	O
:	O
http://t.co/Ss1uXNgNVI	O

I	O
don't	O
see	O
why	O
it's	O
insulting	O
to	O
wonder	O
if	O
men	O
appreciate	O
masculine	O
bodies	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
appreciate	O
feminine	O
ones	O
,	O
smh	O
.	O

@PKMTrainerWhite	O
dont	O
get	O
all	O
sciency	O
on	O
my	O
idc	O
.	O
.	O

@thebluemax1	O
Oh	O
happy	O
days	O
.	O
Maybe	O
we	O
are	O
entering	O
a	O
new	O
cold	O
war	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

@dee_kujo	O
@534peaches	O
that's	O
funny	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
think	O
my	O
headache	O
just	O
has	O
to	O
due	O
with	O
lack	O
of	O
sleep	O
.	O
.	O
no	O
spring	O
weather	O
here	O
yet	O
:(	O

The	O
photos	O
are	O
horrific	O
ya	O
Allah	O
!	O
:(	O
May	O
Allah	O
bless	O
the	O
innocent	O
souls	O
lost	O
today	O
,	O
and	O
may	O
they	O
rest	O
in	O
peace	O
.	O
#Benghazi	B-place

@MDogGeist	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
worst	O
piece	O
of	O
shit	O
I	O
ever	O
watched	O
in	O
my	O
entire	O
life	O
,	O
that	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
watch	O
it	O
again	O

Ppl	O
liked	O
this	O
tbh	O
post	O
I	O
put	O
on	O
IG	O
so	O
fast	O
lmao	O

RT	O
@ObiGotTheJuice	O
:	O
@SeanFuller_	O
@no_L7s_inmy_O	O
only	O
you	O
sean	O
lol	O
http://t.co/uTfbCW2j8u	O

tinder	O
on	O
rt	O
@carolchang	O
:	O
fiquei	O
sem	O
nada	O
pra	O
fazer	O
ontem	O
e	O
saiu	O
isso	O
aqui	O
:	O
http://t.co/8L1nCLbHdM	O

5	O
Things	O
I	O
Learned	O
From	O
Helping	O
My	O
Dad	O
Die	O
|	O
Noah	B-person
Michelson	I-person
|	O
http://t.co/PfTj6xVgwD	O

CAME	O
TO	O
DIS	O
CROWDED	O
ASS	O
MOVIE	O
THEATRE	O
SMD	O
http://t.co/BkyoXJ1qTY	O

@dev_story	O
lol	O
got	O
an	O
official	O
day	O
?	O
what	O
island	O
you	O
on	O

@Ririsel	O
tgal	O
4	O
Juni	O
2014	O
:)	O

@disneyfreak1024	O
@RaeRawrRae1	O
with	O
him	O
bc	O
i	O
was	O
mad	O
at	O
Bayani	B-person

@SHANICEsideup	O
pakyu	O
sinasabi	O
ko	O
lang	O
HAHA	O
momol	O
asap	O
pls	O

Leo	B-person
loving	O
his	O
new	O
'	O
travel	O
buddy	O
'	O
#HenryHugglemonster	O
@sharkeytweets	O
the	O
quality	O
is	O
outstanding	O
!	O
http://t.co/NtryUJ9la4	O

The	O
Sound	O
of	O
Swearing	O
.	O
#EskomMovies	O

RT	O
@JohnGraham813	O
:	O
@BlackGuyRab	O
@Zeroviral	O
still	O
gonna	O
be	O
sitting	O
on	O
your	O
phone	O
at	O
work	O
like	O
you're	O
doing	O
as	O
we	O
speak	O
.	O
Case	O
closed	O
.	O

Zoom	O
focus	O
on	O
your	O
goals	O
and	O
believe	O
.	O
Don't	O
be	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
great	O

@linnea_peterson	O
I	O
guess	O
im	O
different	O
which	O
is	O
what	O
i	O
tell	O
everyone	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
my	O
own	O
style	O
,	O
fashion	O
,	O
and	O
personality	O
.	O
Im	O
honest	O
and	O
fair	O
to	O
all	O

RT	O
@LilianaCamacho0	O
:	O
MAGIC	O
#Vote1D	O
#KCA	O

This	O
TV	O
Segment	O
Got	O
So	O
Tense	O
That	O
Dana	B-person
Perino	I-person
Needed	O
to	O
Take	O
a	O
Deep	O
Breath	O
After	O
Exploding	O
on	O
Her	O
Liberal	O
Co	O
-	O
Host	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

@Crumpet09	O
@RavelElven	O
I	O
want	O
evidence	O
haha	O

Paul	B-person
Ryan	I-person
needs	O
to	O
stop	O
messing	O
about	O
with	O
Cassie	B-person
Winslow	I-person
.	O
What	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
would	O
Barbara	B-person
&	O
amp	O
;	O
Reva	B-person
say	O
?	O
#ATWT	O
#GL	O
#GH	O

Lo	O
mas	O
impresionante	O
es	O
que	O
me	O
lo	O
topo	O
siempree	O
es	O
el	O
destino	O
chicos	O
yo	O
lo	O
se	O

@WashingMachineO	O
@MR_Flargenstein	O
@ellyberries	O
it's	O
that	O
thin	O
Calgary	B-place
air	O
,	O
it	O
got	O
to	O
her	O
head	O

@mark_doubt	O
Cheers	O
!	O
I	O
feel	O
very	O
special	O
.	O

Island	O
Paradise	O
-	O
#IslandParadise	O
-	O
Not	O
all	O
Caribbean	B-place
Islands	I-place
are	O
created	O
equal	O
!	O
St	B-place
Lucia	I-place
is	O
definitely	O
the	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/zGpLsIyJ8N	O

#Job	O
Hospice	O
RN	O
Case	O
Manager	O
-	O
PHX	O
-	O
Gemini	B-organization
Hospice	I-organization
-	O
Phoenix	B-place
,	O
AZ	O
Find	O
this	O
Job	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
More	O
http://t.co/xakndD2b1k	O

I	O
would	O
love	O
to	O
visit	O
Africa	B-place
someday	O
!	O

The	O
gossip	O
in	O
me	O
was	O
looking	O
forward	O
to	O
a	O
@betsyscribeindc	O
write	O
up	O
on	O
CPAC	B-organization
parties	O
.	O
Breitbart	B-person
ruined	O
everything	O
.	O
http://t.co/Qfp0Lb21YP	O

2	O
.	O
"	O
@teddyferrari1	O
:	O
"	O
He	O
fool	O
pass	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
@TheoPhlow	O
:	O
He	O
Be	O
Senior	O
Boy	O
roff	O
"	O
@teddyferrari1	O
:	O
But	O
Welbie	B-person
be	O
some	O
underrated	O
dude	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
"	O
"	O
"	O

That	O
sleep	O
was	O
from	O
God	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
rest	O
looooool	O
me	O
I	O
never	O
get	O
sleep	O
like	O
dat	O
woooay	O

Holy	O
omg	O
wtf	O
#hannibal	B-product

@Sexymadamz	O
hmmm	O
come	O
back	O
here	O

@UpfrontBitch	O
BUT	O
YOURE	O
WRONG	O
DHSKAKTKTOEWK	O

@All_In_Ones	O
Mane	O
I	O
like	O
Neon	B-organization
Trees	I-organization
new	O
song	O
Sleeping	B-product
With	I-product
a	I-product
Friend	I-product
I	O
listen	O
to	O
OneRepublic	B-organization
I	O
like	O
Daughtry	B-organization
,	O
The	B-organization
Fray	I-organization
a	O
lot	O
of	O
people	O
!	O

Church	B-organization
of	I-organization
England	I-organization
school	O
faces	O
allegations	O
of	O
taping	O
children's	O
mouths	O
shut	O
.	O
Police	O
advise	O
parents	O
to	O
sort	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/YSn7AoEB6L	O

@ArianaGrande	O
The	O
house	O
I	O
grew	O
up	O
in	O
was	O
9611	B-place
Carriage	I-place
Rd	I-place
.	I-place
in	I-place
Kensington	I-place
,	I-place
MD	I-place
.	O
The	O
metro	O
area	O
is	O
split	O
between	O
MD	B-place
and	O
VA	B-place
.	O
Traffic	O
sux	O
!	O

For	O
5th	O
consecutive	O
year	O
,	O
#Chevron	B-organization
leads	O
peer	O
-	O
group	O
in	O
5	O
-	O
year	O
total	O
shareholder	O
return	O
(	O
TSR	O
)	O
http://t.co/Kxl9RZkAt8	O
$CVX	O

Watching	O
@BlkSails_Starz	O
with	O
the	O
fam	O
!	O
Cool	O
shit	O
!	O
#fleshandbone	B-product

My	O
phone	O
got	O
took	O
.	O
:(	O

Ledisi	B-person
-	O
Pieces	O
Of	O
Me	O
:	O
http://t.co/JvFYo25i5N	O

#FishFarming	O
#News	O
/	O
155	O
,	O
000	O
#salmon	O
escaped	O
from	O
#fish	O
farm	O
in	O
#Yell	O
,	O
#Shetland	O
.	O
Meridian	B-organization
Salmon	I-organization
Group	I-organization
blames	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/qhDyW96epY	O

are	O
you	O
the	O
one	O
is	O
so	O
stupid	O
but	O
I	O
love	O
it	O
lol	O

(	O
Ween	O
,	O
language	O
warning	O
,	O
duh	O
)	O

@ctoombs	O
this	O
is	O
incredible	O
.	O
My	O
new	O
travel	O
list	O
.	O
Toombs	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
you	O
the	O
best	O
.	O

RT	O
@BURRforshort	O
:	O
Lastnight	O
was	O
really	O
fun	O
.	O
.	O
I	O
needed	O
that	O
.	O

.	O
@bbcscitech	O
Why	O
images	O
of	O
aurora	O
from	O
ISS	B-organization
to	O
explain	O
BICEP2	O
results	O
?	O

Felicitaciones	O
a	O
Nancy	B-person
Ferreira	I-person
Dupuy	I-person
!	O
Ganadora	O
del	O
libro	O
SOY	B-product
75	I-product
Mujeres	I-product
-	I-product
75	I-product
Historias	I-product
Por	O
favor	O
comunicate	O
con	O
la	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/hv31T9bE7W	O

@PositivelyNot	O
Would	O
you	O
buy	O
a	O
second	O
-	O
hand	O
car	O
from	O
him	O
?	O
#SlipperyEel	O

Homs	O
|	O
Talbiseh	O
:	O
Fierce	O
clashes	O
between	O
FSA	B-organization
&	O
amp	O
;	O
regime	O
forces	O
at	O
Jbourin	B-place
+	O
fierce	O
shelling	O
targets	O
the	O
city	O
http://t.co/xXZN7r5mqE	O
#Syria	B-place

Or	O
Yukki	O
from	O
Mirai	B-product
Nikki	I-product

"	O
@amirulashrafh	O
:	O
Zoom	O
dan	O
terbalikkan	O
phone	O
anda	O
http://t.co/yyhSsXdBWA	O
"	O
pocong	O
uih	O
nightmare	O
bye	O

RT	O
this	O
if	O
you	O
want	O
#PerfectSoFar	B-product
to	O
be	O
@ashanti	O
'	O
s	O
next	O
single	O
from	O
#BraveHeart	B-product
#teamashanti	O
@ASHANTINEWS	O
http://t.co/JUVYlweVY5	O

You	O
scared	O
?	O
?	O
?	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
Don't	O
be	O
scared	O
un	O
uhh	O

Yo	O
@YG	O
are	O
you	O
always	O
high	O
bruh	O
?	O

@FierceKitty	O
it's	O
more	O
like	O
material	O
science	O
,	O
but	O
I've	O
worked	O
on	O
compliant	O
surfaces	O
for	O
multitouch	O
screens	O
,	O
finding	O
the	O
right	O
mix	O
of	O
stuff	O
.	O

Masalahnya	O
dari	O
kmrin	O
yg	O
aku	O
takutin	O
malah	O
terjadi	O
.	O
Takutnya	O
yg	O
kali	O
ini	O
juga	O
.	O
Watdehel	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
!	O

Waka	O
Pass	O
@Beautyful_Adzz	O
Rotate	O
again	O
,	O
Con	O
waka	O
Pass	O
her	O
again	O
!	O
!	O
UKU	O

Skipping	O
Resurrection	B-product
because	O
I	O
can't	O
be	O
bothered	O
with	O
that	O
show	O
anymore	O
.	O

RT	O
@moodym0lly	O
:	O
Missing	O
someone	O
is	O
not	O
my	O
favorite	O
feeling	O
.	O

That	O
Lil	O
Nap	O
&	O
gt	O
;	O
&	O
gt	O
;	O

We	O
went	O
0	O
for	O
yesterday	O
.	O
I'm	O
still	O
fed	O
up	O
lol	O

@KeenanRIVALS	O
yes	O
way	O
lol	O
105	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
back	O

Not	O
ur	O
main	O
RT	O
@SpugzBeLike	O
:	O
What	O
are	O
'	O
side	O
hoes	O
'	O
?	O

Good	O
News	O
for	O
Buyers	O
,	O
Sellers	O
:	O
Home	O
Sales	O
Are	O
Up	O
in	O
Birmingham	B-place
Area	O
http://t.co/4SMXaxj0SN	O
#ERAKingBham	O

RT	O
@iCloud3k	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
charge	O
my	O
phone	O
.	O
It	O
never	O
gets	O
to	O
me	O
until	O
it's	O
on	O
5	O
%	O
.	O

Fab	O
Fashion	O
:	O
Givenchy	O
RTW	O
Fall	O
2014	O
:	O
Riccardo	B-person
Tisci	I-person
created	O
a	O
tension	O
between	O
rich	O
romance	O
and	O
p	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/xBHAF2Y5zM	O
#fashion	O
#fab	O

@itsPERFECTO	O
That	O
whole	O
event	O
was	O
gloriously	O
bizarre	O
in	O
hindsight	O
.	O

Alhamdulillah	O
bukan	O
.	O
.	O
ehehehe	O
(	O
-	O
-	O
,	O
)	O
&	O
gt	O
;	O
RT	O
@diaslicious	O
:	O
@AwakeningKay	O
@DiDisea95	O
yah	O
.	O
.	O
aku	O
kira	O
si	O
Di	O
ini	O
yg	O
jadi	O
pacar	O
kamu	O
,	O
kay	O
.	O

RT	O
@BourneAcademyPA	O
:	O
Looking	O
forward	O
to	O
watching	O
Romeo	B-product
and	I-product
Juliet	I-product
Wednesday	O
night	O
@LighthousePoole	O
@clevertheatre	O
remember	O
6	O
:	O
40PM	O
meet	O
!	O

@SagiOrli	O
Well	O
if	O
that	O
train	O
starts	O
flying	O
he'll	O
do	O
whatever	O
he	O
needs	O
to	O
survive	O
.	O
Lol	O
.	O

RT	O
@Kev92Kelly	O
:	O
Gus	B-person
Fring	I-person
bringing	O
the	O
Canaries	B-other
down	O

new	O
boondocks	O
April	O
21st	O
!	O

I	O
can	O
feel	O
my	O
back	O
and	O
my	O
face	O
burning	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O

Texas	B-place
Jury	O
Awards	O
$	O
25M	O
In	O
Cardiac	O
MRI	O
Trade	O
Secret	O
Suit	O
http://t.co/cMEBCU7cVX	O

Fraudulent	O
Flake	O
Fluke	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
Pick	O
One	O
!	O

Stylishly	O
Loud	O
REWIND	O
:	O
Fashionation	O
:	O
Infinite	B-organization
Fashions	I-organization
LLC	I-organization
-	O
Being	O
the	O
Stylishly	O
Loud	O
woman	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
I	O
love	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/LpMZ6z8IRg	O

Did	O
Wisconsin	B-place
just	O
knock	O
Minnesota	B-place
off	O
the	O
bubble	O
?	O
A	O
look	O
at	O
a	O
dominant	O
performance	O
:	O
http://t.co/wrKBYbw7kM	O

The	O
back	O
of	O
this	O
ball	O
cap	O
pretty	O
much	O
says	O
it	O
all	O
!	O
http://t.co/6QfFl9e8Z6	O

Shabnam	B-person
is	O
such	O
a	O
bitch	O
!	O
#EastEnders	O

This	O
nigga	O
bet	O
not	O
post	O
those	O
!	O

U	O
even	O
compress	O
bro	O
?	O
@	O
Encore	O
Recording	O
http://t.co/0V4R1gLQhj	O

@Beautebitch_	O
I	O
left	O
at	O
5	O
.	O
30	O
!	O
Lol	O

I	O
just	O
had	O
the	O
most	O
intense	O
dream	O
of	O
my	O
life	O
.	O

"	O
Russia	B-place
must	O
know	O
that	O
further	O
escalation	O
will	O
only	O
isolate	O
it	O
further	O
"	O
-	O
Obama	B-person
http://t.co/BylkWCxYVV	O

Hope	O
my	O
future	O
students	O
don't	O
put	O
too	O
much	O
effort	O
into	O
tracking	O
down	O
the	O
mile	O
-	O
wide	O
trail	O
of	O
swears	O
and	O
I've	O
left	O
across	O
the	O
internet	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

Pretty	O
glad	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
'	O
pen	O
-	O
and	O
-	O
ink	O
in	O
my	O
friends	O
apartment	O
'	O
look	O
at	O
any	O
point	O

mimi	B-person
lindley	I-person
we	O
have	O
to	O
stalk	O
tw	O
pls	O
ok	O

RT	O
@exomhero	O
:	O
Gua	O
salah	O
milih	O
mulu	O
dah	O
-	O
_	O
-	O

RT	O
@nayahollic	O
:	O
omg	O
how	O
naya	B-person
jumped	O
on	O
harry	B-person
when	O
they	O
were	O
dancing	O
to	O
valerie	B-person

@fartboyniall	O
YOURE	O
GONNA	O
DO	O
GREAT	O

Change	O
of	O
pace	O
/	O
location	O
-	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
beautiful	O
Balkan	B-place
voices	O
:	O
Esma	B-person
Redzepova	I-person
-	O
Gelem	O
,	O
gelem	O
http://t.co/39730xYfib	O

@AmandaCSykes	O
thank	O
you	O
!	O
Really	O
glad	O
you	O
enjoyed	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
lovely	O
time	O
in	O
Salisbury	B-place
,	O
terrific	O
theatre	O
and	O
lovely	O
crowd	O
.	O

How	O
to	O
Block	O
Someone	O
on	O
Linkedin	B-organization
:	O
http://t.co/5MF7LrFCOZ	O
via	O
@YouTube	O

Associate	O
Veterinarian	O
-	O
CO	O
(	O
http://t.co/s1qUnT8VVA	O
)	O
#Veterinarian	O
#jobs	O
#job	O
#GetAllJobs	O

When	O
you	O
put	O
yourself	O
out	O
there	O
that's	O
what	O
you	O
get	O

@frxcknash	O
yup	O
.	O
if	O
it	O
bleeds	O
a	O
lot	O
and	O
for	O
no	O
reason	O
than	O
he	O
snorts	O
cocaine	O
but	O
if	O
it	O
doesn't	O
then	O
he	O
doesn't	O
snort	O
cocaine	O

RT	O
@haetongue	O
:	O
LOL	O
RT	O
@hyukarmpits	O
then	O
hae	O
said	O
as	O
expected	O
we're	O
good	O
than	O
kry	O
haha	O

If	O
you	O
guys	O
care	O
about	O
Gaga	B-person
don't	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
apartment	O
.	O

@SpanishKash_	O
@nazu86	O
cant	O
even	O
lie	O
I	O
did	O
btec	O
science	O
in	O
high	O
school	O
and	O
passed	O
it	O
.	O
is	O
that	O
when	O
flowers	O
have	O
sex	O
or	O
something	O

@TwitchTV_ProdX	O
HOLD	O
OFF	O
ON	O
BUYING	O
IT	O
FROM	O
GMG	B-organization
!	O

RT	O
@_isIand	O
:	O
Thomas	B-person
the	O
Train	O
took	O
one	O
hit	O
of	O
crack	O
cocaine	O
and	O
now	O
look	O
at	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
Ruined	O
.	O
RT	O
for	O
support	O
!	O
http://t.co/aymTvcTPyV	O

#FIFA14	O
#AmazingGoal	O
#YaEtshYaLa3eb	O
#Arsenal	O
@	O
Etsh's	O
place	O
(	O
Cairo	O
)	O
http://t.co/naJEASgxTi	O

Wait	O
school	O
closed	O
?	O

@FallenKitten13_	O
please	O
.	O
And	O
it's	O
not	O
just	O
for	O
me	O
.	O

If	O
I	O
cut	O
,	O
oh	O
well	O
.	O
If	O
I'm	O
going	O
to	O
kill	O
myself	O
,	O
oh	O
well	O
.	O
The	O
earth	O
will	O
be	O
better	O
when	O
I	O
kill	O
myself	O
soon	O
enough	O
:)	O

@Steve5615	O
@DHoltSzcinski	O
@BarracudaMama	O
More	O
of	O
Obama's	B-person
'	O
sons	O
'	O
?	O

It	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
day	O
!	O
#friends	O
#fun	O
#sun	O
#nature	O
#happy	O
;	O
D	O

@FaulknerBruce	O
No	O
need	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
have	O
to	O
do	O
our	O
best	O
with	O
140	O
characters	O
!	O

RT	O
@_LoveLauri	O
:	O
all	O
this	O
love	O
in	O
me	O
no	O
one	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
.	O

I	O
like	O
kissing	O
with	O
my	O
weak	O
ass	O
lol	O

Lukaku	B-person
puts	O
Everton	O
in	O
the	O
lead	O
and	O
brings	O
in	O
part	O
1	O
of	O
our	O
weekend	O
scorer	O
DOUBLE	O
!	O
!	O

Christ	O
should	O
be	O
the	O
focus	O
,	O
NOT	O
church	B-other

OMFG	O
THE	B-product
MAZE	I-product
RUNNER	I-product
TRAILER	O
WAS	O
PERFECT	O
THE	O
LAST	O
SCENE	O
WHERE	O
HE	O
RUNS	O
THROUGH	O
THE	O
WALL	O
GAVE	O
ME	O
GOOSEBUMPS	O

Deel	O
Suikerunieterrrein	O
in	O
bruikleen	O
voor	O
AOC	O
Terra	O
http://t.co/RavfApZOA9	O

@pizzano2l	O
@moranimal_o2l	O
I	O
ONLY	O
SCREENSHOT	O
THE	O
ACTUAL	O
DRAMA	O
.	O
ORION	B-person
AND	O
ANTHONY	B-person
WERE	O
JUST	O
MAKING	O
FUN	O
OF	O
HOW	O
SHE	O
SAID	O
YOU	O
IN	O
THAT	O
ONE	O
VINE	O

Look	O
at	O
the	O
picture	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
$PLUG	O
would	O
keep	O
going	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
hold	O
and	O
now	O
its	O
at	O
$	O
8	O
.	O
00	O
this	O
doesnt	O
suprise	O
me	O
http://t.co/ZPXeEprXL1	O

RT	O
@LosCorrientesFc	O
:	O
#LosCorrientes	O
en	O
#SSC	O
@GabGutierrezF	O
@Bet0man	O
@AndresPellacini	O
http://t.co/lWHKS02yBj	O

#DRH	O
,	O
quels	O
leviers	O
activer	O
pour	O
un	O
retour	O
de	O
la	O
croissance	O
dans	O
vos	O
entreprises	O
?	O
RDV	O
avec	O
@ADP_fr	O
le	O
26	O
mars	O
http://t.co/1I5i83XxI6	O

RT	O
@benjiwalker39	O
:	O
Valiant	O
effort	O
from	O
the	O
@SurbitonHC	O
u18	O
'	O
s	O
#whatcouldhavebeen	O
#valleypeople	O

@KT_HUTCH	O
@alarmingAMANDA	O
@newkingofmedia	O
@jontaffer	O
@AlexandersFells	O
you	O
must	O
get	O
to	O
@papistacos	O
outstanding	O

The	O
only	O
limitations	O
you	O
have	O
is	O
upon	O
yo	O
delf	O

RT	O
@_PrettyyGirlAsh	O
:	O
Sundy	O
got	O
pressure	O
bout	O
Draya	B-person
why	O
?	O
She	O
must	O
didn't	O
accept	O
that	O
money	O
to	O
fuck	O
you	O
huh	O
?	O

@LouisOreo_	O
I	O
love	O
marvel	O
,	O
idk	O
who	O
my	O
fave	O
is	O
I	O
love	O
them	O
all	O

RT	O
@itskjc	O
:	O
Do	O
something	O
useful	O
and	O
roll	O
a	O
joint	O

@lovelocked89	O
is	O
it	O
still	O
around	O
?	O

This	O
just	O
in	O
!	O
#vinyl	O
#records	O
#soundtracks	O
#80s	O
#musicals	O
#opera	O
#classics	O
http://t.co/ZrZyHS6H0y	O

RT	O
@sofiabages	O
:	O
@camipalooza	O
@menemOrdie	O
si	O
que	O
se	O
joda	O
por	O
jugar	O
con	O
su	O
cuerpo	O
bue	O
ay	O
si	O
a	O
veces	O
creo	O
que	O
lo	O
quiero	O
o	O
era	O
siEMPRE	O

I	O
just	O
got	O
a	O
phone	O
call	O
from	O
Texas	B-place
,	O
USA	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

@steeplechasing	O
@helynsar	O
I'm	O
off	O
the	O
bandwagon	O
after	O
the	O
Paddy	B-organization
Power	I-organization
chaps	O
.	O
He's	O
served	O
me	O
well	O
and	O
good	O
luck	O
to	O
him	O
#AlFerof	O

@TyrantMitch	O
@Mr__Rude	O
@RicoChavo	O
that's	O
my	O
kind	O
of	O
damn	O
night	O
!	O

both	O
choices	O
are	O
hilarious	O
http://t.co/tWQrlsxLwG	O

@SandyEatsCandy	O
@erinkarre	O
Oh	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
increase	O
your	O
pain	O
.	O
She	O
wasn't	O
being	O
facetious	O
about	O
the	O
crying	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
feels	O
so	O
good	O
after	O
!	O

Reddit	O
:	O
Selling	O
my	O
June	O
2013	O
Macbook	B-product
Air	I-product
http://t.co/dTi2sQjUUj	O

Perfect	O
combination	O
ever	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
#KotowaCoffee	O
http://t.co/NP6kBkahkM	O

@clarinetbiter13	O
I	O
mean	O
we	O
pet	O
him	O
!	O
And	O
feed	O
him	O
!	O

you	O
are	O
so	O
so	O
dead	O
gurl	O

DreamPad	B-product
pillow	O
plays	O
music	O
only	O
you	O
can	O
hear	O
!	O
http://t.co/Rf9uLjQIl1	O
via	O
@CNET	O

@sam_batalon	O
not	O
that	O
being	O
poor	O
means	O
you're	O
happy	O
,	O
just	O
that	O
being	O
happy	O
doesn't	O
mean	O
being	O
"	O
rich	O
"	O
monetarily	O

@missouri_belle	O
thank	O
you	O
:)	O
I	O
know	O
its	O
been	O
to	O
long	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
how	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
?	O

Kestrel	B-organization
Luxury	I-organization
Travel	I-organization
-	O
Kestrel	B-organization
Luxury	I-organization
Travel	I-organization
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
UK's	B-place
leading	O
specialist	O
luxury	O
tour	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/yY7mBkXmrY	O

RT	O
@DulcetesUSA	O
:	O
#INFO	O
:	O
Ya	O
pueden	O
comprar	O
#AntesQueVerElSol	O
de	O
@DulceMaria	O
en	O
Google	O
Play	O
Store	O
https://t.co/XozbNVlQnd	O

My	O
new	O
bed	O
is	O
too	O
comfortable	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
sanity	O

RT	O
@andrewharbron	O
:	O
@TheSwanseaWay	O
tremmel	O
tiendalli	O
amat	O
Bartley	B-person
Taylor	I-person
emnes	O
Vasquez	O
lita	O
canas	O
donnelly	O
routledge	O

There's	O
a	O
#DeppRoad	O
in	O
#Nevada	B-place
#justsaying	O

ECU	O
starters	O
:	O
Akeem	B-person
Richmond	I-person
,	O
Caleb	B-person
White	I-person
,	O
Antonio	B-person
Robinson	I-person
,	O
Paris	B-person
Roberts	I-person
-	I-person
Campbell	I-person
and	O
Michael	B-person
Zangari	I-person
.	O

RT	O
@PLDemiLovato	O
:	O
Koncert	O
w	O
St.	B-place
Louis	I-place
#NeonLightsTour	O
-	O
20	O
marzec	O
#	O
13	O
http://t.co/JCWl5MXJnp	O

Miami	B-place
-	O
San	B-place
Antonio	I-place
8h	O
aswe	O
a	O
.	O
NBA	O

@yahnehbunny	O
Monday	O
ko	O
dw	O
ma	O
inquire	O
hmbl	O
nya	O
.	O
nka	O
inquire	O
kna	O
ya	O
haw	O
?	O
:)	O

my	O
daughter	O
look	O
just	O
like	O
her	O
daddy	O
lawd	O
!	O
http://t.co/AcX4pylTJy	O

#FOLLOWTRICK	O
!	O
!	O
$	O
RT	O
THIS	O
$	O
FOLLOW	O
@harryftfreewifi	O
$	O
FOLLOW	O
EVERYONE	O
WHO	O
RTS	O
$	O
FOLLOW	O
ME	O
IFB	O
$	O
GAIN	O
!	O
:)	O
#5SOSinPhilippines	O
YAY	O

@Ronan_Lawson9	O
11k	O
bet	O
placed	O
(	O
3k	O
trust	O
)	O
on	O
sociedad	B-organization
to	O
win	O
and	O
over	O
2	O
.	O
5	O
goals	O
17	O
.	O
6k	O
return	O
.	O

Tahini	B-product
sauce	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
tahini	O
to	O
use	O
in	O
hummus	O
.	O
Lemony	O
.	O

Matthew's	B-person
speech	O
was	O
solid	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
would	O
appear	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
Mom	O
proud	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
still	O
feel	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
mentioned	O
the	O
millions	O
lost	O
to	O
AIDS	O

Awwies	O
"	O
@iPoke_em	O
:	O
Allllllll	O
of	O
me	O
!	O
"	O

RT	O
@mrstevebot	O
:	O
Holy	O
crap	O
what	O
a	O
crazy	O
first	O
week	O
!	O
@StartupInst	O
http://t.co/j1QAgaTbMe	O

@DougPologe	O
@todayszamancom	O
not	O
the	O
nation	O
.	O
The	O
lunatic	O
dictator	O
does	O
.	O

RT	O
@RodHissong	O
:	O
Town	B-place
of	I-place
Andrews	I-place
under	O
a	O
BOIL	O
WATER	O
ADVISORY	O
until	O
Monday	O
.	O

RT	O
@tbbinc3	O
:	O
Would	O
you	O
like	O
to	O
keep	O
up	O
with	O
this	O
Bearded	O
Bastard	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
crazy	O
shit	O
he	O
does	O
,	O
well	O
now	O
you	O
can	O
:	O
http://t.co/wjZRJlB7KI	O

UK	B-place
Conference	O
Will	O
Explore	O
Android	B-product
OS	I-product
for	O
Embedded	O
Devices	O
http://t.co/KpMuzTpYg3	O

RT	O
@quickenloans	O
:	O
Kentucky	B-place
advances	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
round	O
!	O
Remember	O
,	O
the	O
top	O
20	O
#BillionBracket	O
entries	O
will	O
win	O
$	O
100K	O
!	O

TUNE	O
IN	O
TO	O
MY	O
NEW	O
SINGLE	O
[	O
HATE	B-product
IF	I-product
YOU	I-product
WANT	I-product
]	O
FEAT	O
@ARSONALDAREBEL	O
#RT	O
#LETSPUSHIT	O
http://t.co/kkiLIitCbE	O

RT	O
@OurNiam	O
:	O
@Real_Liam_Payne	O
PLEASE	O
FOLLOW	O
ME	O
LIAM	B-person
IT	O
WOULD	O
MEAN	O
SO	O
MUCH	O

~	O
Star	O
Based	O
Ventriloquism	O
~	O

Hehehe	O
:(	O
"	O
@anaaaas_	O
:	O
Dikiranya	O
nangis	O
apa	O
:D	O
"	O
@Neti27_	O
:	O
Cup	O
cup	O
cup	O
"	O
@anaaaas_	O
:	O
Aku	O
nungguin	O
lama	O
loh	O
-	O
_	O
-	O
"	O
@Neti27_	O
"	O

@BTwo_Four	O
oh	O
I	O
guess	O
you	O
didn't	O
see	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
thought	O
you	O
did	O
lol	O

*	O
drives	O
up	O
to	O
girl	O
I	O
like	O
*	O
hey	O
?	O
I	O
still	O
have	O
my	O
permit	O
anyways	O
my	O
mom	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
backseat	O
say	O
hi	O
!	O

@firehazardniall	O
IM	O
NOT	O
A	O
CRY	O
BABY	O
YOU	O
STARTED	O
THIS	O

@LatinoPolitics	O
that's	O
the	O
real	O
story	O
lot	O
.	O
Of	O
buzz	O
and	O
only	O
12th	O

RT	O
@ReelTalker	O
:	O
@MisfitsTamara	O
@JoyDanielle61	O
@BlackGirlNerds	O
@reelsistas	O
how	O
about	O
jena	B-person
malone	I-person
as	O
pizazz	O
?	O

Someone	O
DM	O
me	O
:(	O
(	O
(	O
(	O
(	O

Adam	B-person
Carolla	I-person
for	O
president	O
in	O
2016	O

Creepy	O
nung	O
dolls	O
,	O
okay	O
.	O
:(	O
:(	O
:(	O

2NIGHT	O
!	O
#LifestyleSATURDAYS	O
@	O
Belasco	B-place
.	O
Live	O
Performance	O
by	O
"	O
Nipsey	B-person
Hussle	I-person
"	O
.	O
FREE	O
BEFORE	O
11PM	O
.	O
TEXT	O
310	O
.	O
505	O
.	O
6980	O
http://t.co/jYAr3JGZyU	O
RT	O

Hey	O
Copenhagen	B-place
Zoo	O
,	O
fuck	O
you	O
.	O
http://t.co/fdgAUco98A	O

@Aps4466	O
DMK	O
understands	O
politics	O
in	O
true	O
sense	O
of	O
terms	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
Karunanidhi	B-person
must	O
have	O
read	O
Machiavelli	B-person
more	O
than	O
anybody	O

@whysoperfmaddie	O
gurl	O
you	O
need	O
to	O
watch	O
it	O
ASAP	O

@fuckinqclifford	O
JUST	O
SHUT	O
UP	O
BECAUSE	O
I	O
CANT	O
HODL	O
THIS	O

@frenchyphan	O
shit	O
i'm	O
so	O
so	O
sorry	O
i	O
didn't	O
think	O
i	O

@samir	O
how	O
many	O
more	O
Saturday	O
nights	O
will	O
you	O
tempt	O
fate	O
like	O
this	O
my	O
friend	O
?	O

Bukankan	O
semua	O
hal	O
yang	O
diucapkan	O
,	O
walaupun	O
dengan	O
nada	O
sindiran	O
,	O
bercanda	O
ataupun	O
serius	O
,	O
sama	O
saja	O
dengan	O
mendoakan	O
?	O

@fatbusinessman	O
Are	O
you	O
adding	O
any	O
functionality	O
,	O
or	O
just	O
fixing	O
my	O
bugs	O
?	O
:)	O

RT	O
@LovinTheIron	O
:	O
Here	O
I	O
am	O
all	O
alone	O
at	O
work	O
with	O
nothing	O
but	O
my	O
@proteinbites1	O
to	O
keep	O
me	O
company	O
.	O
@AndreCoulson	O
http://t.co/4AaiAe5bBl	O

RT	O
@majutrindadef	O
:	O
se	O
sentir	O
falta	O
,	O
me	O
liga	O

RT	O
@AKINGDOMRP	O
:	O
#MirisItuSederhana	O
aku	O
sayang	O
kamu	O
tapi	O
kamu	O
sayang	O
dia	O
!	O
TT	O
_	O
_	O
TT	O
[	O
fypanny	O
]	O

my	O
stomach	O
needs	O
to	O
be	O
flatter	O
.	O

The	O
thing	O
about	O
zayn	B-person
is	O
you	O
cant	O
expect	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
outgoing	O
you	O
need	O
to	O
watch	O
him	O
carefully	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
while	O
watching	O
youll	O
see	O
the	O
little	O
things	O

"	O
We	O
mature	O
at	O
different	O
rates	O
and	O
we	O
may	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
him	O
until	O
his	O
mid	O
-	O
twenties	O
.	O
.	O
or	O
later	O
still	O
"	O
#Cleverley	O
http://t.co/cjwi51Q5jI	O

@classybrad	O
@xsassyvamps	O
I	O
think	O
it's	O
the	O
official	O
because	O
waddy	O
tweeted	O
it	O
earlier	O
:)	O

RT	O
@Exnorthseatiger	O
:	O
How	O
can	O
u	O
tell	O
she's	O
a	O
LibDem	O
?	O
Cos	O
she's	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
fence	O
,	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
shitting	O
on	O
her	O
neighbour	O
.	O
http://t.co/ADPhAZCrNd	O

@Funshinebear76	O
I	O
feel	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
You'd	O
think	O
that's	O
an	O
organization	O
you	O
could	O
find	O
true	O
friends	O
in	O
.	O

@Jamesbr91	O
@hollywaltersx	O
wasn't	O
you	O
browners	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Heard	O
your	O
a	O
maniac	O
on	O
the	O
dance	O
floor	O

UK	B-place
Bitcoin	O
Exchange	O
Bit121	O
Temporarily	O
Ceases	O
Operations	O
:	O
The	O
British	O
exchange	O
has	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
suspending	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/sTMsuXT3g6	O

it	O
surprises	O
me	O
that	O
no	O
NYK	B-organization
player	O
is	O
on	O
this	O
list	O
.	O
RT	O
@johnschuhmann	O
:	O
The	O
2013	O
-	O
14	O
0	O
-	O
for	O
-	O
10	O
-	O
plus	O
Club	O
:	O
http://t.co/oMrjuFyf63	O

The	O
way	O
Heyman	B-person
talks	O
up	O
Taker	B-person
does	O
a	O
lot	O
.	O
#RAW	O

@CAUTIONZARRY	O
SHUT	O
UP	O
IM	O
VOTING	O
SINCE	O
YESTERDAY	O

@TheRealDaphne	O
Yeah	O
it's	O
an	O
amazing	O
place	O
-	O
intense	O
but	O
inspiring	O
XXX	O

@kimmyb2702	O
I	O
would	O
but	O
I	O
don't	O
wanna	O
get	O
slut	O
on	O
me	O
xo	O

@wintercturner	O
lmao	O
i	O
wanted	O
to	O
stay	O
out	O
so	O
bad	O

Everything	O
is	O
pissing	O
me	O
off	O
this	O
morning	O

Ferdek	O
shagdsgsahdhsj	O

Group	O
seeks	O
more	O
jobs	O
-	O
http://t.co/nFR6cD7zZi	O

RT	O
@SACrimeAlert	O
:	O
@diamond_usa	O
Dear	O
Sara	B-person
K	I-person
.	I-person
E	I-person
.	I-person
Clearly	O
,	O
other	O
than	O
you	O
,	O
thank	O
you	O
,	O
no	O
one	O
cares	O
about	O
the	O
barbaric	O
murder	O
of	O
whites	O
in	O
SA	B-place
.	O

RT	O
@DjKauze	O
:	O
#WelcomeTweet	O
@panamastax	O
Appreciate	O
the	O
#Follow	O
.	O
.	O
I'm	O
Not	O
to	O
big	O
for	O
a	O
S	O
/	O
o	O
just	O
@	O
me	O
#OneLove	O
via	O
http://t.co/YHAme8O4mn	O

Lemme	O
call	O
my	O
dad	O
so	O
he	O
can	O
keep	O
me	O
company	O
walking	O
back	O

That	O
hype	O
god	O
nigga	O
always	O
gonna	O
be	O
meatwad	O
to	O
me	O
hahaha	O

Hope	O
you	O
enjoyed	O
tonight's	O
songs	O
!	O
#nashville	B-place

@Patyanehh	O
haha	O
wala	O
po	O
niloloko	O
ko	O
lang	O
si	O
pussykat	O
;	O
)	O

@buttgrabbing	O
settings	O
-	O
general	O
-	O
international	O
-	O
language	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
pick	O
british	O
english	O

@denimstyles	O
there	O
u	O
go	O
a	O
tru	O
directioner	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
1	O

@choosemari	O
I	O
feel	O
like	O
talking	O
to	O
uuuuu	O

@VERNALICIOUS1	O
@MannCenter	O
@phish	O
I'm	O
ready	O
,	O
see	O
you	O
there	O
Verna	B-person
.	O
#notmyfirstshow	O
#willnotactuallybeworking	O
#lookwhoseinthefreezer	O

siedze	O
sobie	O
a	O
za	O
plecami	O
brat	O
mi	O
gra	O
nem	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
3	O

Fastest	O
KO	O
in	O
MMA	O
history	O
!	O
http://t.co/rDm6KE9iRp	O

@TruckDiBatti	O
And	O
I	O
thought	O
mene	O
nazar	O
lgadi	O
.	O

@lorakolodny	O
LOL	O
-	O
yea	O
,	O
i	O
was	O
simply	O
agreeing	O
with	O
you	O
.	O

@craicingharry	O
I	O
LITERALLY	O
JUST	O
FUCKING	O
SCREAMED	O
OH	O
MY	O
GOD	O

@damncecee	O
,	O
you	O
weak	O
I	O
be	O
hitting	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
beltway	O
.	O

"	O
@kiwiCRISSY	O
:	O
bitch	O
shut	O
the	O
fuck	O
up	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
take	O
these	O
10	O
bricks	O
to	O
Kansas	B-place
!	O
"	O

RT	O
@TEENMUSICCRITIC	O
:	O
You	O
guys	O
need	O
to	O
check	O
out	O
@TaylorRaysTweet	O
vines	O
!	O
https://t.co/V6VmcALKAy	O

ask	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
dm	O
to	O
liam	B-person
okay	O

@HaziqAzahar	O
tapi	O
brader	O
wa	O
tak	O
perasan	O
muka	O
lu	O
.	O
Ini	O
membuktikan	O
Joseh	O
bukan	O
pokan	O
koboi	O
.	O

Also	O
,	O
will	O
churches	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
their	O
budgets	O
to	O
get	O
glow	O
sticks	O
?	O
?	O
What	O
about	O
foam	O
for	O
when	O
the	O
chorus	O
drops	O
?	O
?	O

Lol	O
"	O
@_malangkane	O
:	O
Lol	O
"	O
@MonicaSbahle	O
:	O
@_malangkane	O
@CiandaZuma	O
@AlvinBnkX	O
Yep	O
.	O
He	O
sings	O
and	O
makes	O
u	O
cry	O
.	O
Good	O
for	O
heartbreaks	O

@btsjhopey	O
kalo	O
di	O
gips	O
ngetiknya	O
susuah	O

@Chestar8	O
id	O
be	O
like	O
a	O
wedding	O
just	O
throw	O
a	O
beer	O
garden	O
over	O
there	O
and	O
we	O
are	O
good	O
.	O

PC	O
to	O
the	O
wonderful	O
acc	O
@TamyAlamo	O
!	O
She's	O
super	O
nice	O
,	O
and	O
surely	O
a	O
huge	O
Bullocker	O
!	O
Go	O
follow	O
her	O
!	O
http://t.co/FGAvn3UKaF	O

WMYT	B-organization
106	O
.	O
7	O
FM	O
Sam	B-person
Ibrahim	I-person
is	O
back	O
for	O
an	O
update	O
on	O
the	O
New	B-place
Hanover	I-place
County	O
GOp	O
and	O
the	O
primaries	O
http://t.co/nM3TMaD7sk	O

@BurdettRaelynn	O
hahahaha	O
heck	O
yes	O
I'll	O
start	O
the	O
series	O
tonight	O

RT	O
@kene_co	O
:	O
@mee169	O
&	O
gt	O
;	O
Yemi	B-person
Alade	I-person
-	O
Johnny	B-person
:	O
http://t.co/8tnn8gw2VZ	O
via	O
@YouTube	O

@jacobzimmer	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
made	O
it	O
to	O
your	O
show	O
on	O
time	O
.	O
^	O
CW	O

@ughhhkayla	O
THAT	O
IS	O
SO	O
CUTE	O
WHY	O
ARENT	O
YOU	O
DATING	O
LIKE	O
IM	O

@IRHAKAZMI	O
keep	O
ur	O
own	O
name	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O

buysellbitco	O
.	O
in	O
#bitcoin	O
price	O
in	O
INR	O
,	O
Buy	O
:	O
35839	O
.	O
00	O
INR	O
Sell	O
:	O
34694	O
.	O
00	O
INR	O
.	O
Buy	O
and	O
sell	O
bitcoin	O
in	O
#India	B-place
using	O
#buysellbitcoin	O

everybody	O
ready	O
to	O
throw	O
up	O
?	O

@deargoya_goya	O
@Frankie_Deee	O
@carinusa	O
@milena5774	O
@jetisky	O
@KankichiRyotsu	O
@estefany_saave	O
@BYU1368	O
Cold	O
as	O
a	O
witchs	O
'	O
tit	O
!	O
!	O
With	O
wind	O
.	O

@Luke5SOS	O
Hi	O
Luke	B-person
,	O
in	O
half	O
month	O
it's	O
my	O
birthday	O
14	O
and	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
like	O
before	O
that	O
date	O
?	O
please	O
follow	O
me	O
ily	O
:)	O
830	O

@b_bauchens	O
I'll	O
find	O
someone	O
else	O
.	O
lol	O

@rauhlmarie	O
what	O
omg	O
thank	O
you	O
love	O
aw	O

Quote	O
this	O
tweet	O
with	O
your	O
bestfriend	O
http://t.co/QnOh2EayF5	O

@rauhlolly	O
@strxtfordlegend	O
someone	O
said	O
that	O
but	O
i	O
mean	O
why	O
else	O

RT	O
@LowRentRadio1	O
:	O
Get	O
the	O
Latest	O
episode	O
of	O
#lrr	B-product
here	O
http://t.co/R7LhW2rfYx	O
#nowplaying	O
#Share	O
#Listen	O
#Like	O
#DoublewideNetwwork	B-organization

@M3rcury78	O
@PinkFlamingoGal	O
pahahaha	O
!	O
My	O
work	O
here	O
is	O
finished	O
*	O
saunters	O
off	O
to	O
sad	O
music	O
like	O
a	O
sad	O
,	O
yet	O
smug	O
and	O
sexy	O
Littlest	O
Hobo	O
*	O

@overdramaticmel	O
I	O
also	O
love	O
them	O
because	O
I	O
am	O
on	O
the	O
short	O
side	O
and	O
Levi's	B-organization
let	O
you	O
pick	O
inseam	O
lengths	O
.	O

Here's	O
an	O
idea	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
a	O
jeep	O
,	O
put	O
down	O
your	O
damn	O
phone	O
,	O
engage	O
4wd	O
and	O
go	O
around	O
me	O
.	O
I'm	O
not	O
moving	O
next	O
time	O
.	O

What	O
makes	O
it	O
a	O
secret	O
?	O
You're	O
afraid	O
of	O
the	O
consequences	O
of	O
letting	O
it	O
out	O
?	O
I	O
don't	O
have	O
any	O
secret	O
.	O
The	O
torture	O
is	O
what	O
I	O
can't	O
handle	O

ayy	O
@GlasscoSavanna	O
ope	O
ur	O
good	O
sis	O
.	O
Go	O
Enjoy	O
a	O
#BrandNewMusic	O
Video	O
#Watch	O
"	O
ALRIGHT	O
"	O
http://t.co/rE2NmrDztl	O
shot	O
by	O
@dopexboyfilms	O
RT	O

@Guns_N_Roses00	O
-	O
.	O
-	O
KABHI	O
BHI	O
NA	O
BAAT	O
MANA	O
KARO	O
MANHOOS	O
!	O
!	O
!	O

@alfitriadindya	O
Yuk	O
follow	O
-	O
-	O
-	O
&	O
gt	O
;	O
salma	B-person
&	O
amp	O
;	O
josia	B-person
ICIL	O
4	O
@Salma_Aliyyah	O
lg	O
@Josiasimanjunt	O
*	O
26	O

Life	O
is	O
about	O
competition	O
.	O
You	O
either	O
succeed	O
among	O
others	O
or	O
you	O
fall	O
beneath	O
.	O

You	O
can't	O
slut	O
-	O
shame	O
women	O
.	O
You	O
can't	O
fat	O
-	O
shame	O
women	O
.	O
But	O
you	O
can	O
"	O
hot	O
-	O
shame	O
"	O
them	O
for	O
being	O
physically	O
fit	O
?	O
http://t.co/IyL7OBp1g7	O

RT	O
@Icntbretaga	O
:	O
Wtf	O
did	O
I	O
just	O
watch	O
they're	O
so	O
weird	O
lol	O
https://t.co/UBrXbcX0dN	O

Getting	O
ready	O
for	O
#hoth	O
only	O
the	O
essentials	O
http://t.co/0mMHfkJMFj	O

I'm	O
Feeling	O
myself	O
.	O
.	O

Winter	O
Storm	O
Warning	O
for	O
Bennington	B-place
County	I-place
in	O
VT	B-place
until	O
11	O
:	O
00am	O
Thursday	O
.	O
http://t.co/TZimw0PHqN	O

This	O
is	O
a	O
fight	O
to	O
the	O
death	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
#ColombiaNeedsLLFDTour	O
@30SECONDSTOMARS	O

@larryhernandez1	O
Buenas	O
Tardes	O
!	O
!	O
saludoss	O
para	O
ti	O
y	O
tu	O
Familia	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
#ojalaquetevayamal	O

New	B-organization
York	I-organization
Knicks	I-organization
vs	O
.	O
Miami	B-organization
Heat	I-organization
:	O
Live	O
Score	O
and	O
Analysis	O
http://t.co/S0cRc9Uqhy	O

Falta	O
39	O
pessoas	O
e	O
eu	O
to	O
com	O
sonooo	O

N	B-organization
'	I-organization
Joy	I-organization
e	O
-	O
cig	O
ad	O
on	O
payphone	O
:	O
"	O
Making	O
cigarettes	O
as	O
obsolete	O
as	O
the	O
payphone	O
.	O
"	O
That's	O
like	O
a	O
tapeworm	O
calling	O
you	O
fat	O
from	O
inside	O
your	O
gut	O
.	O

"	O
@RuRuChristian	O
:	O
Grabe	O
talaga	O
si	O
@iamjomi	O
!	O
LOL	O
"	O
-	O
ako	O
pa	O
talaga	O
?	O
!	O
Haha	O
bilis	O
nyo	O
natapos	O
ah	O
.	O
Bumalik	O
pa	O
sya	O
eh	O
.	O
LOL	O

Saya	O
beda	O
dengan	O
mantan	O
anda	O
:)	O
tolong	O
jangan	O
disama2kan	O
;	O
)	O

Wtf	O
is	O
happening	O
smh	O

@HighOnJessie	O
That's	O
what	O
you	O
said	O
yesterday	O
;	O
)	O
Haha	O
,	O
but	O
they'll	O
be	O
ready	O
for	O
when	O
the	O
chapter	O
is	O
up	O
;	O
P	O

@hellahelbig	O
@chestersee	O
i	O
just	O
sang	O
the	O
im	O
a	O
little	O
tea	O
pot	O
song	O

RT	O
@A_Hodges9	O
:	O
@NB3_ImAProblem	O
I	O
See	O
The	O
Boob	O
Job	O
.	O
IDK	O
Bout	O
Them	O
Gym	O
Hrs	O
.	O
Prolly	O
A	O
Lil	O
Fabricated	O
.	O

Bitchez	O
turn	O
lesbian	O
like	O
hoes	O
don't	O
cheat	O
too	O

24	O
radio	O
:	O
JG	B-person
says	O
because	O
Smoke	O
was	O
limping	O
around	O
,	O
pit	O
road	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
closed	O
.	O
Then	O
says	O
light	O
was	O
red	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
.	O

@BecketAdams	O
now	O
I	O
have	O
"	O
give	O
me	O
back	O
that	O
filet	O
o	O
fish	O
"	O
stuck	O
in	O
my	O
head	O
.	O

RT	O
@Oops_Shawdy	O
:	O
Fuck	O
the	O
police	O
!	O
With	O
out	O
that	O
badge	O
you	O
bitch	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
!	O

In	O
plastic	O
surgery	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
more	O
is	O
often	O
not	O
"	O
better	O
"	O
=	O
&	O
gt	O
;	O
http://t.co/bEfIr8ySgs	O

News5	O
Everywhere	O
-	O
MANAGER	O
NG	O
CEBU	O
PACIFIC	O
NA	O
NAMBASTOS	O
DIUMANO	O
SA	O
PASAHERO	O
,	O
PINARUSAHAN	O
NA	O
http://t.co/7N62bFlhzn	O

@susiekearley	O
and	O
I	O
add	O
people	O
to	O
my	O
lists	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
and	O
again	O
I	O
post	O
a	O
tweet	O
to	O
get	O
people	O
talking	O
and	O
intro	O
them	O
:)	O
0O	O
-	O

Same	O
RT	O
@Migquel	O
:	O
My	O
twitter	O
name	O
is	O
my	O
first	O
name	O
so	O
I'm	O
good	O

Lets	O
go	O
Sin	B-person
Cara	I-person
!	O
#RAW	O

Love	O
is	O
the	O
poetry	O
of	O
the	O
senses	O
.	O

Fr	O
@sekar_sningsih	O
lalin	O
dayeuhkolot	O
ramai	O
lancar	O
,	O
walaupun	O
tdk	O
banjir	O
ttp	O
hati2	O
tweeps	O
,	O
jalan	O
berlubang	O
parah	O

Vegas	B-place
WoO	O
Sprint	O
feature	O
FINISH	O
:	O
51	O
,	O
11	O
,	O
49	O
,	O
71M	O
,	O
15	O
,	O
9	O
,	O
24A	O
,	O
4	O
,	O
21M	O
,	O
83	O
,	O
11K	O
,	O
24	O
,	O
o5	O
,	O
21	O
,	O
82c	O
,	O
1	O
,	O
29	O
,	O
7s	O
,	O
41	O
,	O
77x	O
,	O
1s	O
,	O
82	O
,	O
33	O
,	O
9w	O

@itsroanpatrice	O
may	O
play	O
kami	O
kanina	O
sa	O
lit	O

Hihi	O
ngade	O
RT	O
@zeeraaBeckham	O
:	O
@lalita3duardo	O
ahahahaha	O
.	O
selalu	O
tgk	O
awk	O
tweet	O
.	O
sy	O
blajar	O
slow2	O
.	O
hehe	O
tq	O
teacher	O
ekekeke	O

Thank	O
fuck	O
Howard	B-person
Webb	I-person
isn't	O
the	O
ref	O
against	O
the	O
mancs	O
!	O

#JobSearch	O
Club	O
Lounge	O
Attendant	O
-	O
Wyndham	B-organization
Pittsburgh	O
University	O
Center	O
Part	O
-	O
time	O
at	O
Wyndham	B-place
.	O
.	O
.	O
Find	O
this	O
Job	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
More	O
http://t.co/GfKK3G6kug	O

Ser	B-person
Gemelier	I-person
es	O
pasarte	O
el	O
dia	O
escribiendo	O
sus	O
nombres	O
.	O

Climbed	O
up	O
this	O
way	O
cause	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
to	O
do	O
:P	O
#Livestrong	O
#photography	O
http://t.co/rfeUuodG9M	O

@FleurdeB	O
@socialwebcafe	O
What	O
is	O
GaggleAmp	B-organization
?	O
Hi	O
@FleurdeB	O
!	O

@CloseupPH	O
#CloseupForeverSummer	O
!	O
232	O

I	O
have	O
1	O
,	O
000	O
followers	O
!	O
#thankyou	O

RT	O
@LoveCass_	O
:	O
#ontopictalkshow	B-product
why	O
you	O
comparing	O
it	O
to	O
other	O
crimes	O
.	O
:	O
-	O
/	O

Where	O
the	O
bad	O
bitches	O
?	O
Where	O
u	O
hiding	O
?	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
power	O
to	O
make	O
your	O
life	O
so	O
exciting	O
.	O

RT	O
@Cytryny_33	O
:	O
Mocno	O
powiedziane	O
jak	O
na	O
takiego	O
frajera	O
!	O

nothing	O
makes	O
me	O
feel	O
more	O
appreciated	O
then	O
when	O
someone	O
stays	O
on	O
your	O
messages	O
and	O
reads	O
them	O
the	O
second	O
you	O
send	O
it	O

@CandyMora	O
besotes	O
.	O
.	O
Cuidate	O
.	O
.	O

RT	O
@PivotCEO	O
:	O
@OhMyJet	O
@runtrimom	O
@healbe	O
@runnermommy2008	O
WOW	O
!	O
That's	O
a	O
fun	O
way	O
to	O
start	O
a	O
Friday	B-other
.	O
#TGIF	O
#Kindness	O
#support	O

@wantderek	O
larguei	O
no	O
vacuo	O
pra	O
que	O
se	O
estressar	O

RT	O
@camlovescam	O
:	O
"	O
That	O
tweet	O
wasn't	O
funny	O
"	O
https://t.co/TEEsIrZsGx	O

@dreams_ofyou	O
And	O
thank	O
you	O
!	O
Enjoy	O
your	O
day	O
as	O
well	O
.	O
:)	O

:(	O
"	O
@ClairvoyantTzar	O
:	O
Lmaooooooo	O
.	O
Awwww	O
.	O
:	O
'	O
)	O
RT	O
@aywizkid	O
:	O
How	O
would	O
u	O
tell	O
me	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
to	O
watch	O
Fanzone	B-product
!	O
?	O
How	O
"	O

@LInfAlab	O
certo	O
che	O
no	O
ma	O
nn	O
confondiamo	O
:	O
giudice	O
persegue	O
e	O
sanziona	O
violazioni	O
prescrizioni	O
#aia	O
@SPViaDalCarbone	O
@AIA_info	O
@Borrelli_Gio	O

@missrxe	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
?	O
I	O
sent	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
post	O
?	O

khusus	O
cewe	O
RT	O
@Toriiza	O
:	O
@viganunu	O
sagi	O
ga	O
dpt	O
iklan	O
yg	O
barusan	O
yah	O
mang	O
?	O
Brightupyourday	O
?	O
:	O
'	O
)	O

Sooo	O
much	O
laundry	O
to	O
do	O
at	O
work	O
.	O
I	O
probably	O
spend	O
more	O
time	O
doing	O
laundry	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
folding	O
than	O
I	O
do	O
massaging	O
.	O
I	O
swear	O
lol	O
.	O

RT	O
@bevismusson	O
:	O
Callum	B-person
in	O
his	O
There's	B-product
A	I-product
Shark	I-product
In	I-product
The	I-product
Bath	I-product
hoodie	O
for	O
#WorldBookDay	B-other
@jabberworks	O
http://t.co/IXxUYXXTRa	O

BRUH	O
WHAT	O
THE	O
FUCK	O
IS	O
THIS	O
SHIT	O
http://t.co/DZiiIYh382	O

RT	O
@LastSpanishKing	O
:	O
@FluffyBooty94	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
coolest	O
girl	O
on	O
twitter	O

One	O
hour	O
and	O
i	O
finally	O
go	O
home	O
yay	O
\	O
o	O
/	O

Today	O
in	O
1911	O
,	O
the	O
Triangle	B-other
Shirtwaist	I-other
Fire	I-other
http://t.co/c7wwAsvwHj	O

Slimin	O
and	O
fartfunkle	O
@midnight	O
#FilthyCelebrities	O

@N4NA_	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
,	O
how	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
home	O
?	O
I'm	O
good	O
thanks	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
grace	O
of	O
God	O
fully	O
.	O

@JackJackJohnson	O
JACK	B-person
PLEASE	O
FOLLOW	O
ME	O
IM	O
NOT	O
AT	O
MAGCON	O
RIGHT	O
NOW	O
SO	O
I	O
CANT	O
TAKE	O
CUTE	O
PICTURES	O
WITH	O
YOU	O
FML	O
BUT	O
PLEASE	O
FOLLOW	O
ME	O
ILYSM	O
x21	O

escovando	O
os	O
dente	O
e	O
ouvindo	O
guy	O

RT	O
@EspinosaIsDaBae	O
:	O
@jesskian	O
a	O
perfect	O
human	O
being	O

Pakistan	B-place
Day	O
Hai	O
We'll	O
win	O

RT	O
@Younggee	O
:	O
#TopShelfOPENBAR	O
|	O
Tonight	O
|	O
@One17SofaBar	O
|	O
ALL	O
drinks	O
FREE	O
(	O
11	O
-	O
12	O
:	O
30	O
)	O
|	O
RSVP	O
http://t.co/p6hPqKU2Dg	O
|	O
http://t.co/gxMzNc2b8a	O

@DARKMIST_NINJA	O
bro	O
I'm	O
fucking	O
telling	O
you	O
man	O
the	O
nggers	O
Finna	O
catch	O
on	O
lmao	O
and	O
they	O
fuck	O
everything	O
up	O

RT	O
@_MorgAngelOFC	O
:	O
Emang	O
sih	O
,	O
cast	O
couple	O
di	O
film2	O
itu	O
banyak	O
banget	O
.	O
tp	O
yang	O
nemuin	O
kayak	O
ALBIN	O
itu	O
susah	O
,	O
yang	O
berhasil	O
bgt	O
bikin	O
org	O
ngefly	O
.	O
.	O

@chocophilenyc	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
many	O
KitKat	B-product
flags	O
can	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
Chinatown	B-place
and	O
such	O
here	O

Why	O
my	O
supervisor	O
over	O
here	O
sleep	O
lookin	O
like	O
Sup	O
from	O
the	O
PJ's	O

Are	O
we	O
the	O
dining	O
dead	O

@thomaselgenberg	O
Oh	O
yes	O
that	O
looks	O
good	O
Thomas	O
.	O
I'd	O
love	O
some	O
of	O
that	O
right	O
now	O

@IamKeiMante	O
I	O
followed	O
you	O
love	O
!	O

"	O
@PEPATAHKU	O
:	O
gampang	O
senyum	O
oke	O
,	O
gampang	O
menolong	O
bagus	O
,	O
tapi	O
gampang	O
jatuh	O
cinta	O
jangan	O
,	O
apalagi	O
gampang	O
ngarep	O
"	O

RT	O
@ELYARTIFUL	O
:	O
"	O
@ElyarFox	O
:	O
Life	O
rule	O
:	O
never	O
make	O
your	O
morning	O
alarm	O
a	O
song	O
you	O
love	O
"	O
#kca	O
#VoteElyarUK	O

Kronologi	O
kejadian	O
kasus	O
pembunuhan	O
yg	O
di	O
bekasi	O
kok	O
mirip	O
kek	O
video	O
clip	O
nye	O
pixies	O
deh	O
?	O
.	O
.	O
Coincidence	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/kqvplwdO7S	O

So	O
don't	O
let	O
'	O
em	O
jack	O
you	O
up	O
,	O
back	O
you	O
up	O
,	O
crack	O
you	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
pimp	O
smack	O
you	O
up	O
Ya	O
gotta	O
learn	O
to	O
hold	O
ya	O
own	O

RT	O
@annamarieee	O
:	O
@TIHCfest	O
oh	O
my	O
god	O
.	O
I	O
officially	O
love	O
TIH	O
more	O
than	O
life	O
.	O

WHRE	O
ID	O
THIS	O
PICTURE	O
OF	O
NAKED	O
HARRY	B-person

RT	O
@nycsouthpaw	O
:	O
New	O
record	O
.	O
Hrmph	O
.	O
http://t.co/RQ6LKE2chn	O

RT	O
@WorldCupTourny	O
:	O
ALL	O
GROUP	O
GAMES	O
MUST	O
BE	O
PLAYED	O
BEFORE	O
12AM	O
TOMORROW	O
IF	O
NOT	O
THEN	O
YOU	O
GET	O
A	O
1	O
-	O
1	O
DRAW	O

Vote	O
for	O
Houston	B-place
chefs	O
in	O
Food	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
Wine	O
magazine	O
poll	O
http://t.co/J21BPf7fTg	O

RT	O
@Oh_thats_Shan	O
:	O
My	O
b	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
h	O
think	O
she	O
so	O
cute	O
,	O
that's	O
my	O
lil	O
boo	O

+	O
That	O
image	O
of	O
a	O
stick	O
ramming	O
into	O
that	O
bread	O
,	O
the	O
bread	O
tearing	O
apart	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
see	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
9	O
month	O
old	O
vagina	O
tearing	O
apart	O
in	O
that	O
scene	O

RT	O
@jurimoli	O
:	O
nunca	O
tive	O
tanto	O
sono	O
na	O
vida	O

@bizzo509	O
@gbirdbaby203	O
.	O
well	O
lets	O
not	O
indulge	O
in	O
it	O
bizzo	O
.	O
fuck	O
it	O
-	O
next	O
subject	O
lol	O
im	O
over	O
this	O

@AndrewCieslak	O
I	O
like	O
when	O
he	O
gets	O
so	O
pissed	O
off	O
he	O
swears	O
.	O
And	O
his	O
stories	O
about	O
being	O
a	O
GM	O
are	O
fascinating	O
.	O
He's	O
plenty	O
lucid	O
.	O

RT	O
@justiceputnam	O
:	O
@BillinPortland	O
He	O
had	O
no	O
prob	O
with	O
being	O
made	O
a	O
manager	O
like	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
us	O
are	O
.	O

@danielle8D	O
lovely	O
isn't	O
it	O
hahha	O

last	O
one	O
for	O
the	O
night	O
!	O
SUGAR	O
SHACK	O
!	O
http://t.co/LqRcsfA9Fp	O

@Kazsteph	O
Probably	O
a	O
service	O
issue	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
tweet	O
@cleanandgreentweet	O
or	O
contact	O
them	O
here	O
http://t.co/XBg2ZkdF8g	O
although	O
not	O
in	O
til	O
Monday	O

@gxmezdreams	O
hmm	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
I'd	O
say	O
gxmezdreams	O
tbh	O
.	O
.	O

@HowRood	O
nigga	O
prolly	O
didn't	O
say	O
anything	O
after	O
lol	O

Bitches	O
nowadays	O
get	O
so	O
easily	O
influenced	O
by	O
celebrities	O
,	O
now	O
if	O
Rihanna	B-person
and	O
Beyonce	B-person
were	O
to	O
act	O
like	O
hoes	O
.	O
All	O
would	O
follow	O

Paint	O
jobs	O
that	O
last	O
from	O
Cutting	B-organization
Edge	I-organization
Painting	I-organization
!	O
Get	O
a	O
free	O
upgrade	O
to	O
premium	O
paint	O
with	O
this	O
coupon	O
http://t.co/G1Ap9uHVq0	O

@ObservantLynn	O
Yeah	O
,	O
tastes	O
gross	O
,	O
but	O
very	O
high	O
in	O
iron	O
.	O
My	O
blood	O
levels	O
come	O
up	O
a	O
bit	O
then	O
drop	O
each	O
time	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
menstrual	O
cycle	O
.	O
:	O
/	O

For	O
those	O
who	O
feel	O
that	O
Bryce	B-person
Harper	I-person
is	O
overrated	O
.	O
A	O
poll	O
taken	O
by	O
S	B-organization
.	I-organization
I	I-organization
of	O
over	O
400	O
MLB	O
Players	O
rated	O
Derek	B-person
Jeter	I-person
baseball's	O
most	O
overrated	O

did	O
juliana	B-person
submit	O
this	O
?	O
http://t.co/LbH5TxFMGH	O

Really	O
want	O
to	O
be	O
best	O
friends	O
with	O
Dan	B-person
and	O
Phil	B-person

i've	O
seen	O
over	O
fifty	O
trailer	O
parks	O
and	O
churches	O
since	O
i	O
got	O
here	O

Es	O
cierto	O
que	O
golpearon	O
a	O
@MariaCorinaYA	O
en	O
el	O
aeropuerto	O
?	O
@AnonymousVene10	O
@VOZ_URBE	O
-	O
@YuleMorillo2892	O

Dicoba	O
dumss	O
tlist	O
:	O
"	O
http://t.co/QeLLeCwuZk	O

@lola32	O
cool	O
maybe	O
I	O
shall	O
see	O
ya	O
there	O

RT	O
@WMGallery	O
:	O
Our	O
#FirstTweet	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
https://t.co/dwHxxtEGKz	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
yours	O
?	O

RT	O
@patrickmckenna	O
:	O
Bedeque	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
#krafthockeyville	O

Spend	O
them	O
bandssss	O
on	O
them	O
drugs	O

RSC	B-organization
partners	O
with	O
Opus	B-organization
Arte	I-organization
for	O
DVD	O
releases	O
"	O
Richard	B-product
II	I-product
"	O
http://t.co/OGGknZyzV2	O
I	O
think	O
I've	O
got	O
your	O
bday	O
present	O
sorted	O
@becky_feezell	O

@gavinmcgarry	O
I	O
just	O
read	O
your	O
country	O
aircheck	O
interview	O
,	O
and	O
fully	O
agree	O
on	O
expanding	O
country	O
radio	O
globally	O
!	O
-	O
Country	O
fan	O
from	O
Singapore	B-place
!	O

I	O
want	O
to	O
taste	O
alcohol	O
through	O
your	O
mouth	O
.	O

@pjlove10	O
who	O
does	O
that	O
?	O
I	O
don't	O
do	O
that	O
.	O
That's	O
weird	O
!	O

#Pawtucket	O
,	O
RI	O
teacher	O
allegedly	O
assaults	O
student	O
for	O
eating	O
cookie	O
:	O
http://t.co/iOnLxDH31z	O

@Nashgrier	O
ROSES	O
ARE	O
RED	O
,	O
YOUR	O
EYES	O
ARE	O
BLUE	O
,	O
SUGAR	O
IS	O
SWEET	O
AND	O
IF	O
YOU'RE	O
ON	O
TWITTER	O
GIVE	O
ME	O
A	O
TWEET	O
OR	O
A	O
FOLLOW	O
.	O
WOW	O
Im	O
such	O
good	O
.	O
or	O
nah	O

@ValMackinnon	O
@TownofCarbonear	O
Thank	O
you	O
Val	B-person
.	O
Started	O
with	O
14	O
beds	O
and	O
now	O
we	O
have	O
36	O
!	O
Great	O
community	O
effort	O
with	O
all	O
ages	O
participating	O
.	O

RT	O
@fidofinder	O
:	O
Found	O
dog	O
in	O
O	B-place
Fallon	I-place
,	I-place
IL	I-place
US	I-place
(	O
62269	O
)	O
http://t.co/uuZv2iKooC	O
#founddog	O

Car	O
Rental	O
Safety	O
Tips	O
http://t.co/ePIXQKVz46	O
#CarRental	O
#TravelSafety	O

I	O
contradicted	O
myself	O
I	O
know	O

Evergreen	O
1A	O
boys	O
soccer	O
:	O
Hoquiam	O
1	O
-	O
0	O
Montesano	O
(	O
halftime	O
)	O
Alex	B-person
PugaDeLaRosa	I-person
23	O
'	O
goal	O
for	O
Hoquiam	O
.	O
Sea	O
Breeze	O
Oval	O
living	O
up	O
to	O
its	O
name	O
.	O

@kyysongz	O
i	O
def	O
should	O
have	O
i	O
need	O
to	O
download	O
more	O
music	O
lol	O
i	O
feel	O
like	O
be	O
listing	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
shit	O
lbs	O

RT	O
@Tivzzy	O
:	O
goddamnit	O
my	O
parents	O
are	O
fucking	O

CMW	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
some	O
discomfort	O
.	O
Asks	O
Kavanagh	B-person
for	O
a	O
couple	O
more	O
minutes	O
to	O
run	O
it	O
off	O

@OPPOIndonesia	O
hp	O
oppo	O
emg	O
keren	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
yakin	O
bakal	O
jd	O
smartphone	O
no	O
1	O
di	O
indonesia	B-place
,	O
,	O
,	O
,	O
,	O
#oppofindmuse	O
http://t.co/5nz3GrwNhj	O

@luluharris95	O
@_Victoria_Queen	O
I	O
expect	O
the	O
staff	O
@EHOsborneHouse	O
will	O
have	O
restored	O
it	O
in	O
keeping	O
with	O
its	O
original	O
styling	O
.	O
Prince	B-person
A	O
.	O

1	O
-	O
0	O
VILLA	B-person
!	O
good	O
free	O
kick	O
!	O

Ayok	O
temu	O
iii	O
@salikaakmaliyah	O
@vaniiagunawan	O
@italarasati	O
@wulanhermaya	O
sabtu	O
minggu	O
ini	O
free	O
gak	O
?	O

RT	O
@ObeyPatrial	O
:	O
@Clxtch	O
@lncog	O
@SBStratus_	O
nah	O
not	O
zenith	O
:	O
3	O

@OWNTV	O
shocking	O
still	O
how	O
easy	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
become	O
#Addict	O
sad	O
to	O
know	O
its	O
something	O
they	O
have	O
to	O
fight	O
to	O
stay	O
sober	O
everyday	O
#oprahprime	B-product

Sifting	O
through	O
my	O
experiences	O
,	O
I've	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
memories	O
that	O
are	O
most	O
precious	O
to	O
me	O
are	O
those	O
that	O
bloomed	O
from	O
the	O
heart	O
.	O

Punishhhh	O
me	O
pleaseeeee	O

Bitcoin	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
currency	O
.	O
Bitcoin	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
currency	O
.	O
Bitcoin	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
currency	O
.	O
Bitcoin	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
currency	O
.	O

UN	B-organization
:	O
North	B-place
Korea	I-place
evading	O
sanctions	O
via	O
@AJAM	O
http://t.co/sNbbqLkkQO	O

Love	O
hugs	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
kisses	O
2all	O
my	O
tweeps	O
!	O
Nite	O

I	O
.	O
don't	O
.	O
give	O
.	O
a	O
.	O
fuck	O
.	O

Should	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
school	O
orrrrr	O

RT	O
@SZN97	O
:	O
@aakashbhatt97	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
movie	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
bit	O
overrated	O
too	O

Any	O
Bay	O
Area	O
film	O
photographers	O
recommend	O
a	O
good	O
developer	O
/	O
scanner	O
?	O
have	O
120	O
film	O
need	O
done	O
.	O
#photography	O
#film	O
#SanFrancisco	B-place
#thanks	O
PLS	O
RT	O

@stratosathens	O
@journodave	O
Euro	O
designs	O
varied	O
further	O
as	O
member	O
state	O
identifiers	O
but	O
also	O
additional	O
security	O
from	O
counterfeiters	O

Jeanne	B-person
Kenney	I-person
a	O
quick	O
release	O
3	O
gives	O
#LSU	B-organization
Lady	I-organization
Tigers	I-organization
biggest	O
lead	O
,	O
39	O
-	O
29	O
,	O
18	O
:	O
57	O
left	O
.	O

Dwight	B-person
Howard	I-person
topples	O
LeBron	B-person
with	O
strike	O
to	O
the	O
nose	O
http://t.co/1apgCEqyC0	O

@iBurhan26	O
mere	O
matter	O
mein	O
,	O
woh	O
kyun	O
?	O
?	O
:P	O

Morsi	B-person
supporters	O
sentenced	O
to	O
death	O
http://t.co/IaCsKilBZL	O

@RickieBelfield	O
@EdwardOwenB	O
for	O
me	O
Costcutter	O
=	O
Londis	O

Good	O
evening	O
~	O
hahaha	O
http://t.co/SmOo3rIaTa	O

RT	O
@ArtDeity	O
:	O
@iamyaokhari	O
hello	O
!	O
Thanks	O
.	O
Hope	O
I	O
don't	O
disappoint	O
.	O

RT	O
@ISRealTalk	O
:	O
Mufuckas	O
Never	O
Loved	O
Us	O
#BullsNation	O

Am	O
I	O
ready	O
for	O
more	O
snow	O
yet	O
?	O
no	O
no	O
no	O
no	O
no	O
no	O
\	O
_	O
no	O
no	O
no	O
no	O
no	O
no	O

@GlossandPumps	O
It's	O
the	O
best	O
!	O
I'm	O
super	O
sad	O
I	O
keep	O
missing	O
your	O
stunning	O
face	O
when	O
you're	O
here	O
though	O
!	O
xoxo	O
!	O

Jose	B-person
Mourinho	I-person
is	O
just	O
stubborn	O
lol	O

@akashbanerjee	O
I	O
think	O
not	O
vanvaas	O
but	O
sanyaas	O
;	O
-	O
)	O
@digvijaya_28	O
@sardesairajdeep	O

One	O
love	O
.	O
One	O
Flanno	O
.	O
http://t.co/2wdaTBEb1L	O

Do	O
it	O
now	O
,	O
today	O
will	O
be	O
yesterday	O
tomorrow	O

@kimpoyfeliciano	O
Kuyaa	O
!	O
Followback	O
?	O
:(	O
:)	O
)	O
)	O
)	O
#KimpoyJammingWithSpongeCola	O
51	O

@BigJimSports	O
Here's	O
how	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
could	O
happen	O
:	O
http://t.co/Be90wDGXFI	O

@bempsiunisba	O
makasih	O
ya	O
ka	O
,	O
kalo	O
boleh	O
tau	O
ini	O
no	O
nya	O
atas	O
nama	O
siapa	O
ya	O
ka	O
?	O

@TylerToProm	O
hope	O
u	O
like	O
the	O
edit	O
I	O
made	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
3	O
http://t.co/X4QRxqDlFc	O

@thati_swisss	O
please	O
follow	O
baq	O
:	O
/	O
'	O

This	O
is	O
fact	O
RT	O
@ShazSkye	O
:	O
Agreed	O
.	O
RT	O
"	O
@Tokyo_Trev	O
Rock	O
concerts	O
&	O
gt	O
;	O
Rap	O
concerts	O
"	O

throwback	O
to	O
the	O
times	O
where	O
i	O
was	O
obsessed	O
w	O
the	B-product
vampire	I-product
diaries	I-product
http://t.co/gEAlqrdjxw	O

RT	O
@JoseRomero_	O
:	O
Soy	O
joaquin	O
guzman	O
el	O
chapo	O
.	O

@BexandMic	O
oh	O
sorry	O
Hun	O
that's	O
a	O
Shame	O
.	O
Are	O
the	O
squats	O
helping	O
?	O
I'm	O
sure	O
I	O
read	O
that	O
in	O
your	O
blog	O
?	O
xx	O

@PrimasBoy	O
@CNGiacoletti	O
hahahahha	O
wouldn't	O
want	O
it	O
any	O
other	O
way	O

@jacobperry	O
@hboulware	O
She	O
is	O
just	O
taking	O
a	O
break	O
.	O

osnapitz	O
_	O
nouis	O
/	O
/	O
YOUR	O
ACCOUNT	O
MATCHES	O
PERFECTLY	O
AW	O
:)	O
)	O
)	O
FABULOUS	O
ACCOUNT	O
BBY	O

I'm	O
hurt	O
just	O
thinking	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
we'll	O
work	O
through	O
it	O
.	O

Lord	O
please	O
bring	O
sleep	O
to	O
me	O
!	O
!	O

Cfare	O
ndodhi	O
ne	O
1997	O
!	O
Imazhe	O
tronditese	O
.	O
Rishikimi	O
i	O
nje	O
kohe	O
qe	O
tronditi	O
thellesisht	O
shoqerine	O
Shqiptare	O
.	O
Sot	O
,	O
21	O
.	O
00	O
dossier	O
ne	O
Opinion	O
!	O

@iAmTyraShanell	O
smile	O
young	O
lady	O
!	O
.	O
.	O
lol	O

@raye1447	O
told	O
ya	O
it	O
only	O
lasts	O
a	O
day	O
https://t.co/HQ5KlfdySE	O

Can	O
I	O
change	O
my	O
reg	O
name	O
back	O
to	O
h	O
and	O
m	O
I	O
don't	O
care	O
ppl	O
know	O
who	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
pce	O

#Fact	O
:	O
Agriculture	O
accounts	O
for	O
more	O
than	O
two	O
-	O
thirds	O
of	O
water	O
use	O
around	O
the	O
globe	O
.	O
http://t.co/7Az3ScZMyD	O

Just	O
reached	O
home	O
like	O
10	O
minutes	O
ago	O
.	O
.	O
_	O
.	O

Coach	O
19282	O
Signature	O
Stripe	O
Stitch	O
Patent	O
Convertible	O
Hobo	O
Tote	O
Handbag	O
$	O
368	O
http://t.co/YzAJseF9D6	O

What	O
the	O
fuck	O
is	O
ouat	O

@Skyler_Caylen	O
lol	O
don't	O
gang	O
up	O
on	O
me	O
everyone's	O
talking	O
shit	O

@RicoShades	O
Shit	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
a	O
lot	O
brother	O
man	O

Someone	O
is	O
always	O
watching	O
your	O
progress	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
or	O
not	O
.	O

RT	O
@kymgoodell	O
:	O
@toshi_lol	O
@ShelleyDTerrell	O
@PacificCove	O
@CBPratt	O
@StevenKohlhagen	O
@wpkofficial	O
.	O
Right	O
back	O
at	O
cha	O
?	O
;	O
)	O

I'm	O
getting	O
so	O
excited	O
about	O
this	O
.	O
If	O
it	O
actually	O
happens	O
.	O
It	O
would	O
be	O
SO	O
romantic	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
beautiful	O
a	O
perfect	O
reunion	O
https://t.co/41DKz7b4Xw	O

2014	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
2015	O
Ford	B-product
Mustang	I-product
Cobra	I-product
Super	O
Car	O
at	O
Need	B-product
For	I-product
Speed	I-product
Premiere	O
in	O
Hollywood	B-place
03062014	O
:	O
http://t.co/qFyLSd1mVl	O
via	O
@YouTube	O

@kLchamp	O
oh	O
yes	O
.	O
Don't	O
you	O
worry	O
.	O

Vice	O
pleaseee	O
#LadySpikersForGGV	O
@vicegandako	O

RT	O
@Jonathan_Bown	O
:	O
Had	O
it	O
,	O
lost	O
it	O
,	O
got	O
it	O
back	O
.	O
Eight	O
magnificent	O
man	O
-	O
overs	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/IB7AKPbCCP	O

It's	O
another	O
thing	O
entirely	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
by	O
violently	O
trying	O
to	O
eliminate	O
another	O
race	O
why	O
crying	O
that	O
you're	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
privileged	O
class	O
.	O

@MissCharleyWebb	O
please	O
follow	O
me	O
would	O
mean	O
the	O
world	O
to	O
me	O
xxxx	O

@lynzway	O
i	O
know	O
a	O
BUNCH	O
of	O
people	O
would	O
love	O
Brooklyn	B-place
Hype	I-place
buuuut	O
don't	O
think	O
it's	O
a	O
runner	O
.	O
London	B-place
Bridge	I-place
would	O
be	O
sweet	O
in	O
my	O
opinion	O

vai	O
demorar	O
mt	O
pra	O
de	O
noite	O
?	O

when	O
luke	B-person
says	O
they	O
are	O
a	O
serious	O
band	O
i	O
just	O
laugh	O
because	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
way	O
they	O
are	O
serious	O
i	O
mean	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
one	O
wearing	O
a	O
tutu	O

Is	O
there	O
such	O
thing	O
as	O
gold	O
bits	O
vodka	O
wankers	O
cause	O
there	O
piss	O
me	O
off	O
more	O
than	O
grey	O
goose	O
wankers	O

RT	O
@ItzMzTru2U	O
:	O
@REAL_BULLY	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
@FREDTHEGODSON	O
at	O
the	O
event	O
#TheWeekendShow	O
ladies	O
attended	O
in	O
CT	O
Friday	O
http://t.co/PymsZZppOf	O

RT	O
@duksr97	O
:	O
@CoachJimSaret	O
sino	O
susuko	O
?	O
Nakakatense	O
#BiggestLoserPH	O
#biggestloser	O

.	O
@TheTeditorial	O
FWIW	O
,	O
my	O
phone's	O
auto	O
correct	O
just	O
tried	O
to	O
change	O
WTF	O
to	O
TED	O
.	O

RT	O
@InsaneDumps	O
:	O
@CryptsyPumped	O
not	O
bad	O
at	O
all	O
sir	O

I	O
put	O
my	O
heart	O
into	O
this	O
school	O
.	O

@UKCoachCalipari	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
.	O
All	O
you	O
see	O
is	O
continuous	O
improvement	O
within	O
the	O
program	O
.	O
.	O
Let's	O
win	O
this	O
thing	O
#BBN	O

@Luke5SOS	O
hey	O
luke	B-person
:D	O
how're	O
you	O
?	O
please	O
follow	O
me	O
?	O
It	O
will	O
just	O
take	O
a	O
sec	O
.	O
love	O
you	O
lots	O
@Luke5SOS	O
x3	O
.	O
230	O

Would	O
be	O
so	O
awesome	O
if	O
Alex	B-person
and	O
@nickjonas	O
live	O
tweeted	O
the	O
HAWAII	B-product
FIVE	I-product
-	I-product
0	I-product
finale	O
!	O
@PLenkov	O
Hawaii	O
5	O
-	O
0	O
#H50	O

idk	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
w	O
/	O
my	O
life	O
now	O
.	O
should	O
i	O
go	O
back	O
to	O
studying	O
or	O
go	O
cook	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
#CardNation	O

@AaronBloomer	O
@DamnItKasey	O
wow	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
weirdest	O
mixture	O
of	O
ppl	O
on	O
my	O
TL	O
I've	O
ever	O
seen	O

John	B-person
Coleman	I-person
of	O
KUSI	O
:	O
How	O
the	O
#Global	O
#Warming	O
Scare	O
Began	O
:	O
http://t.co/MJTB3GM67m	O
via	O
@YouTube	O
#Truth	O

Bolanet	B-organization
:	O
Sherwood	B-person
Tantang	O
Soldado	B-person
Cetak	O
20	O
Gol	O
:	O
Manajer	O
Tottenham	B-organization
Tim	B-person
Sherwood	I-person
menantang	O
Roberto	B-person
Soldado	I-person
mence	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/mdnxNVEtDf	O

South	B-place
Korea	I-place
returns	O
remains	O
of	O
437	O
Chinese	O
soldiers	O
killed	O
during	O
the	O
Korean	O
War	O
to	O
China	B-place
for	O
final	O
burial	O
-	O
@AFP	O

@AustinHunsucker	O
@Jwhitleyradio	O
@sportguyshow	O
Me	O
neither	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
NAM	O
on	O
?	O
lol	O

#RickyChat	B-person
wish	O
me	O
luck	O
on	O
my	O
chem	O
retest	O
tommorw	O

RT	O
@hannahzappia	O
:	O
id	O
rather	O
someone	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
asshole	O
than	O
be	O
nice	O
and	O
lying	O

PYCKtradr	O
:	O
$NCGI	B-organization
New	O
China	O
Global	O
Inc	O
DD	O
NCGI	O
Company	O
De	O
http://t.co/4kOt3MGowV	O

@paynetrain__44	O
just	O
walk	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
hoe	O
$	O
be	O
like	O
what	O
dat	O
mouf	O
do	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
That's	O
what	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
1	O
/	O
10	O
success	O
rate	O

learning	O
to	O
value	O
my	O
own	O
sanity	O
over	O
a	O
lot	O
of	O
things	O
.	O

@DeniSastro	O
heart	O
attack	O
di	O
RS	O
Porong	O
.	O
Abis	O
acara	O
Tretes	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

@JeffeePalmer	O
Thank	O
you	O
!	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
blast	O
doing	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	B-person
Lamb	I-person
was	O
so	O
gracious	O
and	O
down	O
-	O
to	O
-	O
earth	O
.	O

You	O
do	O
not	O
have	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
learn	O
how	O
to	O
meditate	O
!	O
!	O
Many	O
free	O
sites	O
and	O
videos	O
exist	O
.	O
Just	O
quiet	O
your	O
mind	O
.	O
http://t.co/hAaogZO2hd	O

Looking	O
forward	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
Swimming	O
Gala	O
this	O
afternoon	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
competitive	O
!	O
Good	O
luck	O
to	O
all	O
swimmers	O
!	O

RT	O
@forevertemmie	O
:	O
@Gidi_Traffic	O
I	O
need	O
a	O
job	O
pls	O
help	O
!	O
I	O
have	O
completed	O
my	O
NYSC	B-organization
.	O
I	O
have	O
B	O
.	O
Sc	O
in	O
Sociology	O
.	O

Photo	O
:	O
#nanamica	B-organization
#love	O
http://t.co/nWduVDOB0n	O

@HollywoodChrisB	O
hi	O
Chris	B-person
!	O
We	O
make	O
trick	O
shots	O
on	O
YouTube	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
have	O
22	O
,	O
000	O
,	O
000	O
views	O
.	O
We	O
would	O
love	O
to	O
feature	O
your	O
music	O
in	O
a	O
vid	O
!	O
Interested	O
?	O

ha	O
!	O
RT	O
@tempodotco	O
:	O
Sebelum	B-person
Diusir	I-person
,	O
Prabowo	B-person
Menunggu	I-person
Hampir	I-person
Dua	I-person
Jam	I-person
&	O
amp	O
;	O
nbsp	O
;	O
http://t.co/AHVigKdRNj	O

"	O
harry	B-person
stuck	O
up	O
for	O
himself	O
"	O
"	O
sassy	O
harry	B-person
finally	O
happened	O
"	O
http://t.co/4kRs8PP533	O

@swagger_likeus	O
I'm	O
going	O
to	O
bash	O
this	O
phone	O
into	O
a	O
million	O
pieces	O
.	O

Congratulations	O
,	O
Meryl	B-person
Streep	I-person
!	O

@LittleMixOffic	O
please	O
follow	O
me	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
girls	O
xx	O
I'm	O
giving	O
up	O

Do	O
you	O
wanna	O
see	O
the	O
group	O
hug	O
?	O
#KCA	O
#Vote1DUK	O

@AnasTabarani	O
looooooool	O
Bismillah	O
I	O
didn't	O
even	O
know	O
she	O
knew	O
them	O
.	O
#STOPMYMUM2014	O
#TOOMUCHSOCIALISING	O

Both	O
of	O
these	O
teams	O
are	O
playing	O
like	O
they	O
want	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
heck	O
out	O
of	O
Greensboro	B-place
.	O
But	O
Wells	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
line	O
.	O

Taking	O
a	O
break	O
from	O
snarky	O
Oscar	O
comments	O
to	O
say	O
I	O
just	O
heard	O
Frisco	B-place
ISD	O
is	O
closed	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
Now	O
back	O
to	O
snark	O
.	O

@alydixon262	O
Thanks	O
Aly	B-person
that	O
would	O
be	O
great	O
.	O
Hope	O
your	O
Sunday	O
has	O
started	O
well	O
.	O

I	O
still	O
have	O
the	O
breadsticks	O
from	O
when	O
Karina	B-person
was	O
here	O
they	O
better	O
still	O
be	O
good	O
bc	O
I'm	O
not	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
dining	O
hall	O

@GreenEyedDyke	O
I've	O
always	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
big	O
talent	O
.	O

@astrogothwitch	O
Past	O
Chris	B-person
had	O
no	O
exit	O
strategy	O
and	O
now	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
pick	O
up	O
the	O
pieces	O
.	O

@Nankles300	O
hey	O
are	O
u	O
stil	O
interested	O
?	O

RT	O
@CenterThaRaptor	O
:	O
"	O
@MissCossa	O
:	O
Thank	O
You	O
Lord	O
Jesus	O
For	O
Yet	O
Another	O
Day	O
,	O
#Grateful	O
"	O

Answer	O
to	O
Kelston	B-place
Rd	I-place
closure	O
could	O
be	O
bypass	O
trackway	O
for	O
walkers	O
,	O
#cyclists	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
light	O
vehicles	O
,	O
obstacle	O
wouldn't	O
stop	O
military	O
Ops	O
!	O
@NOWBath	O

drink	O
,	O
eat	O
,	O
art	O
,	O
repeat	O

@LeeTassel	O
time	O
to	O
shake	O
it	O
off	O
and	O
ease	O
into	O
the	O
evening	O
!	O
:)	O

@feline_rouge	O
HORRIFIC	O
,	O
ISN'T	O
IT	O
.	O

@iamjkeating	O
@jillysciarilly	O
@scarilly	O
@Andy	O
25	O
going	O
on	O
12	O
#again	O
?	O

-	O
its	O
all	O
fun	O
and	O
games	O
,	O
until	O
somebody	O
get	O
they	O
ass	O
beat	O
.	O
.	O

Are	O
we	O
even	O
fan	O
accounts	O
anymore	O
we	O
tweet	O
more	O
about	O
our	O
personal	O
life's	O
lmao	O

@Linguagroover	O
there's	O
so	O
much	O
sadness	O
to	O
come	O
-	O
thats	O
a	O
small	O
place	O
and	O
everyone	O
will	O
be	O
affected	O
-	O
much	O
loss	O
in	O
this	O
event	O

Posle	O
odsustva	O
duzeg	O
od	O
godinu	O
dana	O
,	O
delegacija	O
Srbije	O
ponovo	O
u	O
Kongresu	O
lokalnih	O
i	O
regionalnih	O
vlasti	O
Saveta	O
Evrope	O
.	O
http://t.co/eTshFVedgS	O

@jaureuphoric	O
HER	O
ABS	O
KN	O
HNE	O
MKDSLE	O

RT	O
@Mfresh_raps	O
:	O
Happy	O
Birthday	O
to	O
the	O
Flam	B-person
-	I-person
ini	I-person
#strong	O
#dench	O
#proud	O
#appreciateit	O
http://t.co/C2M52Om4Vv	O

@P_O_W_	O
but	O
your	O
car	O
is	O
new	O

Team	O
arriving	O
at	O
the	O
stadium	O
#CCC	O
http://t.co/KKx7VpJsBm	O

RT	O
@JayLuke2	O
:	O
Otc	O
#ProjectSB2k14	O
got	O
me	O
hyped	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
Monday	O
not	O
even	O
here	O
yet	O

RT	O
@joacopiedrabuen	O
:	O
Afrojack	O
#Mtv	O
gogogo	O

Breakfast	O
eaten	O
.	O
Bags	O
packed	O
.	O
Rooms	O
tidied	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
now	O
for	O
some	O
last	O
activities	O
before	O
heading	O
home	O
.	O

Bout	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
some	O
mmmoonnnayyyy	O
#selfie	O
#work	O
#smile	O
#msdimples89	O
http://t.co/LKynMsbPpO	O

RT	O
@ANCALERTS	O
:	O
On	O
The	O
Money	O
:	O
How	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
right	O
investment	O
fund	O
for	O
you	O
http://t.co/jCx0hnbUt5	O

What	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
cruel	O
database	O
mistake	O
is	O
this	O
?	O
!	O
There's	O
no	O
way	O
this	O
is	O
real	O
,	O
sadly	O
.	O
http://t.co/mkKM0JA97L	O

Soldiers	O
in	O
the	O
4th	O
Brigade	O
Combat	O
Team	O
,	O
10th	O
Mountain	O
Division	O
based	O
at	O
Fort	B-place
Polk	I-place
returned	O
from	O
a	O
nearly	O
nine	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/GivHPPqOs5	O

RT	O
@SpotMeGirl	O
:	O
@daydayKnucks	O
if	O
she	O
can't	O
motivate	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
lost	O
cause	O
.	O
http://t.co/UTA5r9VaOO	O

Tolerancia	O
infinita	O
.	O

Among	O
David	B-person
Bowie's	I-person
many	O
attributes	O
was	O
that	O
you	O
could	O
quite	O
safely	O
look	O
up	O
his	O
nostrils	O
.	O
#geniusofDavidBowie	O

isnt	O
jia	B-person
friends	O
with	O
amber	B-person
?	O
?	O
the	O
fuck	O

It's	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
again	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
For	O
every	O
$	O
60	O
we	O
raise	O
this	O
week	O
,	O
we'll	O
be	O
giving	O
away	O
a	O
concert	O
ticket	O
AND	O
artist	O
merch	O
!	O
#BTPMarchMadness	O

New	O
Track	O
old	O
gxld	O
.	O
(	O
blow	O
up	O
the	O
world	O
)	O
http://t.co/kjmW4flnmB	O
on	O
#SoundCloud	O

it's	O
hard	O
to	O
describe	O
.	O
everyone	O
wants	O
to	O
be	O
alone	O
until	O
you're	O
alone	O
with	O
your	O
subconscious	O
.	O

RT	O
@KoolKlubK_	O
:	O
Of	O
Course	O
I	O
Got	O
Her	O
ALL	O
Dolled	O
UP	O
"	O
@ThatsChelseaa__	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
GiGi	B-person
look	O
cute	O
on	O
her	O
birthday	O
.	O
"	O

If	O
These	O
Niggas	O
don't	O
Stop	O
Tweeting	O
Bout	O
a	O
Goddamn	O
Allison	B-person
Ik	O
Something	O
.	O
She	O
Ain't	O
Real	O
Cuhh	O
!	O

km	O
kan	O
kgk	O
prnh	O
mnd	O
sist	O
hahahay	O
@TryzaMonica	O
@widyanisa79	O
@NewAkinanism94_	O
@yuli_nafisa	O
@CiciCerewett	O
@Akinanism94_	O

IM	O
DRUELING	O
ON	O
THE	O
SHIRT	O
I	O
WAS	O
GOING	O
TO	O
WEAR	O
TO	O
SCHOOL	O
TOMORROW	O
http://t.co/gToNDvJZfg	O

The	O
Brits	O
who	O
built	O
the	O
modern	O
world	O
http://t.co/IiXid6JSzo	O
#architecture	O

Spring	O
Detox	O
Yoga	O
Flow	O
|	O
Sequence	O
Inside	O
!	O
via	O
@YOGANONYMOUS	O
http://t.co/ZCKWqoBEKD	O

Tomorrow	O
I'm	O
starting	O
my	O
health	O
kick	O
also	O
handing	O
out	O
resumes	O
and	O
selling	O
stuff	O
on	O
eBay	B-organization
will	O
be	O
very	O
productive	O

Jared	B-person
Leto	I-person
is	O
a	O
beautiful	O
specimen	O
of	O
a	O
man	O

@hoIymiley	O
3	O
of	O
them	O
are	O
gone	O
:(	O
BUT	O
THANKSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSS	O

RT	O
@CoconutGlens	O
:	O
A	O
Big	O
Shout	O
-	O
Out	O
to	O
@peekaboophotos	O
for	O
sharing	O
your	O
family	O
experience	O
us	O
!	O
#CoconutGlensFamilyPhoto	O
http://t.co/63m4XpR88w	O

Something	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
come	O
to	O
realize	O
.	O

All	O
the	O
pretty	O
girls	O
getting	O
ready	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
.	O
yall	O
ugly	O
hoes	O
need	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
instead	O
of	O
tweeting	O
all	O
damn	O
night	O
.	O

@Paullopez76	O
@tarla_a	O
#justgotbrave	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
brave	O
shot	O
!	O

@TNBillP	O
I	O
really	O
like	O
Reggie	B-person
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
more	O
entertaining	O
players	O
I	O
saw	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
kick	O
his	O
feet	O
out	O
and	O
dive	O
.	O
Haha	O

Accs	O
going	O
on	O
private	O
ahoy	O

RT	O
@isabellablowme	O
:	O
I'm	O
allergic	O
to	O
all	O
men	O

@LowkeyLeak	O
@Kennydinkins	O
cmon	O
bruh	O
dont	O
act	O
like	O
yeen	O
a	O
tracklete	O

Senin	O
pagi	O
hujan	O
.	O
Yang	O
harus	O
beraktifitas	O
tabah	O
ya	O
.	O
Gue	O
lagi	O
di	O
atas	O
kasur	O
nih	O
.	O

Twetuje	O
na	O
majzy	O
w	O
autobusie	O
w	O
kiblu	O
#JustinMeetAnita	B-person

RT	O
@BradTheKing_	O
:	O
LOL	O
RT	O
@Jadelynnn_	O
:	O
pause	O
,	O
Gavin	B-person
Neva	I-person
seh	O
that	O
.	O

Everyone's	O
invited	O
tonight	O
to	O
#CFANorthLaredo	O
!	O
@MyLaredoTweeps	O
@VisitaLaredoTx	O
@Pro8News	O
@bigbuck98	O
@hot1061	O
http://t.co/GFJ1sizk7F	O

@burnleyfantom	O
Sounds	O
unreal	O
mate	O
,	O
proper	O
fancied	O
you's	O
today	O
like	O
pleased	O
you've	O
finally	O
broken	O
the	O
duck	O
!	O

Lmfaooo	O
RT	O
@lotyslove	O
:	O
Men	O
are	O
still	O
in	O
my	O
mentions	O
,	O
HOURS	O
later	O
,	O
mad	O
as	O
hell	O
because	O
I	O
said	O
tits	O
were	O
made	O
for	O
babies	O
.	O
Get	O
a	O
fucking	O
life	O
.	O

Vliegtuig	O
Malaysia	B-organization
Airlines	I-organization
maakte	O
mogelijk	O
rechtsomkeer	O
voor	O
verdwijning	O
http://t.co/OvFYRxP0nS	O
#vandaag_be	O

Ah	O
saya	O
galau	O
tapi	O
susah	O
ngungkapin	O
galau	O
ini	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

RT	O
@IamRajenash	O
:	O
"	O
Ayokong	O
tumanda	O
,	O
Ayokong	O
tumanda	O
,	O
Ayokong	O
tumanda	O
,	O
Ayokong	O
tumanda	O
kapag	O
di	O
ka	O
kasama	O
"	O
#NashAguasMOR	O

How	O
Venture	B-product
Capital	I-product
Helps	O
Drive	O
The	O
Startup	O
Economy	O
http://t.co/u0mHirjesj	O
#business	O
http://t.co/Zh8NbNZwHH	O

@LittleMix	O
if	O
u	O
see	O
this	O
please	O
make	O
my	O
day	O
and	O
follow	O
me	O
ilysm	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
33	O
:	O
)	O

@Havefaithiinme	O
WTF	O
YOU	O
HUNG	O
UP	O
ON	O
ME	O

The	O
Open	O
Beta	O
of	O
@XboxWarface	O
is	O
now	O
available	O
for	O
download	O
for	O
all	O
@Xbox	O
Live	O
Gold	O
members	O
.	O
Start	O
playing	O
today	O
!	O
http://t.co/UiLSkIfUsm	O

@INT0XICATEDLUKE	O
wow	O
that	O
was	O
really	O
lame	O
.	O

menino	O
abusado	O
DHOSIAHOIDHASHDOIASIODHAIOS	O
'	O

At	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
'	O
sode	O
,	O
his	O
sidekick	O
actually	O
goes	O
into	O
the	O
manger	O
,	O
but	O
Herc	B-person
hangs	O
back	O
and	O
is	O
like	O
"	O
naw	O
go	O
ahead	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
too	O
big	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
"	O

Beetje	O
reclame	O
maken	O
voor	O
rtl5	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
dit	O
wordt	O
een	O
beetje	O
teveel	O
#expeditierobinson	O
bij	O
#widm	O
voor	O
mij	O
#wieisdemol	O
#ned1	O

@hemmo_empire	O
no	O
not	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
mean	O
just	O
in	O
general	O
.	O

Absurd	O
.	O
Throw	O
it	O
away	O
"	O
@edrooney_	O
:	O
More	O
shrimp	O
.	O
@akaPRock	O
#EddiesCouplaPizzas	O
http://t.co/v20NuYJhWU	O
"	O

Soooo	O
fucking	O
rude	O
!	O
"	O
@natz0711	O
:	O
Seriously	O
?	O
Lmao	O
"	O
@KINGRobin_	O
:	O
Do	O
you	O
wash	O
your	O
face	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
ass	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
cloth	O
?	O
?	O
?	O
"	O
"	O

RT	O
@PennStateBASE	O
:	O
Anderson	B-person
gets	O
a	O
groundout	O
to	O
1st	O
and	O
PSU	B-organization
wins	O
9	O
-	O
6	O
!	O
!	O
!	O

@SophChezzabelle	O
werentfansthen	O
lal	O
alalalalalal	O

@D_Hardie	O
lo	O
sunah	O
rasul	O
gih	O
drpd	O
ngetwit	O

@MikeSigers	O
Hey	O
,	O
I'm	O
all	O
for	O
more	O
slots	O
on	O
the	O
shelf	O
!	O

Congrats	O
to	O
Mike's	B-person
Alma	O
Mater	O
CBC	O
Highschool	O
2014	O
State	O
Basketball	O
Champs	O
!	O
Pic	O
is	O
Mike's	B-person
1957	O
Prep	O
Player	O
of	O
Year	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/0I0Q4CcaB6	O

My	O
new	O
prescription	O
glasses	O
#Avi	O
#FourEyedLawyer	O
x	O
_	O
x	O

@L_MaryCrawley	O
to	O
you	O
Mary	B-person
,	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
scared	O
and	O
this	O
isn't	O
ideal	O
timing	O
but	O
I	O
couldn't	O
be	O
any	O
more	O
bloody	O
excited	O
unless	O
somebody	O
was	O
-	O
c	O
-	O

I	O
use	O
to	O
ask	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
lmai	O

to	O
explain	O
why	O
and	O
in	O
what	O
circumstances	O
people	O
make	O
decisions	O
under	O
uncertainty	O
.	O
Psychometric	O
theory	O
too	O
hard	O
for	O
most	O
orgs	O
.	O
2	O
/	O
2	O

Konferenca	O
DevopsDays	O
za	O
administratorje	O
in	O
razvijalce	O
http://t.co/zPnX4zynMP	O

Order	O
ko	O
sa	O
pizza	O
hut	O
:D	O
so	O
hungry	O
-	O
_	O
-	O
#hungry	O
#pizza	O
#PizzaHut	O
http://t.co/UVPcgXQDcd	O

RT	O
@EdPubTeachers	O
:	O
The	O
ATA	B-organization
shares	O
key	O
principles	O
for	O
curriculum	O
redesign	O
,	O
development	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
implementation	O
.	O
http://t.co/J52zCFmxBu	O

"	O
A	O
dream	O
is	O
what	O
you	O
desire	O
if	O
anything	O
and	O
everything	O
is	O
possible	O
.	O
"	O
-	O
#DreamBig	O

@loze4seddie	O
e	O
com	O
certeza	O
vai	O
ter	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
3	O
#VoteJennette	O
#KCA	O

RT	O
@Nilknarfh	O
Having	O
to	O
hold	O
mum's	O
hand	O
as	O
we	O
rounded	O
the	O
corner	O
upstairs	O
to	O
face	O
the	O
GIANT	O
ANTLERED	O
BEAST	O
!	O
She	O
was	O
petrified	O
of	O
it	O
:)	O

@BYEKatee	O
I	O
KNOW	O
OH	O
MY	O
GOD	O
I	O
LITERALLY	O
CANT	O
BREATHE	O

hipster	O
restaurants	O
and	O
delicious	O
milkshakes	O

@miund	O
punya	O
uang	O
,	O
passion	O
tinggalin	O
dulu	O
.	O
Nanti	O
kalo	O
urusan	O
idup	O
udah	O
tertata	O
jgn	O
lupain	O
passion	O
.	O
Biar	O
idup	O
kaya	O
neraca	O
akuntansi	O
,	O
seimbang	O

@huynas	O
HAHAHA	O
HOW	O
DID	O
WE	O
NOT	O
FIND	O
IT	O
YTD	O
THOUGH	O

Independent	O
females	O
deserve	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
And	O
to	O
get	O
their	O
booty	O
ate	O
.	O

GUY	O
VIDEO	O
IN	O
1	O
HOUR	O
30	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O

Setiap	O
upacara	O
biasanya	O
milih	O
barisan	O
yg	O
paling	O
depan	O
ada	O
yg	O
mau	O
dilihat	O
,	O
tp	O
upacara	O
besok	O
dibelakang	O
aja	O
soalny	O
yg	O
mau	O
dilihat	O
itu	O
ga	O
ada	O
~	O

why	O
give	O
up	O
the	O
whole	O
forest	O
for	O
a	O
plant	O
?	O

Patio	O
furniture	O
is	O
out	O
!	O
http://t.co/IbYfwCm4Z8	O

@Jorge_ParedesG	O
vas	O
a	O
dejar	O
que	O
tu	O
princesa	O
muera	O
de	O
hambre	O
?	O
:(	O

ZIALLBEYONCE	B-person
fuck	O
fuck	O
fuck	O
ur	O
icon	O

I'm	O
not	O
going	O
to	O
front	O
I	O
miss	O
@kasislike_	O
@MellyMell_O	O
@NikkiSiixx	O
#mygirls	O
#NikkiJoMazing	O

i	O
got	O
a	O
hangover	O
.	O
.	O
you	O
dont	O
have	O
that	O
problem	O
with	O
LOUD	O
!	O

Rochester	B-place
is	O
too	O
small	O
for	O
people	O
to	O
not	O
know	O
everybody	O
,	O
So	O
if	O
yu	O
aint	O
know	O
me	O
,	O
You	O
was	O
a	O
house	O
nigga	O
lol	O
cause	O
i	O
been	O
in	O
every	O
nigga	O
hood	O

Everyones	O
indirecting	O
you	O
now	O
u	O
happy	O
luke	O

Awwww	O
shit	O
I	O
knew	O
that	O
bitch	O
n	O
wade	O
a	O
come	O
bck	O
one	O
day	O

Is	O
it	O
wrong	O
that	O
as	O
I	O
go	O
through	O
this	O
girls	O
pictures	O
I'm	O
just	O
like	O
"	O
you	O
need	O
a	O
nose	O
job	O
,	O
nose	O
job	O
,	O
nose	O
job	O
"	O
lololol	O

@GirlUp	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
will	O
follow	O
me	O
:)	O

God	O
keeps	O
me	O
going	O
Prayer	O
keeps	O
me	O
humble	O
Life	O
keeps	O
me	O
thankful	O
People	O
keeps	O
me	O
loving	O

@Special_Asim	O
:D	O
Waisay	O
CONGRAATSS	O
:P	O
