@thomaselgenberg	O
Oh	O
yes	O
that	O
looks	O
good	O
Thomas	O
.	O
I'd	O
love	O
some	O
of	O
that	O
right	O
now	O

Hell	O
NAWWW	O
!	O
Smellin	O
like	O
hot	O
ass	O
-	O
for	O
real	O
tho	O
!	O
RT	O
@LAFLIPPERS	O
:	O
@helluvannette	O
yea	O
can't	O
have	O
no	O
shitty	O
gummy	O
worms	O
lol	O

@martinslahey	O
i'm	O
1000000	O
%	O
sure	O
you	O
still	O
look	O
so	O
much	O
better	O
than	O
i	O
do	O
so	O
next	O
time	O
you	O
should	O
just	O
reply	O
okay	O
omg	O

@Ririsel	O
tgal	O
4	O
Juni	O
2014	O
:)	O

And	O
MadBum	B-person
looks	O
even	O
readier	O
for	O
the	O
season	O
.	O

@CameronDallas	O
CAAAAAM	O
FOLLOW	O
MEEEEEEEEEE	O
I	O
LOVE	O
YOU	O
XO	O

@overdramaticmel	O
I	O
also	O
love	O
them	O
because	O
I	O
am	O
on	O
the	O
short	O
side	O
and	O
Levi's	B-organization
let	O
you	O
pick	O
inseam	O
lengths	O
.	O

India's	B-place
forex	O
kitty	O
goes	O
beyond	O
USD	O
298	O
billion	O
by	O
third	O
week	O
of	O
March	B-other

On	O
our	O
@knowhownonprof	O
site	O
you'll	O
find	O
free	O
how	O
-	O
tos	O
,	O
video	O
learning	O
options	O
and	O
more	O
-	O
http://t.co/qfkk4N7a8a	O

@DaMattAlbright	O
Ha	O
!	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
came	O
through	O
on	O
my	O
phone	O
,	O
though	O
.	O
Are	O
those	O
winged	O
W's	O
?	O
Like	O
bats	O
?	O
;	O
)	O

#Dubai	B-place
Tricksters	O
who	O
robbed	O
Dh63	O
,	O
000	O
from	O
Dubai	B-place
bank	O
client	O
jailed	O
for	O
3	O
years	O
:	O
Three	O
Uzbek	O
visitors	O
were	O
sen.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/jYUQHRVYi0	O

@ricky_martin	O
@Seal	O
How's	O
Everybody	O
Tonight	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
Johnny	B-person
D	I-person
http://t.co/bbmaPGw19y	O

@theazizio	O
maksudnya	O
surya	O
paloh	O
?	O
|	O
re	O
:	O
admin	O
aura	O
kasih	O

That	O
ain't	O
culture	O
RT	O
@Msatterfield4	O
:	O
@Blueraydre	O
a	O
stripper	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
bmw	O
from	O
me	O
2	O
days	O
ago	O
.	O

Heh	O
monna	O
nie	O
meer	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
RT	O
@OwaMelato_O	O
:	O
Mosensei	O
hahahahaha	O
.	O
U	O
came	O
out	O
alive	O
.	O
U'll	O
get	O
better	O
each	O
year	O
.	O
Don't	O
skil	O
leg	O
days	O
nigga	O
.	O

I	O
go	O
turtle	O
on	O
that	O
bootay	O
.	O
#sxsw	O

@lelaaspr	O
iya	O
ka	O
,	O
tapi	O
lusa	O
jg	O
balik	O
ke	O
padang	O
hehe	O

Schnucks	O
Drive	O
Time	O
Special	O
-	O
$	O
4	O
.	O
75	O
Tuna	O
Surprise	O
-	O
-	O
&	O
gt	O
;	O
http://t.co/l26RimkhwR	O

@vindhyasabnani	O
@twitdebbzie	O
:	O
o	O
semoga	O
urusan	O
lancar	O
segera	O
dan	O
gak	O
kenapa2	O
lagiii	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

#space	O
#astronomy	O
Sleepless	O
in	O
Kiev	B-place
:	O
Anderson	B-person
Cooper	I-person
talks	O
shop	O
from	O
the	O
Ukraine	B-place
:	O
CNN's	B-product
prime	O
-	O
time	O
host	O
talks	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/5YaJ0VKaAG	O

Lmao	O
@	O
Chuck	B-person
and	O
Kenny	B-person

jogging	O
is	O
the	O
worst	O
thing	O
ever	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
feels	O
so	O
good	O
after	O
you've	O
done	O
it	O

Her	O
dress	O
is	O
a	O
bit	O
short	O
#nsfw	O
#teamskeetpicks	O
http://t.co/GcwQqAZfGd	O

RT	O
@Cezzabean	O
:	O
Poem	O
by	O
Eva	B-person
,	O
17	O
.	O
The	B-product
Underground	I-product
Sun.	I-product
#Page3	O
@NoMorePage3	O
@TheSunNewspaper	O
https://t.co/tTeVJRMN5Q	O

let's	O
play	O
a	O
game	O
called	O
spot	O
the	O
couple	O
hint	O
:	O
harry	B-person
and	O
louis	B-person
http://t.co/l4KVyFdLn4	O

Something's	O
burning	O
,	O
I	O
can't	O
figure	O
out	O
what	O
.	O
.	O
It's	O
either	O
lust	O
or	O
a	O
cloud	O
of	O
dust	O

@TheBmoreGamer	O
I'm	O
about	O
to	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
more	O
.	O
My	O
timeline	O
is	O
so	O
bad	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
I	O
care	O
about	O
reading	O
get	O
lost	O
in	O
the	O
shuffle	O
lol	O

@lindo_dlamini	O
Yeah	O
we	O
have	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
extension	O

RT	O
this	O
if	O
you	O
want	O
#PerfectSoFar	B-product
to	O
be	O
@ashanti	O
'	O
s	O
next	O
single	O
from	O
#BraveHeart	B-product
#teamashanti	O
@ASHANTINEWS	O
http://t.co/JUVYlweVY5	O

Stupa	O
udah	O
jd	O
blom	O
Ian	O
?	O
RT	O
@Septiyans	O
:	O
Selamat	O
malam	O
buat	O
kamu	O
yg	O
selalu	O
bisa	O
membuat	O
lengkung	O
senyum	O
terus	O
terpancar	O
dari	O
dalam	O
sanubari	O
:)	O

@DrewCourt	O
He	O
thinks	O
"	O
private	O
charity	O
"	O
will	O
shovel	O
the	O
sidewalk	O
.	O

#FootBall	O
#Sports	O
Referee	O
decisions	O
cost	O
us	O
-	O
Ronaldo	B-person
http://t.co/pBe7jxGBES	O
#Fashion	O
CRNews	O

RT	O
@daijja_	O
:	O
Never	O
let	O
them	O
hoes	O
get	O
in	O
-	O
between	O
of	O
what	O
we	O
started	O
.	O

@AustinMahone	O
I	O
WANNA	O
MEET	O
YOU	O
SO	O
BAD	O
:(	O
#KCA	O
#VoteUKMahomies	O

I	O
just	O
wanna	O
see	O
my	O
babes	O
@AustinMahone	O
and	O
@CodySimpson	O
get	O
slimed	O

your	O
intellect	O
is	O
disrespectful	O
.	O
.	O

Great	O
song	O
.	O
Great	O
Video	O
:	O
http://t.co/PDX9AJjZS6	O
On	O
that	O
note	O
,	O
it's	O
bedtime	O
,	O
tomorrow	O
is	O
another	O
day	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

RT	O
@mdotbrown	O
:	O
On	O
a	O
scale	O
of	O
1	O
-	O
Bette	B-person
Midler	I-person
,	O
how	O
unnecessary	O
is	O
this	O
?	O

Morning	O
@savvykenya	O
.	O
Glad	O
you	O
enjoyed	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Mzee	B-person
shared	O
more	O
football	O
consultation	O
stories	O
off	O
the	O
record	O
.	O
I	O
laughed	O
.	O

@TheReal_DreDope	O
you	O
can	O
!	O
And	O
it	O
really	O
has	O
well	O
accept	O
the	O
one	O
time	O
I	O
seen	O
you	O
on	O
Main	B-place
Street	I-place
lol	O

Our	O
art	O
circle	O
&	O
gt	O
;	O
anyone	O
else's	O
.	O

#oldJawn	O
Get	O
Ready	O
!	O
#rahtyrose	O
#blackhearsesquad	O
#bytchdoitlooklikeicare	O
#mcjagurclothing	O
http://t.co/6Sv1YRzDob	O

[	O
Exclusive	O
Video	O
]	O
"	O
Caruso's	O
Dream	O
"	O
Suspends	O
Glowing	O
Pianos	O
Over	O
San	B-place
Francisco	I-place
Sidewalk	O
|	O
The	O
Creator	O
http://t.co/Jdxtedg9Qb	O

@Chillednigga317	O
boring	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
the	O
weather	O
blows	O
.	O

Maafin	O
Orang	O
yang	O
uda	O
buat	O
kita	O
kecewa	O
katanya	O
Mudah	O
,	O
tp	O
pada	O
Kenyataannya	O
ga	O
Semudah	O
Lidah	O
Berucap	O
*	O
FaktanyaBegitu	O
*	O

RT	O
@gede_prama	O
:	O
The	O
true	O
summer	O
is	O
summer	O
in	O
the	O
heart	O
@photo98765	O
:	O
http://t.co/JkC7azvvP7	O

BigGucciMaster	O
aka	O
Caleb	B-person
Uchiha	I-person
aka	O
Master	O
Hunna	O
aka	O
The	O
Coon	O
Slayer	O

@JoeRoseShow	O
FAU	O
Spring	O
game	O
in	O
9	O
days	O
.	O
April	O
5th	O
at	O
1	O
:	O
00pm	O
-	O
Free	O
admission	O
,	O
Free	O
concert	O
at	O
10	O
:	O
30am	O
,	O
Free	O
Parking	O
.	O
Check	O
out	O
the	O
Owls	O
!	O

Absolutely	O
horrific	O
that	O
Malaysia	B-organization
Airlines	I-organization
TEXT	O
the	O
victims	O
family	O
members	O
to	O
tell	O
them	O
the	O
news	O
.	O
So	O
inhumane	O
about	O
such	O
a	O
tragic	O
situation	O

Febani	B-person
girls	O
its	O
your	O
vagina	O
nobody	O
can	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
you	O
can't	O
do	O
with	O
it	O

A	O
dress	O
will	O
have	O
to	O
do	O
for	O
today	O

Life	O
is	O
like	O
a	O
bowl	O
of	O
Pasta	O
,	O
Exercise	O
is	O
like	O
sauce	O
.	O
Just	O
the	O
right	O
amount	O
of	O
sauce	O
and	O
the	O
pasta	O
taste	O
great	O
,	O
too	O
much	O
and	O
u	O
have	O
no	O
life	O
.	O

ditunggu	O
aja	O
ya	O
RT	O
@deanfahmi	O
:	O
JapaneseMusicID	O
req	O
One	O
Ok	O
Rock	O
-	O
Clock	O
Strike	O
dong	O
dj	O
^	O
^	O

Who	O
Wanna	O
Play	O
Me	O
In	O
2k14	O
On	O
XboxLive	B-product

@CrownC_Ray	O
udah	O
/	O
?	O
lgsg	O
dikasih	O
td	O
/	O
?	O
/	O
masuk	O
kmr	O
rome	O
oppa	O
/	O
?	O

#porn	O
,	O
#sex	O
,	O
#video	O
,	O
#naked	O
:	O
Mutual	O
Fuck	O
For	O
A	O
Sexy	O
Brunette	O
In	O
Pink	O
Lingerie	O
http://t.co/mRObPt4JFz	O
#Shemale	O

@AWellVersedMan	O
lol	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
and	O
then	O
send	O
them	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
?	O

@True_Beautyx3	O
that	O
chicken	O
smell	O
good	O
lemme	O
get	O
a	O
well	O
done	O
piece	O
.	O

@thatgirlallie	O
also	O
.	O
The	O
hell	O
with	O
a	O
spoon	O
I'll	O
dip	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
jar	O
with	O
my	O
finger	O
.	O
@guatemeha	O

DA	O
Manifesto	O
:	O
Economy	O
held	O
hostage	O
by	O
inefficiencies	O
of	O
#Eskom	B-organization
monopoly	O
and	O
over	O
-	O
reliance	O
on	O
coal	O
.	O
#loadshedding	O
http://t.co/2EVysI2lMH	O

@tobyvandre	O
@americans4amer	O
The	O
people	O
are	O
scared	O
by	O
the	O
talking	O
points	O
.	O
The	O
sheeple	O
vote	O
for	O
#GOPAssholes	O
.	O
Via	O
the	O
#TeaVangelicals	O

Creamy	O
Avocado	O
Hummus	O
http://t.co/rUCbAVKfF5	O

MATCHING	O
JUMPERS	O
IM	O
SCREAMING	O
#VoteDirectionersUK	O
#KCA	O
http://t.co/g0RyPN6NOC	O

@glai_vicerylle	O
nakaspeaker	O
pala	O
yon	O
.	O
Hahahahahaha	O

@kinseyschofield	O
thanks	O
for	O
the	O
follow	O
back	O
:)	O
how	O
are	O
you	O
?	O

@Sewellside	O
it's	O
your	O
BURFDAY	O
?	O
!	O

Panel	O
#selfie	O
!	O
#cesarchavez	B-person
#lurn	O
@	O
Landmark	O
Theatres	O
http://t.co/EE5YkGZIVx	O

@varsity_kale	O
I	O
need	O
to	O
get	O
on	O
your	O
oatmeal	O
level	O
.	O

Awesome	O
match	O
between	O
@TheShieldWWE	O
and	O
Wyatt	B-person
family	O
#WWEChicago	B-organization

Are	O
You	O
Wearing	O
Jorts	O
?	O
Take	O
this	O
quiz	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
!	O

Reading	O
Colin	B-person
Thubron	I-person
;	O
feeling	O
like	O
no	O
writer	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
explore	O
a	O
multi	O
-	O
storey	O
carpark	O
and	O
I'd	O
still	O
be	O
gripped	O
.	O

this	O
show	O
deserve	O
it	O
#VoteSamAndCat	O
#KCA	O

News5	O
Everywhere	O
-	O
MANAGER	O
NG	O
CEBU	O
PACIFIC	O
NA	O
NAMBASTOS	O
DIUMANO	O
SA	O
PASAHERO	O
,	O
PINARUSAHAN	O
NA	O
http://t.co/7N62bFlhzn	O

@jesselee14	O
nakakainis	O
!	O
!	O
BALER	O
!	O
Hate	O
you	O
po	O
hahaha	O
!	O
Enjoy	O
.	O
:	O
*	O

@GuaxinimGamer	O
voce	O
tem	O
que	O
resolver	O
se	O
vai	O
ser	O
um	O
guaxinim	O
ou	O
um	O
gatinho	O
kkk	O

Wat	O
do	O
u	O
do	O
when	O
u	O
finally	O
found	O
everything	O
u	O
thought	O
u	O
wanted	O
in	O
a	O
career	O
n	O
one	O
of	O
ur	O
competitors	O
offers	O
20bands	O
more	O
n	O
a	O
car	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
Damn	O
Smh	O

Apparemment	O
je	O
vais	O
enfin	O
pouvoir	O
me	O
brosser	O
les	O
dents	O
,	O
ouf	O

This	O
weekend	O
about	O
to	O
have	O
ya'll	O
on	O
some	O
other	O
shhhh	O
.	O

@EddySteezRYD	O
I'm	O
glad	O
to	O
be	O
apart	O
of	O
it	O
too	O
.	O
Nice	O
to	O
meet	O
u	O
as	O
well	O
.	O
You	O
going	O
to	O

@cymroglyn	O
oh	O
dear	O
.	O
Wouldn't	O
put	O
it	O
past	O
him	O
reporting	O
me	O
for	O
that	O
!	O
:-)	O

I'll	O
upload	O
pics	O
later	O

@SaintMarche	O
how	O
much	O
?	O
Seeing	O
here	O
everyday	O
with	O
latex	O
wear	O
make	O
it	O
worth	O
it	O
-	O
maybe	O
I	O
can	O
have	O
more	O
from	O
her	O

RT	O
@fxckbobby	O
:	O
Louisville	B-place
in	O
my	O
final	O
4	O
.	O
.	O
lets	O
fucking	O
go	O
smh	O

RT	O
@jurimoli	O
:	O
nunca	O
tive	O
tanto	O
sono	O
na	O
vida	O

@Batigol1908	O
@TheCalcioGuy	O
He	O
must	O
have	O
missed	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
scored	O
4	O
.	O
against	O
Arsenal	B-organization
.	O

s	O
/	O
o	O
to	O
3	O
Loudoun	B-place
Valley	I-place
baseball	O
college	O
commits	O
:	O
Anthony	B-person
Woods	I-person
(	O
D3	O
Randolph	B-organization
-	I-organization
Macon	I-organization
)	O
,	O
William	B-person
Reed	I-person
(	O
D2	O
Shepherd	B-organization
)	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
JD	B-person
Carpenter	I-person
(	O
D3	O
Wheaton	B-organization
)	O

There	O
is	O
no	O
way	O
you	O
can	O
preach	O
about	O
loyalty	O
and	O
faithfulness	O
,	O
when	O
you've	O
cheated	O
on	O
every	O
girl	O
you've	O
been	O
with	O
.	O
SHUT	O
THE	O
FUCK	O
UP	O

@BenGoldsmith90	O
haha	O
knew	O
you	O
would	O
like	O
it	O
!	O
#Team39	O

@neonmichaeI	O
I	O
can't	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
word	O
without	O
smiling	O
lmao	O

Enjoyed	O
a	O
spring	O
hike	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
Taking	O
a	O
moment	O
to	O
cloud	O
watch	O
and	O
witness	O
crepuscular	O
rays	O
beam	O
over	O
the	O
valley	O
.	O

Having	O
Someone	O
To	O
Stick	O
Around	O
When	O
The	O
Rough	O
Times	O
Get	O
Thick	O

@pIateau	O
gente	O
q	O
coisa	O
de	O
louco	O

@nina_rr	O
jack	B-person
wasn't	O
Italian	O
water	O
under	O
the	O
bridge	O
.	O

MR	B-person
AND	I-person
MRS	I-person
CARTER	I-person
KILLED	O
ME	O
AGAIN	O

Hamas	B-organization
supporters	O
demonstrate	O
near	O
Egypt	B-place
border	O
in	O
Gaza	B-place
to	O
protest	O
Egypt's	B-place
decision	O
to	O
ban	O
Hamas	B-organization
&	O
amp	O
;	O
designating	O
it	O
a	O
terrorist	O
org	O
.	O

@FitPr1nces	O
probably	O
the	O
better	O
option	O
.	O

@sassyhutch	O
@thejlawthg	O
I	O
WAS	O
SAD	O
AND	O
CRYING	O
I'M	O
SORRY	O

Nigerian	O
shit	O
RT	O
@UATheFirst	O
:	O
@dghjsus	O
you	O
real	O
as	O
hell	O

8	O
)	O
stunning	O
selection	O
of	O
Cheese	O
http://t.co/asju0ip0M9	O

niDCas	O
Don't	O
Like	O
Me	O
But	O
Fuk	O
Em	O
Ima	O
Do	O
Me	O
Regardless	O

RT	O
@MisterBihajver	O
:	O
ajde	O
sad	O
da	O
bude	O
leto	O
i	O
da	O
tvitujem	O
iz	O
kade	O

@Musicalgoose71	O
most	O
of	O
it	O
is	O
smog	O
I	O
been	O
in	O
China	B-place
far	O
to	O
long	O
I'm	O
ready	O
to	O
head	O
out	O
.	O

Painting	O
with	O
a	O
Twist	O
Featured	O
in	O
New	B-product
York	I-product
Times	I-product
http://t.co/mlPwUg4tcE	O

Gomez	B-person
:	O
Fiorentina	B-organization
never	O
gave	O
up	O
against	O
Juventus	B-organization
:	O
Fiorentina	B-organization
striker	O
Mario	B-person
Gomez	I-person
spoke	O
of	O
his	O
delight	O
at	O
netti	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/Ukcc1GSilW	O

$	O
17	O
.	O
99	O
Escali	O
Taso	O
Mixing	O
Bowl	O
Scale	O
Was	O
$	O
59	O
via	O
Posh	O
on	O
a	O
Budget	O
-	O
*	O
*	O
$	O
17	O
.	O
99	O
Escali	O
Taso	O
Mixing	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/KISx16Em56	O

@LiamMagz	O
loool	O
bun	O
everyone	O
!	O
!	O

A	O
needed	O
reminder	O
that	O
just	O
because	O
it	O
isn't	O
happening	O
here	O
,	O
doesn't	O
mean	O
it	O
isn't	O
happening	O
http://t.co/NqqGl9ipWW	O

@michaelford1983	O
@AnonyOps	O
@YourAnonGlobal	O
@blackplans	O
U	O
cant	O
spell	O
Revelation	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
and	O
u	O
an	O
Xtian	O
?	O
LMMFAO	O

On	O
this	O
UGK	O
"	O
Swishas	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
Dosha	O
"	O

Can't	O
wait	O
to	O
move	O
out	O
and	O
move	O
to	O
Brisbane	B-place
and	O
never	O
see	O
people	O
I	O
don't	O
want	O
to	O
aka	O
every	O
person	O
from	O
school	O
ever	O
again	O

One	O
of	O
my	O
followers	O
just	O
compared	O
Blake	B-person
Bortles	I-person
to	O
Joe	B-person
Flacco	I-person
.	O
That's	O
a	O
very	O
fair	O
comparison	O
.	O
Alot	O
of	O
similarities	O
.	O

RT	O
@RockersDive	O
:	O
#Listen	O
to	O
@CoreCritical	O
-	O
Core	O
Critical	O
-	O
Tryin	O
'	O
to	O
Seem	O
Normal	O
-	O
on	O
Rocker's	B-organization
Dive	I-organization
Radio	I-organization
http://t.co/OkhKOprCOC	O

Hey	O
folks	O
,	O
check	O
out	O
a	O
Wind	B-product
-	I-product
up	I-product
Knight	I-product
2	I-product
live	O
stream	O
starting	O
in	O
just	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
!	O
http://t.co/6l6xdSqhK1	O

Any	O
help	O
here	O
?	O
RT	O
@tpslinger	O
my	O
league	O
folded	O
.	O
Any	O
recs	O
on	O
where	O
I	O
can	O
find	O
an	O
active	O
league	O
to	O
join	O
?	O

@chuckrussell1	O
well	O
then	O
externalize	O
,	O
get	O
your	O
edges	O
sharpened	O
,	O
and	O
people	O
won't	O
want	O
to	O
step	O
on	O
the	O
doormat	O
anymore	O
:)	O

Si	O
la	O
tenes	O
gorda	O
,	O
larga	O
y	O
ancha	O
se	O
sabe	O
que	O
me	O
gustas	O
.	O

@KennyBooChainzz	O
lmaoo	O
wat	O
happened	O
?	O

Maybe	O
the	O
second	O
invisigremlin	O
has	O
run	O
off	O
after	O
its	O
friend	O
got	O
shot	O
.	O
#xfiles	O

@YeDevolutionist	O
It's	O
right	O
in	O
the	O
final	O
paragraph	O
.	O
"	O
Commercial	O
espionage	O
"	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
not	O
terrorism	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
it	O
fine	O
.	O
Sounds	O
like	O
you	O
didn't	O
.	O

28	O
days	O
until	O
#coachella	B-other
.	O
time	O
to	O
start	O
getting	O
those	O
outfits	O
planned	O
out	O

SHT	O
NO	O
I	O
NEED	O
TO	O
SEE	O
THEM	O
AGAIN	O

Every	O
girl	O
alive	O
secretly	O
wants	O
to	O
get	O
dicked	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
legendary	O
Edis	B-person
himself	O
.	O

@amylutz4	O
What	O
happens	O
if	O
we're	O
arguing	O
over	O
Obama's	B-person
bracket	O
picks	O
?	O

@dereknason	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
told	O
Claire	B-person
?	O

With	O
one	O
final	O
roster	O
spot	O
,	O
both	O
are	O
players	O
I	O
think	O
could	O
be	O
in	O
play	O
as	O
potential	O
call	O
-	O
ups	O
to	O
the	O
Thunder	B-organization
:	O
http://t.co/N3ElAiGcKL	O

RT	O
@cliffordadtr	O
:	O
Still	O
seeing	O
twenty	O
one	O
pilots	O
live	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
best	O
thing	O
to	O
ever	O
happen	O
to	O
me	O

#ViajeNaPoltrona	O
indica	O
o	O
livro	O
Duas	O
Vidas	O
,	O
Um	O
Caminho	O
,	O
sobre	O
o	O
Caminho	O
de	O
#Santiago	O
de	O
Compostela	O
http://t.co/SZgfj3cGLk	O

@JFigs25	O
@Willc22	O
little	O
*	O
lol	O
forgetting	O
words	O

Shout	O
out	O
to	O
my	O
bro	O
@_TallAssBud_	O
for	O
that	O
EARLY	O
morning	O
bake	O
.	O
#6am	O
#HappyBirthday	O

@Special_Asim	O
:D	O
Waisay	O
CONGRAATSS	O
:P	O

Idgaf	O
about	O
no	O
Boosie	B-person

@sexyRippahBex	O
Welche	O
Linie	O
?	O
*	O
grins	O
*	O

@bottomharry	O
ill	O
kms	O
6	O
times	O
tmrrw	O
bc	O
of	O
this	O
joke	O

NCAA	B-organization
Wrestling	O
Championships	O
Session	O
I	O
Roundup	O
.	O
Video	O
interviews	O
coming	O
soon	O
.	O
Session	O
II	O
begins	O
at	O
7	O
on	O
ESPNU	B-organization
:	O
http://t.co/3JXpOtO62m	O

This	O
is	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
our	O
15	O
%	O
off	O
sale	O
!	O

"	O
@DavidMBowers	O
Arthur	B-person
Housman	I-person
and	O
Walking	B-product
Dead's	I-product
Norman	B-person
Reedus	I-person
:	O
Separated	O
at	O
birth	O
?	O
#WalkingDead	O
http://t.co/mDH5Te5cL1	O
"	O
haha	O

@theactivestick	O
I	O
only	O
watch	O
his	O
random	O
game	O
clips	O
but	O
I	O
like	O
him	O
better	O
than	O
a	O
lot	O
of	O
hosts	O
.	O

RT	O
@ShenmueFans	O
:	O
[	O
Shenmue	O
Fans	O
]	O
Guizhang	B-product
&	I-product
amp	I-product
;	I-product
Ryo	I-product
wallpaper	O
by	O
Riken	B-organization
Productions	I-organization
.	O
Download	O
:	O
http://t.co/lAsDDbF556	O
http://t.co/wm2q12epGw	O

Has	O
there	O
ever	O
been	O
a	O
black	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
Polar	B-organization
Bear	I-organization
club	I-organization
?	O

opaaaa	O
saiu	O
ep	O
novo	O
de	O
Castle	B-product

Damnit	O
I	O
don't	O
wanna	O
get	O
up	O
for	O
work	O

I	O
usually	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
black	O
boxer	O
off	O
gp	O
but	O
emmmmmm	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
Amir	B-person
Khan	I-person
may	O
really	O
put	O
hands	O
on	O
Broner	B-person
lmao	O

RT	O
@ConvivialSiren	O
:	O
"	O
She's	O
a	O
whore	O
.	O
"	O
This	O
is	O
why	O
I	O
love	O
@EnticingFaux	O
.	O

@BillfromBendigo	O
@EnergyQuest	O
@PetefromHayNSW	O
To	O
my	O
mind	O
,	O
no	O
discussion	O
of	O
CSG	B-organization
mining	O
is	O
reasonable	O
unless	O
the	O
risks	O
are	O
accounted	O

@Karliiee6	O
ARE	O
YOU	O
FOR	O
REAL	O
DONT	O
BE	O
FCKING	O
WITH	O
ME	O
KARLIE	B-person
SRSLY	O

@FootyTippsy	O
@monarchadvisory	O
@ebonykd	O
@atlemax3	O
@coultercoulter	O
fantastic	O
day	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Great	O
day	O
for	O
forwards	O
http://t.co/dS63XRMsX5	O

Is	O
it	O
wrong	O
that	O
as	O
I	O
go	O
through	O
this	O
girls	O
pictures	O
I'm	O
just	O
like	O
"	O
you	O
need	O
a	O
nose	O
job	O
,	O
nose	O
job	O
,	O
nose	O
job	O
"	O
lololol	O

@keeweeeee	O
if	O
you're	O
craving	O
sugar	O
/	O
carbs	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
that	O
you're	O
low	O
on	O
serotonin	O
.	O
Hahaha	O
.	O

@taylorcaniff	O
awh	O
bby	O
we	O
love	O
you	O
soo	O
much	O
!	O
:)	O
#taylorday2014	O

@notmepaaaal	O
@1CrazyPATSfan	O
you	O
want	O
me	O
out	O
then	O
stop	O
talking	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
That's	O
how	O
it's	O
normally	O
done	O
.	O

I	O
feel	O
someone	O
uncle	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
wave	O
cap	O
on	O
like	O
I	O
should	O
walk	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
in	O
house	O
shoes	O
n	O
socks	O

Capital	B-organization
was	O
talking	O
about	O
twitter	B-organization
being	O
down	O
oh	O

@awwxharry	O
omg	O
!	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
followed	O
you	O
?	O

@NateDogg_254	O
that's	O
love	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
I	O
got	O
you	O
bro	O

@TalkTalkXFactor	O
please	O
choose	O
me	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
@nickymacx	O
for	O
#TalkTalkVIP	O
Birmingham	B-place
it'd	O
mean	O
ALOT	O
http://t.co/BpSjeI7BL3	O
http://t.co/1IDHd3ROHv	O
394	O

I	O
only	O
fuck	O
wit	O
a	O
few	O
niggas	O
cuz	O
they	O
kept	O
it	O
1000	O
fuck	O
100	O

SHIT	O
THAT	O
DANCER	O
IS	O
HOT	O
HAHA	O

@D_Hardie	O
lo	O
sunah	O
rasul	O
gih	O
drpd	O
ngetwit	O

RT	O
@emilyooh	O
:	O
#NoPlaceLikeHome	O
@5sos	O
Cute	O
http://t.co/wvKE9GA9Gg	O

@palemisfit	O
hahahaha	O
.	O
Ayat	O
tu	O
memang	O
normal	O
dimana	O
mana	O

why	O
the	O
fuck	O
would	O
you	O
smoke	O
if	O
you're	O
pregnant	O

RT	O
@AlainaBergsma	O
:	O
Excited	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Brazil	B-place
for	O
Carnival	O
!	O
Should	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
weekend	O
!	O
!	O
#FirstTime	O
#holidayabroad	O

@lupetto858	O
Do	O
yourself	O
a	O
favour	O
though	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
go	O
somewhere	O
really	O
special	O
for	O
lunch	O
/	O
dinner	O
,	O
try	O
out	O
Zinzi	O
at	O
Tsala	B-organization
Lodge	I-organization
.	O
.	O

Happy	O
Pancake	O
day	O
*	O
Insert	O
inappropriate	O
comment	O
about	O
tossing	O
here	O
*	O

Arghh	O
Ozil	B-person
out	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
weeks	O
with	O
a	O
hamstring	O
.	O
This	O
happens	O
to	O
us	O
everyyyy	O
season	O
bruv	O

RT	O
@ISRealTalk	O
:	O
Mufuckas	O
Never	O
Loved	O
Us	O
#BullsNation	O

@Mayberrykush	O
that's	O
mine	O
lol	O
but	O
yeah	O
bro	O
I	O
wish	O

Had	O
suuuuuuuuuch	O
a	O
good	O
day	O
with	O
the	O
fam	O
for	O
my	O
birthday	O
!	O
Bring	O
on	O
next	O
weekend	O
with	O
the	O
giiiiirlieees	O

Memorial	O
battle	O
royals	O
are	O
always	O
the	O
best	O
battle	O
royals	O
.	O
#LRPRIDE	O
#WWE	B-organization
#RAW	O

RT	O
@Nickoteen_	O
:	O
@BKFUniversity	O
turn	O
her	O
ass	O
in	O
!	O
Snitch	O

We	O
cant	O
wait	O
to	O
see	O
@onedirection	O
August	O
22	O
@	O
Reliant	O
Stadium	O
-	O
-	O
&	O
gt	O
;	O
#np	O
Story	O
of	O
My	O
Life	O
#listen	O
http://t.co/O5wwduOlYt	O

@Torontobot	O
Hey	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
you	O
lived	O
in	O
my	O
hood	O
:-)	O
I	O
see	O
beers	O
in	O
our	O
future	O
:-)	O

@iHeartMaslow_xo	O
then	O
east	O
coasters	O
always	O
ruin	O
it	O
for	O
is	O
with	O
their	O
tweets	O
and	O
stuff	O
.	O
Staahpppp	O

when	O
luke	B-person
says	O
they	O
are	O
a	O
serious	O
band	O
i	O
just	O
laugh	O
because	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
way	O
they	O
are	O
serious	O
i	O
mean	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
one	O
wearing	O
a	O
tutu	O

kik	O
me	O
to	O
sleep	O
:	O
EssaSuwi	O
.	O
.	O
khkhkhkhk	O
latshootoni	O
he	O
he	O
he	O
he	O
he	O
he	O
he	O
he	O
he	O
he	O
he	O
heh	O
e	O
he	O
agol	O
laish	O
ma7ad	O
yba	O
yrab3ni	O
ha	O
ha	O
ha	O
he	O
gn	O

I'll	O
shut	O
up	O
now	O
/	O
no	O
I	O
won't	O
probably	O
/	O

SAY	O
WHAT	O
YOU	O
MEAN	O
.	O
TELL	O
ME	O
IM	O
RIGHT	O
.	O
AND	O
LET	O
THE	O
SUN	O
RAIN	O
DOWN	O
ON	O
ME	O
.	O

RT	O
@T_Breezzyy1	O
:	O
Whenever	O
a	O
nigga	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
line	O
this	O
how	O
I	O
act	O
https://t.co/qdJX5kTdCl	O
@_steadyrockin	O
last	O
night	O
LMAO	O

Finally	O
getting	O
to	O
watch	O
The	B-product
Walking	I-product
Dead	I-product
from	O
sunday	O
.	O
.	O
OnDemand	O
takes	O
soo	O
long	O
to	O
put	O
shows	O
up	O
.	O
#thestruggleisreal	O

Stay	O
/	O
/	O
Miley	B-person
Cyrus	I-person
#np	O

Could	O
not	O
be	O
more	O
excited	O
for	O
Rob	B-person
and	O
Lance	B-person
.	O
Congratulations	O
!	O
!	O
#robandlance	O
@	O
The	O
Coronado	O
Ballroom	O
http://t.co/LDzfKAihWB	O

johnlockedness	O
:	O
allabitofablur	O
:	O
the	O
-	O
deadpoetssociety	O
:	O
AM	O
I	O
THE	O
ONLY	O
ONE	O
WHO	O
THINKS	O
THIS	O
GUY	O
AND	O
THIS	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/6XwL3fikJr	O

REPORT	O
:	O
India	B-place
power	O
into	O
ICC	O
#Wt20	O
semi	O
-	O
finals	O
with	O
eight	O
-	O
wicket	O
win	O
over	O
Bangladesh	B-place
:	O
http://t.co/bIrfnSz2p3	O
#IndvsBan	O

@Dai_davies31	O
@sheffplayers	O
haha	O
oh	O
Jesus	B-person
he's	O
back	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
Xxx	O

And	O
here	O
we	O
go	O
when	O
cHeat	O
refs	O
start	O
to	O
control	O
the	O
game	O
.	O

@nlacross1979	O
I	O
can't	O
find	O
it	O
either	O
on	O
Youtube	B-organization
or	O
http://t.co/nBUziwmO2c	O
,	O
unfortunately	O

@jonislike	O
i	O
might	O
see	O
ya'll	O
later	O
if	O
i'm	O
not	O
to	O
tired	O
to	O
drive	O
out	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
want	O
me	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
jacket	O
?	O

I	O
LOVENTHISN	O
CONVRRSATION	O

Republic	O
of	O
Spoof	O
MT	O
@kirpit	O
:	O
#Turkey	B-place
is	O
the	O
first	O
country	O
in	O
history	O
that	O
is	O
hijacking	O
the	O
Internet	O
of	O
its	O
citizens	O
!	O
http://t.co/JUNFwvZ6wZ	O

Once	O
again	O
,	O
Williamson	B-place
County	I-place
is	O
named	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
healthiest	O
places	O
in	O
Texas	B-place
.	O
http://t.co/5FP5DLjTwm	O
#txlege	O

Heh	O
.	O
Kristen	B-person
Anderson	I-person
-	I-person
Lopez	I-person
handed	O
her	O
purse	O
to	O
@jamiefoxx	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
discreetly	O
passed	O
it	O
off	O
to	O
Jessica	B-person
Biel	I-person
during	O
her	O
#Oscars	O
speech	O
.	O

@nicolacourtney	O
Hah	O
!	O
No	O
,	O
33	O
1	O
/	O
3	O
.	O
It's	O
a	O
series	O
of	O
cool	O
music	O
books	O
on	O
albums	O
that	O
does	O
an	O
open	O
call	O
every	O
year	O
or	O
two	O
for	O
proposals	O
.	O

BRUH	O
UNO	O
BEAT	O
IS	O
RIDICULOUS	O

Makes	O
me	O
mad	O
when	O
players	O
don't	O
get	O
that	O
recognition	O
for	O
the	O
talent	O
they	O
got	O
coming	O
from	O
Ark	O
.	O
Texas	B-place
garbage	O
and	O
Florida	B-place
and	O
Cali	B-place
.	O

.	O
@chuchomaeza	O
Le	O
agradezco	O
enormemente	O
su	O
tuit	O
.	O
Bueno	O
saber	O
que	O
lo	O
que	O
uno	O
hace	O
sirve	O
para	O
algo	O
de	O
vez	O
en	O
cuando	O

HOW	O
IS	O
ELIJAH	B-person
STILL	O
ALIVE	O
WHAT	O
THE	O
HELL	O

@mims	O
you	O
don't	O
think	O
it's	O
shitty	O
to	O
dox	O
the	O
guy	O
.	O
there's	O
no	O
proof	O
,	O
and	O
even	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
,	O
why	O
does	O
it	O
matter	O
?	O
where	O
'	O
public	O
interest	O
?	O

@natashaluxe	O
silly	O
Jake	B-person
!	O
He	O
also	O
has	O
the	O
height	O
advantage	O
:	O
studies	O
show	O
tall	O
guys	O
get	O
paid	O
more	O
and	O
promoted	O
faster	O
.	O
Conclusion	O
:	O
dudevantage	O

Vodafone	B-organization
offering	O
free	O
Sony	B-product
Bravia	I-product
TV	I-product
with	O
first	O
3000	O
pre	O
-	O
orders	O
of	O
new	O
flagship	O
Sony	B-product
Xperia	I-product
Z2	I-product
smartphone	O
http://t.co/patXGl5lr3	O

If	O
i	O
wear	O
an	O
outfit	O
one	O
day	O
and	O
no	O
one	O
important	O
is	O
there	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
i	O
didn't	O
really	O
wear	O
the	O
outfit	O

Events	O
:	O
@hustleGRL	O
CMW	O
Showcase	O
w	O
/	O
Naturally	O
Born	O
Strangers	O
@TreMission	O
@theairplaneboys	O
@AGameMedia	O
-	O
May	O
8	O
@	O
Tattoo	B-place
http://t.co/OCC3VN37AN	O

@ErosNow	O
#RamleelaOnErosNow	O
1	O
)	O
AAG	O

#Nowplaying	O
-	O
Rascalz	O
-	O
Quest	B-product
For	I-product
Rhyme	I-product
-	O
http://t.co/QsU9NwdOq7	O
#Vancouver	B-place
#Hiphop	O
#Rnb	O

Jeanette	B-person
still	O
needs	O
help	O
.	O
Please	O
RT	O
and	O
help	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
.	O
#HelpJeanette	O
Make	O
it	O
trend	O
!	O
http://t.co/mpwD81NIvP	O

@EsraAuldeo	O
hahaha	O
makanya	O
nyari	O
pacar	O
sra	O

@Dwayne_wins	O
Hey	O
dwayne	B-person
!	O
Yeah	O
,	O
looks	O
like	O
it's	O
an	O
LA	O
Stories	O
storytelling	O
event	O
at	O
@StoriesEchoPark	O
.	O
You	O
shld	O
go	O
:)	O

RT	O
@TheFinanceLab	O
Shouldn't	O
banks	O
be	O
reinvesting	O
in	O
local	O
economies	O
?	O
P	B-person
.	I-person
Kelly	I-person
of	O
Unity	B-organization
Trust	I-organization
Bank	I-organization
makes	O
the	O
case	O
http://t.co/BMQPs11s3y	O

I	O
have	O
now	O
played	O
3	O
games	O
of	O
TitanFall	B-product
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
good	O
at	O
dying	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
learned	O
.	O

Does	O
teen	O
pregnancy	O
CAUSE	O
bad	O
economic	O
outcomes	O
,	O
or	O
is	O
it	O
a	O
leading	O
indicator	O
?	O
Schneider	B-person
at	O
EconLog	B-organization
:	O
http://t.co/c34RQmuyRR	O

@eezms	O
hit	O
them	O
squats	O
so	O
i	O
could	O
pinch	O
that	O
ass	O

Niggas	O
eat	O
ass	O
but	O
won't	O
eat	O
a	O
TV	O
Dinner	O

RT	O
@Aimeegarden_	O
:	O
"	O
@iCristinaBos_	O
:	O
NO	O
crean	O
en	O
nadie	O
.	O
"	O

haters	O
are	O
the	O
best	O
motivators	O
.	O

TUNE	O
IN	O
TO	O
MY	O
NEW	O
SINGLE	O
[	O
HATE	B-product
IF	I-product
YOU	I-product
WANT	I-product
]	O
FEAT	O
@ARSONALDAREBEL	O
#RT	O
#LETSPUSHIT	O
http://t.co/kkiLIitCbE	O

"	O
Brate	O
ala	O
si	O
nam	O
zakomplikovala	O
zivot	O
"	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
aj	O
ne	O
lazi	O
,	O
ZIVOTA	O
TI	O
?	O
?	O
?	O
I	O
TO	O
umem	O
da	O
uradim	O
?	O
!	O
?	O
!	O
?	O
No	O
puedo	O
creer	O
!	O
!	O
!	O

RT	O
@Brian_Linhart	O
:	O
@Huntahray	O
@KPhucinTrann	O
@CFRN_	O
Jesus	O
doesn't	O
think	O
Deer	O
Valley	O
boys	O
are	O
thirsty	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

Then	O
he	O
asks	O
them	O
why	O
they	O
are	O
looking	O
for	O
their	O
dad	O
WTF	O
#Khumbu	O

@andshootthesun	O
well	O
ill	O
take	O
that	O
as	O
a	O
compliment	O

@rockvsto	O
vc	O
sabe	O
que	O
eu	O
falei	O
de	O
sacanagem	O
,	O
ne	O
?	O

The	B-product
Generation	I-product
Game	I-product
http://t.co/o9brrW3ZEx	O
#football	O
#news	O

Dylan	B-person
O	I-person
'	I-person
Brien	I-person
is	O
such	O
a	O
good	O
actor	O
he's	O
like	O
a	O
mix	O
of	O
Logan	B-person
Lerman	I-person
and	O
Zac	B-person
Efron	I-person
I	O

RT	O
@SipMyJuice_Box	O
:	O
"	O
@MurdaAveDomo	O
:	O
Ion	O
F	O
.	O
ck	O
w	O
/	O
B	O
.	O
tches	O
"	O
Fuck	O
Bitches	O
I	O
Don't	O
like	O
Em	O

ohp	O
wait	O
now	O
I'm	O
sad	O

You	O
suck	O
at	O
surprises	O
@angiemiller	O

Full	O
lovibonds	O
unit	O
representation	O
#beaglecask	O
http://t.co/8xLhHwkXo2	O

It's	O
one	O
where	O
we	O
need	O
every	O
fan	O
to	O
be	O
super	O
loud	O
tonight	O
-	O
a	O
repeat	O
of	O
Orient	O
would	O
be	O
perfect	O
.	O
Enjoy	O
the	O
match	O
!	O
#ColU	O

@DavidSpade	O
Everyone	O
in	O
L	B-place
.	I-place
A	I-place
.	I-place
is	O
talking	O
about	O
the	O
rain	O
.	O
Apparently	O
it's	O
more	O
rare	O
than	O
a	O
Hollywood	B-place
movie	O
without	O
gratuitous	O
sex	O
and	O
violence	O

RT	O
@JustInNotOut	O
:	O
Marvin's	O
"	O
What's	B-product
going	I-product
on	I-product
"	O
album	O
was	O
just	O
one	O
REALLY	O
long	O
song	O
.	O

Pregnant	O
wmn	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
on	O
tv	O
.	O
It's	O
obvious	O
and	O
distracting	O
and	O
confusing	O
and	O
they	O
look	O
FAT	O
#scandal	O

@Andrew_Reiner	O
@Futterish	O
ask	O
him	O
about	O
his	O
licorice	O
baths	O

@andrew_j_stone	O
@tsantero	O
adding	O
to	O
my	O
2	O
.	O
0	O
cookbook	O

@hamsandwich	O
i	O
know	O
they	O
are	O
a	O
juggernaut	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
ex	O
-	O
Fossil	O
guys	O
started	O
Shinola	O
.	O
BUT	O
STILL	O
.	O
i'm	O
not	O
a	O
snob	O
but	O
you	O
get	O
it	O
.	O

@ildarima	O
happy	O
birthday	O
my	O
brother	O
amir	B-person
!	O
Have	O
a	O
blast	O
!	O
Goodluck	O
in	O
your	O
future	O
and	O
may	O
Allah	B-person
bless	O
you	O
always	O
:)	O

@OriginalOestrus	O
You	O
leave	O
JUST	O
as	O
I	O
go	O
on	O
my	O
lunch	O
break	O
:	O
/	O
See	O
you	O
soon	O

Lo	O
mas	O
impresionante	O
es	O
que	O
me	O
lo	O
topo	O
siempree	O
es	O
el	O
destino	O
chicos	O
yo	O
lo	O
se	O

Oh	O
u	O
made	O
d	O
cake	O
init	O
?	O
RT	O
@ronkizzle93	O
@Xebrizzy	O
cutting	O
of	O
the	O
cake	O
ni	O

@edenthecat	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
every	O
day	O
.	O
=	O
(	O

@SameClothzErday	O
but	O
makaveli	B-person
came	O
back	O
april	O
15	O
.	O
.	O

A	O
Foodie	O
and	O
His	O
Grace	O
http://t.co/FRmMThYFqh	O

i	O
hope	O
you	O
all	O
think	O
of	O
me	O
when	O
you	O
see	O
a	O
blue	O
towel	O

@embIemtea	O
@ilykeaton	O
lay	O
off	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
kid	O

Penyerahan	O
Donasi	O
#MaskerUntukRiau	O
#MelawanAsap	O
|	O
@FLOCKIndonesia	O
@berbaginasiMKS	O
@EHmakassar	O
@MksrBerkebun	O
http://t.co/KfzEwDzuXj	O

I	O
been	O
in	O
tub	O
so	O
many	O
times	O

So	O
she	O
stops	O
hating	O
him	O
bcs	O
he's	O
beautiful	O
lol	O
def	O
a	O
good	O
reason	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
lol	O

RT	O
@BPWest_	O
:	O
"	O
@SiRackedUp	O
:	O
what	O
artists	O
would	O
u	O
like	O
to	O
see	O
on	O
the	O
official	O
"	O
Like	O
That	O
"	O
Remix	O
?	O
"	O
Wholagun	B-person
n	O
stormzy	O

Lindsay	B-person
Lohan	I-person
Pens	O
Celeb	O
-	O
Filled	O
Lovers	O
List	O
,	O
Tabloid	O
Pounces	O
:	O
Lindsay	B-person
Lohan	I-person
is	O
back	O
in	O
the	O
news	O
,	O
although	O
this	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/KNNRv1xPCV	O

Lauren	B-person
&	O
amp	O
;	O
Chloe	B-person
have	O
fallen	O
out	O
over	O
man	O
!	O
Tut	O
tut	O

@miss_jillyb	O
@ItsAshleyTam	O
I	O
wanna	O
know	O
by	O
who	O
!	O

Yes	O
,	O
I	O
still	O
care	O
about	O
what	O
other	O
people	O
think	O
.	O

RT	O
@KimHaleDance	O
:	O
Hello	O
Indianapolis	B-place
and	O
@Precision_Arts	O
!	O

I'm	O
so	O
hungover	O
I	O
could	O
die	O

"	O
Why	O
would	O
Joe	B-person
Hallenback	I-person
give	O
a	O
fuck	O
about	O
this	O
asshole's	O
Prince	O
impression	O
?	O
"	O
-	O
Shane	B-person
Black	I-person
,	O
on	O
a	O
scene	O
that	O
was	O
NOT	O
in	O
his	O
original	O
script	O

@jilltomlinson	O
Right	O
move	O
.	O
Discussion	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
professionalism	O
are	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
go	O
.	O

@daydreamjack	O
@edshewalk	O
@heartfeItstyles	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
other	O
people	O
and	O
then	O
i	O
said	O
harry	B-person
can	O
i	O
have	O
a	O
kissing	O
picture	O
and	O
he	O
looked	O
at	O

Eco	O
exam	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O

RT	O
@Rarahmaajeng	O
:	O
Selamat	O
ulangtahun	O
vega	O
{	O
}	O
@urayvega	O

RT	O
@DatGrandeAss	O
:	O
Somebody	O
best	O
of	O
recorded	O
that	O
and	O
got	O
it	O
up	O
on	O
YouTube	B-organization
in	O
the	O
next	O
five	O
minutes	O
or	O
I'll	O
cry	O
.	O
.	O
wait	O
I	O
already	O
am	O

@podidosai	O
here	O
Whole	O
Food	O
market	O
is	O
selling	O
canned	O
"	O
Organic	O
coconut	O
water	O
"	O
lololol	O

so	O
he	O
just	O
took	O
illegal	O
drugs	O
instead	O
http://t.co/Bnn0Lu85XE	O

@hans_faber	O
@hansdocter	O
Dank	O
.	O
Hopelijk	O
succesvol	O
!	O

#playingnow	O
Jason	B-person
Crest	I-person
-	O
Charge	O
of	O
the	O
Light	O
Brigade	O
-	O
how	O
apt	O
!	O

Me	O
too	O
&	O
gt	O
;	O
@KerryGorgone	O
:	O
I	O
don't	O
look	O
at	O
inspirational	O
photos	O
where	O
the	O
person	O
tags	O
like	O
50	O
people	O
.	O
Automatic	O
ignore	O
.	O
#BizHeroes	O

UK	B-place
:	O
#MalaysianGP	B-other
is	O
in	O
@BBCOne	O
right	O
now	O
.	O
Watch	O
out	O
for	O
#BenedictCumberbatch	B-person
presenting	O
on	O
the	O
winners	O
podium	O
at	O
around	O
1100	O
BST	O

@meiloveako	O
ay	O
:(	O
dko	O
pa	O
alam	O
eh	O
hahah	O
sabi	O
mo	O
napa	O
arbor	O
mo	O
na	O
:(	O

Bangun	O
tidur	O
badan	O
pegel	O
dan	O
mules	O
juga	O
males	O
:)	O
)	O

I	O
swear	O
im	O
a	O
fashion	O
intern	O
on	O
a	O
foreign	O
exchange	O
program	O
in	O
Milan	B-place
learning	O
bout	O
fabrics	O
and	O
shit	O

Pics	O
with	O
#dogwithablog	B-product
cast	O
@BlakeMichael14	O
@ImTheFrancescaC	O
@G_Hannelius	O
http://t.co/znTD96yNJJ	O

This	O
red	B-organization
lobster	I-organization
bitch	O
try	O
to	O
hit	O
the	O
panic	O
button	O
on	O
us	O
smh	O

#DRH	O
,	O
quels	O
leviers	O
activer	O
pour	O
un	O
retour	O
de	O
la	O
croissance	O
dans	O
vos	O
entreprises	O
?	O
RDV	O
avec	O
@ADP_fr	O
le	O
26	O
mars	O
http://t.co/1I5i83XxI6	O

18	O
-	O
1	O
BUCS	B-organization
!	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
7th	O
vs	O
.	O
Toronto	B-organization
.	O
This	O
is	O
obviously	O
the	O
premiere	O
offense	O
in	O
MLB	B-organization
right	O
now	O
.	O
:-)	O
#LetsGoBucs	O

Just	O
had	O
a	O
double	O
Toffee	B-product
Trevi	I-product
so	O
I'm	O
good	O
:D	O
RT	O
@Miss_Unathi	O
Same	O
:(	O
"	O
Yanga	O
:	O
Yhu	O
ndatsho	O
ndafuna	O
iMcFlurry	O
"	O

Woah	O
I	O
totally	O
dont	O
know	O
how	O
I	O
feel	O
about	O
Oculus	B-product
Rift	I-product
/	O
facebook	B-organization
.	O
Half	O
of	O
me	O
is	O
happy	O
because	O
VR	O
will	O
100	O
%	O
happen	O
due	O
to	O
FB	B-organization
cash	O
money	O
&	O
gt	O
;	O

How	O
Your	O
Chamber	O
of	O
Commerce	O
Can	O
Use	O
LinkedIn	B-product
http://t.co/TtWfPfG7yr	O

LACS	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
more	O
than	O
likely	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

Fusilli	O
Pasta	O
with	O
Broccoli	O
,	O
Garlic	O
Toasted	O
Breadcrumbs	O
and	O
Parmesan	O
Cheese	O
http://t.co/hcwZ357aeb	O
#ROC	O
#ROCBuzz	O

I	O
just	O
be	O
joking	O
,	O
nothin	O
serious	O

RT	O
@CatchAnything	O
:	O
I'm	O
actually	O
tired	O
of	O
dre	O
.	O

I'm	O
on	O
Instagram	B-organization
too	O
!	O
http://t.co/UYv4BnWZWf	O
I'm	O
slightly	O
addicted	O
!	O
Love	O
finding	O
me	O
accounts	O
to	O
follow	O
!	O
#bbloggers	O
#lbloggers	O
#psbloggers	O

all	O
you	O
hafta	O
do	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
bff	O
is	O
make	O
my	O
happiness	O
a	O
priority	O
,	O
but	O
also	O
leave	O
me	O
the	O
fuck	O
alone	O
like	O
86	O
%	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
.	O

@jordanstallchic	O
@UKLisaW	O
@Loganberry09	O
@sjcNKOTB	O
Yup	O
.	O
See	O
ya	O
soon	O
xo	O

@osnapitzxgrande	O
a	O
czemu	O
pytasz	O
,	O
czy	O
ja	O
znam	O
?	O

@nickbull21	O
Wha	O
?	O
You	O
mean	O
'	O
The	B-product
Hurricane	I-product
'	O
was	O
about	O
Bob	B-person
?	O
!	O
All	O
bets	O
are	O
off	O
.	O
Nah	O
,	O
I'll	O
stick	O
with	O
the	O
greatest	O
pound	O
-	O
for	O
-	O
pound	O
boxer	O
ever	O
.	O

RT	O
@Bamboo_Bangaa	O
:	O
It	O
truly	O
is	O
NOT	O
FAIR	O
that	O
men	O
don't	O
have	O
periods	O
or	O
cramps	O
.	O

@arie_doll	O
get	O
up	O
for	O
school	O
lol	O

@Eubankwarrior	O
great	O
meeting	O
u	O
this	O
morn	O
Chris	B-person
.	O
Really	O
enjoyed	O
our	O
chat	O
http://t.co/v9IIv4jaoE	O

I	O
want	O
to	O
skate	O
.	O
Let's	O
go	O
.	O

Arutz7	O
:	O
Students	O
in	O
Canada's	B-place
Capital	I-place
Boycott	O
Israeli	O
Hummus	O
:	O
Students	O
at	O
University	B-place
of	I-place
Ottawa	I-place
campaign	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/Mp5W9Pjcbu	O
#israel	O

Necesito	O
+	O
1	O
para	O
jugar	O

Should	O
parents	O
overprotect	O
their	O
kids	O
?	O
Studies	O
show	O
that	O
it	O
can	O
actually	O
hinder	O
a	O
child's	O
development	O
.	O
http://t.co/Re8wMNuYFq	O
@TheAtlantic	O

@UAfitprincess6	O
OMG	O
I'm	O
dying	O
hahahahhahahahahahahahahahhahaha	O

@lukeblanche	O
We	O
went	O
Straight	O
to	O
computer	O
room	O
for	O
Sali	B-person
so	O
she	O
didn't	O
notice	O
or	O
take	O
reg	O
,	O
and	O
GK	O
didn't	O
say	O
anything	O

@OregonPhilsphan	O
Has	O
it	O
really	O
been	O
that	O
long	O
?	O
I	O
remember	O
laughing	O
at	O
how	O
stupid	O
they	O
all	O
were	O
.	O

RT	O
@Mernakhaled5	O
:	O
@bahaaXmostafa	O
Happy	O
birthdaayy	O
:D	O

Buildings	O
Collapse	O
from	O
Gas	O
Explosion	O
in	O
Harlem	B-place
,	O
2	O
Dead	O
,	O
18	O
Injured	O
-	O
http://t.co/GLmF7I2ghw	O

ever	O
get	O
them	O
days	O
where	O
you	O
just	O
don't	O
even	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
tweet	O

@allofstyles	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
faving	O
xxx	O

they	O
gon	O
hate	O
when	O
they	O
see	O
u	O
movin	O
on	O
.	O
.	O

Our	O
greatest	O
weakness	O
lies	O
in	O
giving	O
up	O
.	O
Don't	O
ever	O
give	O
up	O
.	O

@ZARI_theGIANT	O
thanks	O
babes	O
.	O
.	O
I	O
want	O
it	O
done	O
professionally	O

5	O
Hurricanes	O
Who	O
Could	O
Surprise	O
People	O
This	O
Spring	O
http://t.co/Ee447Yd7XX	O

Pemanasan	O
dulu	O
sebelum	O
tampil	O
.	O
Happy	O
AE	O
!	O
#AllEnglandSSP	O
http://t.co/3TtEhW5ZoM	O

@hiplibertarian	O
My	O
entire	O
head	O
fills	O
up	O
the	O
monitor	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
voice	O
is	O
cool	O
.	O
HA	O
#preppertalk	O

Leo	B-person
telling	O
Matthew	B-person
to	O
sleep	O
with	O
one	O
eye	O
open	O
tonight	O
http://t.co/903xyZW9IA	O

Only	O
R	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
B	O
artist	O
I	O
listen	O
to	O
anymore	O
is	O
august	B-person
or	O
@rickey_fontain	O

@peacefultaru	O
I've	O
been	O
Buzzfeed	O
surfing	O
:)	O

If	O
they	O
not	O
with	O
you	O
then	O
they	O
against	O
you	O
.	O
.	O

@slothingwitjai	O
I'm	O
not	O
leaving	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
will	O
I'm	O
just	O
losing	O
respect	O
for	O
them	O

@TMurph207	O
Yep	O
.	O
He's	O
a	O
total	O
nihilist	O
.	O
Rust	O
would	O
love	O
McCarthy	B-person
.	O

@its_arctic	O
jeidnwskksksn	O
,	O
eu	O
sempre	O
me	O
confundo	O

It	O
is	O
STILL	O
shocking	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
80	O
%	O
of	O
PIs	O
applying	O
to	O
NSF	B-organization
have	O
historically	O
only	O
submitted	O
a	O
single	O
proposal	O
per	O
yr	O
(	O
and	O
DM	O
.	O
Just	O
don't	O
)	O

The	O
Lego	B-product
Movie	I-product
was	O
so	O
deep	O
and	O
intense	O
what	O
the	O
fuck	O
I	O
feel	O
inspired	O

@welshwannabe	O
@ali_freestone	O
@NorahsArk	O
@ScoobyySue	O
@charbhardy	O
@hastillonlyme	O
@__Gran2F__	O
@kgimson	O
I've	O
got	O
all	O
endeavor	O
recored	O
but	O
not	O

RT	O
@zcott	O
:	O
So	O
this	O
is	O
what	O
twitter	B-organization
looks	O
like	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

@DiianIslamiati	O
boleeh	O
:	O
)	O
mau	O
wrna	O
apa	O
?	O
?	O

@vinosity	O
i	O
feel	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
about	O
earwigs	O

@kid_juju	O
you	O
cute	O
af	O
my	O
nigga	O

@IvDreaMvI	O
and	O
people	O
think	O
no	O
scoping	O
in	O
cod	O
is	O
bad	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
lmao	O

My	O
brother	O
in	O
the	O
hole	O
upstate	O
at	O
coal	O
township	O
free	O
Lanny	B-person

How	O
Venture	B-product
Capital	I-product
Helps	O
Drive	O
The	O
Startup	O
Economy	O
http://t.co/u0mHirjesj	O
#business	O
http://t.co/Zh8NbNZwHH	O

@snowfairy1234	O
Besides	O
the	O
truth	O
nearly	O
always	O
comes	O
back	O
to	O
bite	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
arse	O
.	O

@SchaaPieyka	O
@Suhaheboh	O
tadi	O
mu	O
dgn	O
zierah	O
jeke	O
g	O
?	O
oh	O
esk	O
mu	O
balik	O
awal	O
plk	O
la	O
?	O

Great	O
day	O
at	O
the	O
@RudeyeAgency	O
office	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
Lots	O
of	O
jobs	O
booked	O
which	O
is	O
always	O
nice	O
!	O
!	O

@elvisknievil	O
some	O
soldier	O
quote	O
I	O
can't	O
credit	O
anyone	O
"	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
more	O
greater	O
feeling	O
than	O
knowing	O
you	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
die	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
then	O
you	O
dont	O

hannah	B-person
blocked	O
me	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
mirelys	B-person

This	O
flu	O
is	O
so	O
rude	O
.	O
It's	O
here	O
!	O

@bmeegwun	O
Better	O
than	O
those	O
other	O
actors	O
in	O
those	O
kinds	O
of	O
movies	O
xD	O

RT	O
@ginakuhn	O
:	O
candy	B-product
crush	O
is	O
Scientology	B-organization
cult	O
status	O
shit	O

@fygyoung	O
gak	O
punya	O
duit	O
un	O
:	O
(	O

AUSTIN	B-person
HUST	I-person
TEEETED	O
MADDIE	B-person

@beaniebabelouis	O
yahhhh	O
but	O
I'll	O
keep	O
shit	O
haha	O

Don't	O
think	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
any	O
hungrier	O
right	O
now	O
.	O

I	O
FEEL	O
LIKE	O
SOMETHING'S	O
CRAWLING	O
UP	O
MY	O
NECK	O

"	O
@amirulashrafh	O
:	O
Zoom	O
dan	O
terbalikkan	O
phone	O
anda	O
http://t.co/yyhSsXdBWA	O
"	O
pocong	O
uih	O
nightmare	O
bye	O

@IAMJHUD	O
can	O
Play	O
@ArethaFranklin	O
for	O
sure	O
in	O
a	O
movie	O
!	O
!	O

@V0GUEIRWIN	O
yes	O
it	O
will	O
because	O
he	O
loves	O
you	O
and	O
so	O
do	O
i	O
http://t.co/koTOtRL7fw	O

What's	O
so	O
funny	O
about	O
peace	O
,	O
love	O
,	O
and	O
murderous	O
fantasies	O
?	O
http://t.co/x2Mjw6DWuN	O
THE	B-product
CUTTING	I-product
EDGE	I-product
#Humor	O
#Suspense	O
#Kindle	O
#Nook	O

@dreams_ofyou	O
And	O
thank	O
you	O
!	O
Enjoy	O
your	O
day	O
as	O
well	O
.	O
:)	O

@TKingbooyyy	O
@GDixon410	O
http://t.co/02519RXpA2	O
Me	O
after	O
seeing	O
that	O
cross	O
up	O
.	O

RT	O
@bellarinaholic	O
:	O
I	O
vote	O
for	O
#Swifties	O
-	O
Taylor	B-person
Swift	I-person
#SoFantastic	O
@radiodisney	O
@TaylorSwift13	O
cinquenta	O
e	O
nove	O

kl	O
g	O
nungguin	O
jeketi	O
g	O
bkl	O
nntn	O
ini	O
acara	O

ready	O
to	O
end	O
this	O
week	O
bc	O
spring	O
break	O
bc	O
sleep	O
all	O
day	O

Justin	B-person
likes	O
girls	O
who	O
has	O
flat	O
boobs	O
and	O
flat	O
ass	O
.	O
Lol	O

I	O
really	O
just	O
want	O
to	O
play	O
FFX	B-product
-	I-product
2	I-product
HD	I-product
,	O
but	O
I	O
paid	O
50	O
bucks	O
for	O
this	O
collection	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
guess	O
I	O
gotta	O
make	O
my	O
way	O
through	O
*	O
some	O
*	O
portion	O
of	O
FFX	B-product
.	O

Jake	B-person
is	O
mos	O
def	O
about	O
that	O
life	O
.	O
#Scandal	O

@MariaamMohamed_	O
fe	O
el	O
nzam	O
el	O
3	O
'	O
eza2y	O
!	O
xD	O

@elveinte	O
gracias	O
amigo	O
!	O
!	O
abrazo	O
grande	O
y	O
estate	O
listo	O
:)	O

I	O
do	O
think	O
Kobe's	B-person
comments	O
were	O
a	O
bit	O
misguided	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
also	O
has	O
a	O
point	O
.	O

RT	O
@RagingPhratHard	O
:	O
Online	O
class	O
teachers	O
that	O
don't	O
accept	O
late	O
work	O
are	O
obviously	O
cunts	O
.	O

@persiandreaam	O
lmao	O
yeah	O
til	O
the	O
3rd	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
have	O
people	O
from	O
the	O
company	O
coming	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
gotta	O
dress	O
all	O
nice	O
nshit	O
smh	O

Or	O
Yukki	O
from	O
Mirai	B-product
Nikki	I-product

Rosberg	B-person
versus	O
Vettel	B-person
http://t.co/jr51X4R1qe	O

Does	O
anybody	O
know	O
an	O
elegant	O
way	O
of	O
replying	O
to	O
AND	O
accepting	O
LinkedIn	B-organization
invites	O
ie	O
without	O
having	O
to	O
delve	O
into	O
your	O
inbox	O
archive	O
?	O

Id	O
get	O
me	O
some	O
lunch	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
desire	O
to	O
move	O
.	O

College	O
basketball	O
is	O
dumb	O

ion	O
care	O
long	O
as	O
she	O
happy	O
ain't	O
my	O
business	O
man	O

Going	O
to	O
fucking	O
cry	O
ahaha	O
Liverpool	B-place
I	O
love	O
you	O

No	O
but	O
someone	O
seriously	O
help	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
magcon	O
outfit	O

@Folktergeist	O
estamos	O
en	O
las	O
mismas	O
:(	O

@ChampagneFriday	O
YESSS	O
#ChampagneFriday	O
#weekend	O

"	O
@asdfghooligan_	O
:	O
@caeleerrss	O
@imjusthavinfun	O
*	O
whispers	O
*	O
rich	O
kid	O
e	O
"	O
lol	O
no	O
it's	O
not	O
even	O
permanently	O
mine	O
haHAHA	O
NOOO	O
:(	O
(	O

I'm	O
up	O
listening	O
to	O
@BishopPorter	O
and	O
I'm	O
ready	O
for	O
church	O
NOW	O
!	O
My	O
God	O
!	O
Don't	O
be	O
late	O
tomorrow	O
it's	O
going	O
up	O
!	O
#netchurch	O

@YouCantFindMe19	O
Alex	B-person
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
We	O
can't	O
be	O
friends	O
.	O
Or	O
even	O
acquaintances	O
tbh	O

RT	O
@rag3ah0lic	O
:	O
waitress	O
ask	O
how	O
many	O
bottles	O
I	O
said	O
#	O
23	O
j's	O
on	O
my	O
feet	O
http://t.co/epomhogw2t	O

S	O
/	O
o	O
to	O
the	O
main	O
.	O
Always	O
been	O
there	O
since	O
day	O
one	O
@TheTorilynn	O

@KarlLukeman	O
@LewCLeslie	O
@DeanoLukeman	O
mate	O
its	O
all	O
about	O
to	O
kick	O
off	O
in	O
corrie	O
I'll	O
advise	O
u	O
to	O
get	O
home	O
before	O
half	O
8	O
#AllKickingOff	O

RT	O
@RealMissOKTeen	O
:	O
Up	O
and	O
at	O
em	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
boot	O
camp	O
!	O
#Vanbros	O

@HollywoodDanny	O
DANIEL	B-person
MARTIN	I-person
GERAGHTY	I-person
IF	O
YOU	O
ARENT	O
GOING	O
TO	O
MARRY	O
ME	O
THE	O
LEAST	O
YOU	O
COULD	O
DO	O
IS	O
FOLLOW	O
ME	O
THANK	O
YOU	O
FOR	O
YOUR	O
TIME	O

Getting	O
to	O
know	O
you	O
#pips4life	O
http://t.co/gZQ1D5wJxL	O

Only	O
Demi	B-person
can	O
make	O
pig	O
tails	O
look	O
so	O
cute	O
http://t.co/t4TfN3JLgZ	O

"	O
@TRU_GOGETTAH	O
:	O
I'm	O
finnA	O
get	O
amber	B-person
drunk	O
"	O

@xshtonirwn	O
@fivesosfangirl	O
@4seconds_of_1d	O
oH	O
MY	O
GFD	O
WHAT	O
IS	O
THI	O
S	O

@thereisnoBattle	O
@DogePromotions	O
@moolah_io	O
@tipdoge	O
no	O
I	O
see	O
it	O
as	O
inactive	O
though	O
.	O

Precision	O
#Nutrition	O
Plates	O
by	O
Dr.	B-person
John	I-person
Berardi	I-person
.	O
.	O
good	O
stuff	O
!	O
http://t.co/klcioTfu2J	O

Tonight	O
two	O
last	O
episode	O
of	O
bates	B-product
motel	I-product

RT	O
@gorgirwinnarry	O
:	O
my	O
brother	O
thinks	O
cus	O
im	O
nice	O
to	O
him	O
once	O
that	O
now	O
were	O
friends	O
ew	O

Ass	O
shots	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O

@AshersMomOKC	O
@wedgepizza	O
@glynis_crawford	O
@Lupita_Nyongo	O
It's	O
not	O
a	O
contest	O
!	O
#ohwaititis	O

@glitterh4rry	O
@justenotario	O
@stylesteimosa	O
louis	O
tb	O
nao	O
,	O
niall	O
orgulho	O
das	O
mofa	O

"	O
You	O
dont	O
think	O
wed	O
buy	O
a	O
house	O
and	O
not	O
have	O
a	O
Joey	B-person
room	O
"	O

RT	O
@BYElaserland	O
:	O
@BeforeYouExit	O
but	O
Riley's	B-person
at	O
the	O
gym	O

Sepi	O
:	O
|	O
ngga	O
ada	O
yg	O
mention	O
nih	O
?	O

So	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
hover	O
boards	O
are	O
a	O
thing	O
now	O
.	O
http://t.co/dXCNzURSoB	O

RT	O
@AnickGervais	O
:	O
Me	O
and	O
@LizaStinton	O
tonight	O
!	O
I'm	O
pumped	O
!	O

@PresenterJMB	O
me	O
and	O
you	O
are	O
gonna	O
fight	O
tomorrow	O
watch	O
.	O

@normanikordei	O
Follow	O
me	O
please	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
3	O
i	O
love	O
u	O

@JeffeePalmer	O
Thank	O
you	O
!	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
blast	O
doing	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	B-person
Lamb	I-person
was	O
so	O
gracious	O
and	O
down	O
-	O
to	O
-	O
earth	O
.	O

I	O
Am	O
Mixtapes	O
163	O
-	O
@DJSuperstarJay	O
.	O
.	O
Shout	O
Out	O
http://t.co/MjNnLmiZLv	O

Tendangan	O
Asamoah	O
Buat	O
Fiorentina	O
Pulang	O
Dengan	O
Tangan	O
Hampa	O
http://t.co/LmTMl3BGMs	O
via	O
SportSatu	O

Tersisa	O
dua	O
hari	O
lagi	O
sebelum	O
HTC	B-organization
Weekend	O
Promo	O
berakhir	O
.	O
Segera	O
datang	O
ke	O
outlet	O
Erafone	O
yaa	O
!	O
#SalamHTC	O
:)	O
http://t.co/xHRt96wXOS	O

RT	O
@Ant_pinehill	O
:	O
5	O
am	O
In	O
Jersey	B-place
http://t.co/IWs23LqMdu	O
on	O
#SoundCloud	O

RT	O
@bop_trill	O
:	O
@PinkkXLipstickk	O
Goodnight	O
love	O
and	O
love	O
you	O
too	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
blessed	O
day	O
tomorrow	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
1love	O

Join	O
Multi	O
-	O
Faith	O
Conversations	O
TOMORROW	O
from	O
5	O
:	O
45	O
-	O
7	O
PM	O
in	O
Tucker	B-place
105	I-place
to	O
discuss	O
ethical	O
and	O
spiritual	O
eating	O
choices	O
!	O
RSVP	O
to	O
:	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

I	O
knew	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
stuck	O
to	O
my	O
original	O
plan	O
and	O
drawn	O
a	O
buttcrack	O
on	O
the	O
moon	O
.	O

I	O
think	O
I'm	O
hungover	O
from	O
a	O
stupid	O
grey	B-product
goose	I-product
champagne	O
cocktail	O
.	O
Fuck	O
.	O

RT	O
@roamin	O
:	O
Wednesday	O
Flipped	O
http://t.co/N3mpzlkbZZ	O

I	O
miss	O
my	O
kitty	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
:(	O
#LonelyFennec	O

RT	O
@rosaleenauk	O
:	O
@HanahPhilippa	O
@LiterateCyNickS	O
Page	O
3	O
is	O
a	O
choice	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
dont	O
understand	O
why	O
feminists	O
want	O
to	O
snatch	O
it	O
away	O
from	O
women	O
.	O

Everytime	O
i	O
come	O
on	O
twitter	B-organization
i	O
see	O
her	O
tweets	O
dem	O
and	O
dem	O
gone	O
like	O
half	O
hour	O
ago	O

Ghost	O
sign	O
on	O
Stamford	B-place
Hill	I-place
http://t.co/wjVTid743f	O

Strawberry	B-product
sundae	I-product
is	O
the	O
best	O
*	O
_	O
*	O

@immolations	O
is	O
that	O
the	O
forest	O
where	O
people	O
go	O
to	O
commit	O
suicide	O
?	O

I	O
got	O
my	O
eyes	O
on	O
you	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
:	O
*	O
@greysonchance	O

Cross	O
the	O
line	O
,	O
speak	O
about	O
my	O
mine	O
.	O
Ima	O
way	O
this	O
tech	O
Ima	O
geek	O
about	O
mine	O

@Something_AFC	O
@arsenalfc49	O
I'm	O
most	O
certainly	O
not	O
wenger	O
in	O
,	O
appreciate	O
what	O
he's	O
done	O
but	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
sake	O
his	O
rep	O
is	O
fast	O
eroding	O
.	O

@optimusfab	O
thats	O
basically	O
wat	O
i	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
tweet	O
fatty	O
.	O
.	O

5	O
-	O
0	O
LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL	O

@LondonLee62	O
Wouldn't	O
it	O
?	O
Looks	O
like	O
an	O
alternative	O
universe	O
version	O
of	O
Fairport's	B-product
Unhalfbricking	O
.	O

-	O
you	O
see	O
,	O
that's	O
boring	O
.	O
@Pony_Brony	O

@ShanSykesHoran	O
the	O
thing	O
is	O
I	O
WASNT	O
EVEN	O
STANDING	O
UP	O

Monday	O
;	O
6	O
.	O
23am	O
;	O
1	O
degree	O
!	O
What	O
no	O
rain	O
!	O
?	O
!	O
!	O
Time	O
to	O
trg	O
!	O
What	O
will	O
@StuartAmoryPT	O
have	O
in	O
store	O
this	O
cold	O
beautiful	O
morning	O
#FitTeam14	O

"	O
Don't	O
Michael	B-person
Jordan	I-person
still	O
got	O
his	O
hoop	O
earring	O
in	O
?	O
"	O

@missrxe	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
?	O
I	O
sent	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
post	O
?	O

@e3way	O
eu	O
era	O
a	O
drewphoric	O
/	O
hommobrien	O
idk	O
oi	O

I'LL	O
SMOKE	O
U	O
OUT	O
RIGHT	O
NOW	O
@ScHoolBoyQ	O

Kepala	O
hotak	O
dia	O
nak	O
tunda	O
minggu	O
depan	O
.	O
Hish	O

@timothypembroke	O
@rustyrockets	O
@smh	O
Fair	O
enough	O
-	O
I	O
read	O
very	O
little	O
cellulose	O
these	O
days	O

I'm	O
currently	O
sitting	O
on	O
my	O
laptop	O
but	O
I	O
don't	O
want	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
bc	O
I'm	O
very	O
comfortable	O
rn	O

I	O
give	O
you	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
Spankys	O
Pail	O
Punch	O
!	O
3	O
kinds	O
of	O
vodka	O
and	O
fruit	O
juices	O
http://t.co/lFfOvn3MTp	O

He's	O
like	O
woah	O
woah	O
you	O
don't	O
remember	O
me	O
do	O
you	O
?	O
And	O
I'm	O
like	O
lol	O
yeah	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

RT	O
@Deadspin	O
:	O
Real	O
-	O
life	O
Kenny	B-person
Powers	I-person
spotted	O
:	O
http://t.co/0jTeRlh1Gx	O

Where's	O
John	B-person
Travolta	I-person
been	O
hiding	O
?	O
#2014Oscars	O

i	O
got	O
medusa	O
on	O
my	O
sneakers	O
my	O
dick	O
up	O
like	O
nice	O
to	O
meet	O
cha	O

@harrypintudo	O
eu	O
tenho	O
17	O
ainda	O
kkkkkkkj	O
mas	O
eu	O
sempre	O
levo	O
os	O
documentos	O
da	O
moto	O
/	O
carro	O
quando	O
eu	O
saio	O

I'm	O
at	O
Ayam	O
Goreng	O
ABC	O
,	O
Batu	O
-	O
Malang	O
(	O
Batu	O
-	O
Malang	O
)	O
http://t.co/KpWtXA8q1c	O

@CalvLyfeson	O
@boyonthefence	O
Kono	B-person
only	O
plays	O
wide	O
left	O
though	O
,	O
right	O
?	O

@fryind	O
It's	O
called	O
the	O
butterfly	O
effect	O
.	O
.	O
but	O
whatever	O
Goodnight	O
,	O
enjoy	O
your	O
day	O
x	O

@Th0tiana_	O
I'll	O
bring	O
them	O
to	O
you	O

But	O
first	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
take	O
a	O
sellfie	O
.	O
Selfie	O
at	O
a	O
bookstore	O
,	O
because	O
why	O
not	O
.	O
http://t.co/fi0YV6P35f	O

My	O
greatest	O
achievement	O
in	O
life	O
is	O
being	O
blocked	O
by	O
ryan	B-person
murphy	I-person
on	O
twitter	O
though	O
.	O

RT	O
@TeaPartyOrg	O
:	O
Reporter	O
detained	O
by	O
Capitol	B-place
Hill	I-place
police	O
for	O
trying	O
to	O
ask	O
EPA	B-organization
chief	O
a	O
question	O
http://t.co/znoOzbfqXE	O
#TeaParty	O

vou	O
mudar	O
meu	O
design	O
pelo	O
iphone	O
mesmo	O

PRODUCT	O
REVIEW	O
:	O
SWISH	B-product
BEFORE	I-product
YOU	I-product
KISS	I-product
.	O
-	O
News	O
-	O
Bubblews	O
http://t.co/6wRznpKLdr	O
#bubblews	O

@natcore01	O
yap	O
punta	O
ako	O
!	O
:)	O
pwede	O
daw	O
ba	O
may	O
manood	O
?	O
:)	O

RT	O
@newmedialuvvy	O
:	O
People	O
of	O
#Yorkshire	B-place
,	O
get	O
ready	O
for	O
your	O
new	O
#radio	O
station	O
#radioyorkshire	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
http://t.co/K6ZQSphA8q	O

Im	O
The	B-organization
Grove	I-organization
&	O
amp	O
;	O
CPA	B-organization
old	O

@MdShahzad	O
so	O
now	O
its	O
Merc	O
then	O
1s	O
after	O
is	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
grid	O
,	O
Starting	O
with	O
barfeela	O
insaan	O
.	O

RT	O
@KTVN	O
:	O
#BREAKING	O
:	O
Deputies	O
have	O
found	O
human	O
remains	O
in	O
the	O
backyard	O
of	O
Coleen	B-person
and	O
Gerald	B-person
Muhl	I-person
.	O
Coleen	O
has	O
been	O
#missing	O
for	O
several	O
weeks	O

Matthew	B-person
McConaughey's	I-person
dad	O
is	O
drinking	O
a	O
miller	O
lite	O
while	O
having	O
a	O
cajun	O
-	O
themed	O
oscar	O
dance	O
party	O
in	O
heaven	O
.	O
#oscars	B-other

My	O
new	O
bed	O
is	O
too	O
comfortable	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
sanity	O

Nicki	B-person
Lewinski	I-person
better	O
make	O
an	O
appearnce	O
on	O
the	O
3rd	O
album	O
.	O

@PelicanDick	O
@LilKimNews	O
@shittingonurfav	O
Drake	B-person
still	O
has	O
endorsements	O
.	O
Try	O
again	O
sis	O
.	O

Wow	O
the	O
first	O
earthquake	O
I've	O
felt	O
in	O
LA	B-place
cool	O
hashtag	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
cool	O

What	O
Content	O
Marketing	O
And	O
First	O
Dates	O
Have	O
In	O
Common	O
by	O
@Uberflip	O
~	O
http://t.co/fHRiJq9zJw	O
via	O
@SlideShare	O

@Buckets_McNasty	O
YOU'RE	O
A	O
LOSER	O
GO	O
MAKE	O
SOME	O
REAL	O
FRIENDS	O
NERD	O

Tryna	B-person
decide	O
if	O
I	O
want	O
weave	O
or	O
not	O
for	O
SXSW	O
.	O

anitta	O
ta	O
com	O
cara	O
de	O
rica	O
antes	O
ela	O
tinha	O
cara	O
de	O
pobre	O
sinceramente	O

Streaming	O
data	O
has	O
revealed	O
the	O
top	O
68	O
songs	O
since	O
Nov	O
:	O
http://t.co/byIIDEBONp	O
Who	O
will	O
win	O
this	O
preview	O
match	O
-	O
up	O
?	O
http://t.co/YFPQWG89l1	O

i	O
feel	O
like	O
harry	B-person
when	O
nobody	O
laughs	O
at	O
his	O
jokes	O

Men	O
will	O
say	O
us	O
women	O
do	O
.	O
Us	O
women	O
will	O
admit	O
we	O
do	O
and	O
say	O
you	O
niggas	O
do	O
as	O
well	O
.	O

RT	O
@StaceyMcKenzie1	O
:	O
Can't	O
wait	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
fashions	O
on	O
the	O
Oscars	O
red	O
carpet	O
!	O
#Oscars2014	B-product
#fashion	O
#style	O
#actors	O
#stars	O

@elsa_key	O
Should	O
I	O
call	O
you	O
'	O
Elsa	B-person
'	O
rather	O
than	O
'	O
unnie	O
'	O
?	O

do	O
us	O
all	O
a	O
#Favor	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
#AbortYourself	O
@SandraFluke	O
@LGIVLG	O

I've	O
been	O
tweeting	O
about	O
relationships	O
alot	O
.	O
.	O
I'm	O
just	O
sick	O
of	O
hearing	O
the	O
same	O
relationship	O
problems	O
over	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
over	O
that	O
can	O
easily	O
be	O
resolved	O

@alisonbuckley	O
The	O
planet	O
has	O
lost	O
an	O
incredible	O
amount	O
of	O
glacial	O
ice	O
.	O
That	O
has	O
an	O
impact	O
.	O
@ElizMcQuern	O
@jbtalker	O
@jmbaird32	O
@NigelBritto	O

Thongs	O
,	O
stubbies	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
crop	O
tops	O
banned	O
!	O
A	O
new	O
dress	O
code	O
released	O
for	O
NSW	B-place
public	O
school	O
#teachers	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
what	O
were	O
your	O
teachers	O
'	O
fashion	O
faux	O
pas	O
?	O

.	O
@johndavidblake	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
few	O
good	O
generals	O
-	O
including	O
the	O
Croat	O
Svetozar	B-person
Boroevic	I-person
http://t.co/LKblVCueMd	O
http://t.co/fDGJqwlZi8	O

#QPR	O
-	O
a	O
faded	O
,	O
used	O
Armani	B-organization
suit	O
,	O
bought	O
for	O
20	O
times	O
it's	O
market	O
value	O
,	O
ambling	O
down	O
a	O
crowded	O
beach	O
wondering	O
why	O
women	O
won't	O
look	O
at	O
him	O

Money	B-product
Aint	I-product
A	I-product
Problem	I-product
-	O
(	O
Dirty	O
)	O
from	O
-	O
Listen	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
Download	O
@captainco9	O
http://t.co/LE3RXDbq0g	O

@lrjwtravel	O
from	O
Texas	B-place
currently	O
in	O
Arkansas	B-place

Latest	O
#MRSBulletin	B-product
available	O
online	O
!	O
Organic	O
nanoparticles	O
for	O
drug	O
delivery	O
and	O
imaging	O
-	O
-	O
http://t.co/xuQuFleU3M	O
@gopalrrao	O
#materials	O

#fashion	O
#love	O
Cobalt	O
-	O
from	O
He	O
Spoke	O
Style	O
-	O
Men's	O
Style	O
,	O
Fashion	O
,	O
Grooming	O
,	O
Tips	O
and	O
AdviceI've	O
talked	O
recently	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/YfCMHGKxJC	O

God	O
Bless	O
You	O
too	O
bro	O
!	O
!	O
RT	O
"	O
@DJSPINALL	O
:	O
God	O
bless	O
@iamSMADE	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
"	O

Anddddd	O
farm	O
rant	O
over	O
.	O
Sorry	O
guys	O
I'm	O
just	O
kinda	O
a	O
big	O
supporter	O
of	O
farmers	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
farming	O
especially	O
since	O
I	O
live	O
on	O
a	O
farm	O
.	O

RT	O
@Numptei	O
:	O
This	O
months	O
cheese	O
club	O
fuelled	O
my	O
run	O
today	O
#cheeseglut	O
#cheeseclub	O
@TheRiserBerko	O
;	O
)	O

Girls	O
call	O
everyone	O
boo	O
that's	O
annoying	O

@levelsofhaze	O
@NickSommers	O
mind	O
literally	O
blown	O
af	O

big	O
accounts	O
are	O
so	O
lucky	O
it's	O
unfair	O

Birthday	O
in	O
May.	O
Just	O
wait	O
on	O
it	O
#GeminisWeAre	O
#May25th	O

@RicoShades	O
Shit	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
a	O
lot	O
brother	O
man	O

RT	O
@classystilinski	O
:	O
@flawlessbreeze	O
icon	O
:	O
10	O
/	O
10	O
header	O
:	O
10	O
/	O
10	O
bio	O
:	O
10	O
/	O
10	O
un	O
:	O
10	O
/	O
10	O
you're	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
favs	O
.	O
ily	O

RT	O
@esfahanhanim	O
:	O
We	O
r	O
choking	O
on	O
gas	O
,	O
people	O
still	O
pushing	O
forward	O
against	O
Polis	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
Tomas	B-person
in	O
Izmir	B-place
-	O
maybe	O
5	O
,	O
000	O
-	O
rough	O
estimate	O
!	O

Guys	O
it's	O
pat	B-person
Tillman	I-person
.	O
I	O
confirmed	O
it	O

*	O
blocked	O
*	O
RT	O
@IjebuPrincesss	O
:	O
Making	O
Indomie	O
with	O
egg	O
duvet	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
Quite	O
eggzited	O
.	O

Chrysler	B-organization
is	O
hiring	O
Predictive	O
ER	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
amp	O
;	O
D	O
Estimator	O
-	O
-	O
Auburn	B-place
Hills	I-place
,	O
MI	O
http://t.co/HhGPqtB2Vg	O
#WorkForChrysler	O

RT	O
@TOPFLIGHTDOE	O
:	O
@witchaprettyass	O
guuuud	O
morning	O
!	O
!	O

@Greenfaery	O
:-(	O
Hope	O
it's	O
easily	O
sorted	O

He's	O
just	O
the	O
best	O
.	O
CC	O
:	O
@D1scourse	O
RT	O
@BrianKWTX	O
Karl	O
Hess	O
just	O
tossed	O
Tim	O
Miles	O
in	O
an	O
NCAA	O
Tournament	O
game	O
#KingKarl	O

my	O
phone	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O

@singhpk99	O
@RedNationRising	O
@Rickmayhem	O
WE	O
NEED	O
TO	O
STEP	O
UP	O
THEN	O
.	O
CANT	O
COUNT	O
ON	O
THEM	O
!	O

Bakit	O
seashells	O
?	O
Hahahaha	O
di	O
ko	O
gets	O

okay	O
i	O
made	O
a	O
fansite	O
list	O
for	O
mark	O
lol	O

chris	B-person
asking	O
the	O
other	O
inmates	O
'	O
visitors	O
to	O
buy	O
loyal	O
:(	O
(	O
(	O
rochelle	B-person
i	O
fucking	O
hate	O
you	O

@AustinMahone	O
what	O
percentage	O
is	O
you're	O
phone	O
at	O
?	O
!	O
?	O
!	O
?	O
!	O
?	O
!	O
?	O
!	O
?	O
!	O

@cupcakedojb	O
queria	O
o	O
s3	O
)	O
:	O
but	O
nao	O
tenho	O
$	O
$	O
tempo	O
$	O
$	O
de	O
ir	O
comprar	O
hfjgxhj	O

Ohoooo	O
"	O
@Masethekid	O
#np	O
Jealousy	O
@akaworldwide	O
cc	O
nhingirikini	B-person
"	O

@HIORHEYHAZZA	O
I	O
KNOW	O
ITS	O
HORRIBLE	O

Poll	O
:	O
GOP's	O
Gardner	O
Just	O
a	O
Whisker	O
Behind	O
Udall	B-person
in	O
Colo	O
.	O
Senate	O
Race	O
http://t.co/zRU6fuJuHN	O
via	O
@Newsmax_Media	O

Superwoman	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
I	O
still	O
have	O
to	O
Ace	O
my	O
exam	O
and	O
outgrow	O
the	O
people	O
around	O
me	O

OK	O
,	O
well	O
if	O
you	O
haven't	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
tell	O
by	O
my	O
last	O
few	O
tweets	O
-	O
people	O
of	O
#yeg	O
CHECK	O
OUT	O
#TasteofIceland	O
-	O
amazing	O
foods	O
!	O

@SoBendito	O
you're	O
looking	O
for	O
@matt_levine	O
(	O
who	O
I'm	O
unfollowing	O
for	O
that	O
equities	O
comment	O
)	O
http://t.co/JlrM8ce76s	O

@Rodriguez5_	O
thanks	O
homie	O
!	O
Haters	O
are	O
motivators	O
!	O

Move	O
to	O
sell	O
-	O
off	O
Tesco	B-organization
store	O
in	O
North	B-place
Lincolnshire	I-place
welcomed	O
-	O
Scunthorpe	B-organization
Telegraph	I-organization
http://t.co/X0Azhe0PFR	O
#Lincolnshire	O

@fxsyoungestz	O
alrd	O
had	O
a	O
practice	O
princess	O
.	O
Just	O
laying	O
without	O
breathing	O
?	O
:p	O

@Basketballinc1	O
too	O
bad	O
you're	O
still	O
ugly	O

I	O
hate	O
to	O
admit	O
to	O
@cmckeon15	O
that	O
FSU	B-organization
girls	O
are	O
top	O
3	O
talent	O
.	O

RT	O
@EW	O
:	O
'	O
Parks	B-product
and	I-product
Recreation	I-product
'	O
at	O
PaleyFest	O
:	O
Season	O
finale	O
is	O
'	O
bonkers	O
'	O
-	O
-	O
plus	O
video	O
of	O
the	O
show's	O
BIGGEST	O
fan	O
http://t.co/uhJYGEUFG4	O

Welp	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
gonna	O
be	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
:	O
/	O

Somebody	O
text	O
me	O
.	O
.	O
Phone	O
dryyyy	O

@Exchange_FC	O
dont	O
blame	O
u	O
.	O
Delivery	O
is	O
expensive	O
to	O
highlands	B-place

Real	O
-	O
time	O
(	O
and	O
quite	O
beautiful	O
)	O
weather	O
map	O
shows	O
#CycloneLusi	O
'	O
s	O
path	O
heading	O
to	O
#NZ	B-place
&	O
gt	O
;	O
http://t.co/WLuegIzvI6	O

Civil	O
society	O
to	O
monitor	O
elections	O
in	O
Ghor	B-place
http://t.co/IDsaUixXQc	O

Please	O
Do	O
Not	O
Try	O
Ta	O
Run	O
Game	O
On	O
Me	O
.	O
.	O
She	O
Don't	O
Wanna	O
Be	O
A	O
Freak	O
Nomo	O
.	O
@MigosATL	O

@Karlcastan	O
Lol	O
.	O
Yes	O
Karl	B-person
but	O
usually	O
when	O
I	O
get	O
up	O
the	O
sun	O
is	O
up	O
!	O

ie	O
.	O
-	O
Glad	O
I'll	O
be	O
speaking	O
truths	O
when	O
I	O
tell	O
my	O
future	O
son	O
you	O
can	O
be	O
a	O
loser	O
in	O
highschool	O
and	O
still	O
marry	O
the	O
hottest	O
girl	O
in	O
your	O
class	O

@tommyfawuy	O
situasinya	O
juga	O
bisa	O
beda	O
.	O
Banyak	O
pemain	O
bintang	O
di	O
tim	O
Argentina	B-place
dibanding	O
tim	O
Portugal	B-place
.	O

RT	O
@benjamingaines	O
:	O
Tufte	B-person
:	O
Sports	O
analytics	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
good	O
day	O
,	O
is	O
about	O
the	O
subtlety	O
and	O
inherent	O
beauty	O
of	O
sports	O
.	O
#SSAC14	B-other

RT	O
@DBdarma	O
:	O
"	O
You	O
taught	O
me	O
why	O
hurricanes	O
are	O
named	O
after	O
people	O
.	O
"	O
-	O
Unknown	O

@dibutler	O
that'd	O
be	O
rad	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
open	O
.	O

@benelwell	O
Alas	O
,	O
phone	O
cam	O
didn't	O
get	O
it	O
through	O
grubby	O
library	O
windows	O
.	O

Thought	O
-	O
Driven	O
or	O
Heart	O
-	O
Driven	O
-	O
News	O
-	O
Bubblews	O
|	O
@scoopit	O
http://t.co/PZQTvQQNl2	O

http://t.co/F1KbbMl2ts	O
"	O
couple	O
new	O
things	O
to	O
try	O

@eluzhun	O
@AbbyMartin	O
@piersmorgan	O
I	O
couldn't	O
disagree	O
more	O
based	O
on	O
what	O
got	O
her	O
there	O
.	O
He's	O
already	O
a	O
fool	O
,	O
she	O
allowed	O
the	O
BS	O
to	O
stand	O
.	O

At	O
lavish	O
SXSW	O
festival	O
,	O
some	O
tech	O
influencers	O
opt	O
for	O
smaller	O
,	O
quieter	O
http://t.co/k6b46u37nP	O
H	O
/	O
T	O
@jgombita	O

:	O
Ujian	O
Allah	O
pada	O
hamba	O
yang	O
terus	O
menjadi	O
leka	O
.	O
Adakah	O
kita	O
salah	O
seorang	O
daripadanya	O
?	O

Anything	O
the	O
#Oscars	B-product
can	O
do	O
,	O
we	O
can	O
do	O
better	O
!	O
#Afghanistan	B-place
#SelfieOlympics	O
http://t.co/mWWU1i6eFw	O

@Piensalo___	O
anything	O
anyone	O
does	O
for	O
me	O
aye	O
I	O
appreciate	O
it	O
.	O
I'm	O
not	O
gonna	O
lie	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
sweet	O
of	O
you	O
to	O
do	O
.	O

@hotgirlsday	O
what	O
a	O
true	O
sexy	O
gal	O

RT	O
@FLOCKAfierce	O
:	O
I've	O
learned	O
that	O
looks	O
rarely	O
matter	O
when	O
it	O
comes	O
to	O
cheating	O
and	O
side	O
bishes	O
.	O

Nail	O
salon	O
tomorrow	O
,	O
much	O
needed	O
!	O

@iObey_donuts	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
idea	O
Omg	O
sorry	O

http://t.co/fX7CtFHulp	O
2971	O
notes	O
am	O
i	O
popular	O
yet	O
?	O

@SHANICEsideup	O
pakyu	O
sinasabi	O
ko	O
lang	O
HAHA	O
momol	O
asap	O
pls	O

RT	O
@Kaylen_Bedford	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
fucking	O
bored	O

(	O
Montreal	B-place
,	I-place
Canada	I-place
)	O
6th	O
-	O
ranked	O
trend	O
:	O
#habs	O

Quinn	B-person
gonna	O
get	O
caught	O
up	O
2	O

RT	O
@just_nubian	O
:	O
I'm	O
always	O
stressing	O
myself	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
just	O
need	O
to	O
breathe	O
.	O

Andriy	B-person
Parubiy	I-person
,	O
security	O
cncl	O
head	O
:	O
call	O
on	O
all	O
who	O
want	O
2	O
serve	O
Ukraine	B-place
2	O
do	O
their	O
duty	O
and	O
join	O
National	O
Guard	O
.	O
Training	O
starts	O
this	O
week	O

DTN	O
Stock	O
Market	O
:	O
Search	O
for	O
Missing	O
Plane	O
Faces	O
Steep	O
New	O
Challenges	O
-	O
New	O
York	O
Times	O
:	O
Indian	O
ExpressSearch	O
f	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/ylkdcr3DUR	O

at	O
night	O
+	O
twitter	O
+	O
bed	O
+	O
cuddle	O
+	O
phone	O
+	O
relax	O
=	O
STARVING	O

RT	O
@Vibxs	O
:	O
Appreciate	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
,	O
before	O
its	O
gone	O
.	O

follow	O
my	O
instagram	B-product
i'll	O
follow	O
back	O
http://t.co/5H8s9pjIrb	O

Pulau	O
Cipir	O
ini	O
disebut	O
juga	O
Pulau	O
khayangan	O
atau	O
Pulau	O
Kuipir	O
dan	O
dalam	O
bahasa	O
belanda	O
juga	O
disebut	O
Kujiper	O
#Sejarah3Pulau	O

Come	O
on	O
#PakCricket	B-organization
#PakvSL	O

sorry	O
love	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
don't	O
really	O
care	O
.	O

@4yourvets	O
thank	O
u	O
4	O
#following	O
me	O
ur	O
#militaryservice	O
2	O
#USA	B-place
ur	O
#singing	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
#songwriting	O
contribution	O
to	O
#Americas	O
#heroes	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
#volunteering	O
!	O

@gabbyxnoud	O
ewww	O
omg	O
:	O
(	O
so	O
embarrassed	O
but	O
I	O
just	O
didn't	O
gafos	O
ja	O
feel	O
?	O

Cm	O
punk	O
look	O
anxious	O
yo	O

How	O
many	O
Chuck	B-person
Norris	I-person
pages	O
are	O
gonna	O
follow	O
me	O
?	O

@StillDMC	O
you	O
don't	O
dnt	O
want	O
this	O
issue	O
on	O
the	O
4	O
playa	O

@AfrahMedFood	O
I	O
actually	O
do	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
your	O
tactic	O
tacky	O
and	O
knew	O
a	O
pitch	O
was	O
coming	O
!	O

This	O
@TheColourist	O
album	O
is	O
pretty	O
awesome	O
.	O
Stream	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
show	O
at	O
@UHallDC	O
on	O
Friday	O
.	O
http://t.co/ri3yG8uEkk	O
#AllThingsGold	O

.	O
@FOX2News	O
10PM	O
.	O
ARE	O
POLICE	O
OFFICERS	O
ENCOURAGING	O
DETROITERS	O
TO	O
TAKE	O
THE	O
LAW	O
INTO	O
THIER	O
OWN	O
HANDS	O
?	O
ANOTHER	O
HOMEOWNER	O
SHOOTS	O
TO	O
KILL	O
.	O
WOULD	O
U	O
?	O

Ok	O
new	O
crush	O
:	O
JAMES	B-person
REID	I-person
:	O
"	O
&	O
gt	O
;	O
&	O
lt	O
;	O
3	O

My	O
boss	O
told	O
me	O
60	O
!	O
So	O
45	O
is	O
really	O
a	O
thirsty	O
number	O
but	O
who	O
not	O
gone	O
b	O
thirsty	O
fresh	O
outta	O
skoo	O

I	O
want	O
to	O
taste	O
alcohol	O
through	O
your	O
mouth	O
.	O

RT	O
@_Riece	O
:	O
My	O
phone	O
he	O
prolly	O
fell	O
to	O
read	O
a	O
text	O
RT	O
@ODAT_	O
:	O
Your	O
iphone	O
falls	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
ur	O
spouse	O
fall	O
down	O
what	O
do	O
u	O
pick	O
up	O
first	O
?	O

Badman	O
@Thatgurl_Efe	O
RT	O
@NomskyN	O
:	O
I'm	O
sure	O
the	O
thing	O
the	O
devil	O
is	O
most	O
disappointed	O
about	O
is	O
the	O
fact	O
that	O
Edo	O
people	O
pronounce	O
his	O
name	O
as	O

@netcitizen	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
charger	O
close	O
by	O
especially	O
with	O
camera	O
deamon	O

RT	O
@simiskimmed	O
:	O
to	O
me	O
big	O
sean	O
is	O
winning	O
the	O
most	O
out	O
of	O
all	O
these	O
celeb	O
couples	O
.	O

music	O
withdrawal	O
is	O
a	O
real	O
thing	O
and	O
i	O
have	O
it	O
and	O
it's	O
fucking	O
awful	O

@inrickmansworth	O
@hornetboy84	O
@RickyFestival	O
now	O
there's	O
a	O
thought	O
,	O
possibly	O
I	O
love	O
Ricky	O
Week	O

We	O
are	O
live	O
again	O
#GenevaMotorShow	B-other
http://t.co/cyd6vlY9de	O

@radiantjustin	O
yeah	O
and	O
idk	O
what	O
happened	O
after	O
that	O

Tell	O
Ya	O
Bitch	O
We	O
Some	O
YOUNG	O
RICH	O
HOMIES	O

/	O
/	O
Heading	O
on	O
out	O
.	O
Be	O
back	O
for	O
21	O
:	O
00	O
-	O
GMT	O
-	O
Till	O
then	O
~	O
Ciao	O
!	O
#JokersOffine	O
http://t.co/OfC8pAYCKc	O

The	O
big	O
Lockerbie	B-place
story	O
the	O
Telegraph	B-organization
is	O
running	O
with	O
is	O
basically	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
Der	B-organization
Spiegel	I-organization
did	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
witness	O
,	O
in	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
1997	O
!	O

RT	O
@surfedoutruger	O
:	O
#blessed	O
and	O
#breathing	O

Reminder	O
to	O
come	O
see	O
us	O
at	O
booth	O
8212	O
@expowest	O
this	O
weekend	O
!	O
#newavitae	O
#instantgo	O
#caffeinewater	O

@Emcat93	O
Doesn't	O
feel	O
like	O
my	O
week	O
in	O
London	B-place
was	O
a	O
full	O
week	O
.	O
And	O
no	O
on	O
the	O
camera	O
.	O
It's	O
probably	O
in	O
my	O
big	O
bag	O
.	O

@GhareeboAjeeb	O
Kar	O
lia	O
karo	O
.	O
Abhi	O
tak	O
wo	O
bunkabab	O
tak	O
na	O
khilaya	O
.	O

Former	O
NSA	B-organization
Whistleblower	O
Sheds	O
Light	O
on	O
the	O
Science	O
of	O
Surveillance	O
[	O
Q	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
A	O
]	O
:	O
Scientific	O
American	B-place
http://t.co/iu2MHZRpwE	O

@rafavalbuena	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
picture	O
earlier	O
today	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
unit	O
/	O
brigade	O
they	O
are	O
from	O
?	O
@Liberationtech	O
@orvtech	O

AAP	O
nominee	O
Anjali	B-person
Damania	I-person
has	O
immovable	O
property	O
of	O
Rs	O
3	O
.	O
50	O
crore	O
:	O
http://t.co/5Mx2tSeuoD	O

@ByRJRoan	O
Great	O
point	O
.	O
But	O
those	O
lotteries	O
are	O
run	O
by	O
each	O
state's	O
gov't	O
with	O
presence	O
in	O
that	O
municipality	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
huge	O
gray	O
area	O
.	O

#NewsNOW	O
in	O
Toronto	B-place
:	O
@PMHarper	O
takes	O
part	O
in	O
moderated	O
Q	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
A	O
session	O
at	O
Prospectors	O
and	O
Developers	O
conference	O
.	O

Can't	O
be	O
witcha	O
if	O
I	O
don't	O
trust	O
ya	O

Pretty	O
sweet	O
TJ	B-person
Warren	I-person
poster	O
page	O
in	O
today's	O
print	O
edition	O
thanks	O
to	O
@LeithCars	O
http://t.co/c8QwNEZZUD	O

@SiedVanRiel	O
OMG	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
he	O
answered	O
.	O
#BestDayEver	O
#Madisonism	O

Hitler	B-person
poderia	O
ter	O
sido	O
jesus	B-person
cristo	I-person

RT	O
@crewvatto	O
:	O
Justin	B-person
Bieber	I-person
ft	O
.	O
Miley	B-person
Cyrus	I-person
,	O
por	O
favor	O
.	O

IM	O
SO	O
NERVOUS	O
I	O
WANNA	O
BARF	O
http://t.co/zjHR28RDuV	O

@For6et	O
@BCakesx	O
you	O
weird	O
as	O
fuck	O
nigga	O

Refueling	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
(	O
@	O
Brix	O
)	O
http://t.co/OkzWWMa46I	O

RT	O
@umjosee_	O
:	O
Guys	O
don't	O
worry	O
@Levi_PerryID	O
replied	O
to	O
my	O
message	O
and	O
Idc	O
if	O
it's	O
weird	O
http://t.co/LCcnb7pElh	O

@KimTateSports	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
happy	O
about	O
that	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
my	O
Xolos	O
!	O

RT	O
@TheMarcoLoya	O
:	O
Planning	O
jasons	B-person
bachelor	O
.	O
Whoever	O
is	O
invited	O
,	O
just	O
know	O
you're	O
about	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
sickest	O
party	O
you've	O
ever	O
been	O
in	O

@sam_batalon	O
not	O
that	O
being	O
poor	O
means	O
you're	O
happy	O
,	O
just	O
that	O
being	O
happy	O
doesn't	O
mean	O
being	O
"	O
rich	O
"	O
monetarily	O

My	O
heart	O
stumbles	O
on	O
things	O
I	O
don't	O
know	O
.	O

@gxccihemmings	O
MADDIE	B-person
HOW	O
DO	O
YOU	O
GET	O
IT	O
TO	O
TELL	O
YOU	O
WHEN	O
THEY	O
FOLLOWED	O
SOMEONE	O
?	O

RT	O
@COLEGrlLngStory	O
:	O
The	O
way	O
my	O
bed	O
feels	O
right	O
now	O
&	O
gt	O
;	O

@GoodbyeClutter	O
Not	O
serving	O
up	O
coffee	O
this	O
year	O
,	O
but	O
supporters	O
of	O
the	O
#modo8k	O
and	O
big	O
@modo_carcoop	O
fans	O
!	O

@FlyGuyRyyy	O
nobody	O
see	O
u	O
.	O
.	O
Drink	O
bleach	O

@marta3030	O
me	O
puedes	O
twittear	O
su	O
cabecera	O
?	O

MY	O
COUSIN	O
IS	O
HERE	O
KDBNCB	O

Julia	B-person
is	O
running	O
da	O
4x800	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
da	O
cake	O

RT	O
@HoodDisciplesYo	O
:	O
Hopefully	O
wen	O
ur	O
boy	O
gets	O
to	O
heaven	O
dey	O
got	O
sum	O
size	O
ninez	O
http://t.co/doyaxqKQO0	O

@GagaInjectsMe	O
HSHSJSJS	O
PE	O
.	O
SHJS	O
.	O
LEE	O
UNO	O

katanya	O
smartphone	O
kok	O
masih	O
lemot	O
aja	O
.	O

But	O
I	O
don't	O
wanna	O
live	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
reading	O
into	O
every	O
word	O
you	O
say	O
.	O
.	O

@lisariemers	O
Do	O
add	O
the	O
details	O
to	O
the	O
#Greenwich	B-place
@Netmums	O
#familyfriendly	O
#Restaurant	O
section	O
:)	O
http://t.co/IeyqCd88lh	O

@valsparchamp	O
Have	O
any	O
pics	O
of	O
Senden	B-person
with	O
the	O
trophy	O
?	O
#pgatour	B-other
#valsparchampionship	B-other

Diangkat	O
dari	O
kisah	O
nyata	O
titik	O
balik	O
penyelamatan	O
seni	O
era	O
Nazi	O
RT	O
@gilsasoy	O
@humadilangit	O
@boyasboyas	O
@brightnus	O
@isaiyas	O
@ottyrancajale	O

How	O
do	O
I	O
go	O
on	O
private	O
help	O

RT	O
@Karachi_Post	O
:	O
Bail	O
of	O
52	O
year	O
old	O
man	O
arrested	O
in	O
connection	O
with	O
murder	O
of	O
Dr	B-person
Imran	I-person
Farooq	I-person
extended	O
till	O
July	O
.	O
#London	B-place
#Karachi	O

RT	O
@eigergigas	O
:	O
May	O
magpapaedit	O
ng	O
video	O
,	O
sana	O
cash	O
nalang	O
ibigay	O
wag	O
food	O
.	O
I	O
need	O
maneeeeeh	O
.	O
Hahahaha	O
.	O
Aww	O

RT	O
@petfurniture	O
:	O
submitted	O
without	O
comment	O
http://t.co/eokFpJ5vJz	O

NEW	O
:	O
Video	O
:	O
Drake	B-person
Performs	O
New	O
Song	O
In	O
Birmingham	B-place
http://t.co/IkfkIb9I2r	O

The	O
actual	O
lesson	O
for	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
RT	O
@xoGiaxo_	O
:	O
Blend	O
your	O
make	O
up	O
and	O
your	O
weave	O
.	O
Always	O
.	O

Louisville	B-place
a	O
4	O
?	O
?	O
!	O
?	O
!	O
?	O

@tomtuck01	O
haha	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
In	O
desperate	O
need	O
of	O
a	O
top	O
class	O
cb	O
though	O
!	O

@mspiratesocks	O
Well	O
played	O
my	O
learned	O
friend	O
.	O
*	O
golf	O
clap	O
*	O

By	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
2014	O
#Vestas	B-organization
expects	O
to	O
have	O
more	O
than	O
2	O
,	O
000	O
workers	O
in	O
#Colorado	B-place
http://t.co/3iLJ3QBch3	O

.	O
@OfficialNihat	O
spamlayin	O
sunu	O
arkadaslar	O
.	O
Fake	O
nihat	O
dogan	O
bu	O
.	O

YES	O
MILEY	B-person
ON	O
ELLEN	B-person
AKDJDK	O
http://t.co/omZPHO5Pxs	O

To	O
decide	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
level	O
of	O
choice	O
is	O
to	O
take	O
resonsibility	O
for	O
your	O
life	O
.	O
-	O
Arbie	B-person
Dale	I-person
.	O
More	O
CHOICE	O
Quotes	O
at	O
http://t.co/mai1fw0VFK	O

im	O
so	O
emotional	O
lmao	O
k	O
bye	O

Russian	O
troops	O
take	O
over	O
Ukraine	B-place
&	O
amp	O
;	O
#	O
39	O
;	O
s	O
Crimea	B-place
region	O
http://t.co/oMQAbUqvZz	O
Don't	O
you	O
just	O
wish	O
we	O
could	O
nuke	O
Russia	B-place
sometimes	O
?	O

RT	O
@ProjectBieberBR	O
:	O
#BieberNews	O
Nova	O
tatuagem	O
do	O
Justin	O
http://t.co/VHZ9jMxJXo	O

N	B-organization
'	I-organization
Joy	I-organization
e	O
-	O
cig	O
ad	O
on	O
payphone	O
:	O
"	O
Making	O
cigarettes	O
as	O
obsolete	O
as	O
the	O
payphone	O
.	O
"	O
That's	O
like	O
a	O
tapeworm	O
calling	O
you	O
fat	O
from	O
inside	O
your	O
gut	O
.	O

Can	O
I	O
have	O
Miley's	B-person
voice	O
pls	O

New	O
Hong	B-place
Kong	I-place
Disneyland	O
Pins	O
featuring	O
everyone's	O
favorite	O
bear	O
,	O
Duffy	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/i9voKPhp3k	O

I	O
liked	O
a	O
@YouTube	O
video	O
from	O
@iphonemaster323	O
http://t.co/c7n6AR2u5T	O
Hot	O
Theme	O
iQuartZ	B-product
for	O
iOS7	B-product

RT	O
@SpursFeathers	O
:	O
Now	O
the	O
chant	O
has	O
changed	O
to	O
"	O
just	O
like	O
Dabo	O
"	O

Come	O
party	O
with	O
me	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
the	O
IYH	O
fam	O
.	O
http://t.co/WjXrnacMgT	O

De	O
Deense	O
bondscoach	O
Morten	O
Olsen	O
zorgde	O
op	O
Wembley	O
na	O
afloop	O
voor	O
enige	O
consternatie	O
door	O
te	O
zeggen	O
:	O
'	O
Good	O
luck	O
in	O
Brasil	B-place
.	O
You'll	O
need	O
it	O
.	O
'	O

This	O
just	O
in	O
!	O
#vinyl	O
#records	O
#soundtracks	O
#80s	O
#musicals	O
#opera	O
#classics	O
http://t.co/ZrZyHS6H0y	O

@BieberAriLove	O
am	O
i	O
annoying	O
you	O
or	O
something	O
?	O
if	O
i	O
am	O
sorry	O
:)	O
im	O
just	O
really	O
bored	O
and	O
my	O
twitter	B-product
is	O
dead	O
.	O

RT	O
@Keriooo_	O
:	O
I	O
swear	O
some	O
cancers	O
kill	O
me	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

@CHIEF_KEE_	O
mimi	B-person
,	O
niecy	B-person
,	O
jamal	B-person
.	O
.	O
regular	O
,	O
wya	O
?	O

@nathaanvi	O
diumumkan	O
setiap	O
hari	O
Selasa	O
:)	O

Sikattttt	O
RT	O
@TebeReza20	O
:	O
Situ	O
ga	O
lagi	O
main	O
petak	O
ngumpet	O
,	O
tapi	O
kenapa	O
ngumpetnya	O
dipikiran	O
aku	O
terus	O
-	O
.	O
-	O

RT	O
@_TayKayShay	O
:	O
you	O
will	O
ALWAYS	O
meed	O
me	O
before	O
i	O
need	O
you	O
any	O
given	O
day	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
lets	O
not	O
forget	O
it	O
.	O

Good	O
news	O
for	O
Anglers	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
Hunters	O
:	O
@CanadianTire	O
is	O
creating	O
pro	O
-	O
shops	O
to	O
expand	O
hunting	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
fishing	O
stock	O
!	O
http://t.co/Ve79jtWGhv	O
via	O
@OODMag	O

RT	O
@FurqonAshari	O
:	O
spesial	O
untuk	O
hari	O
spesial	O
gikwang	O
.	O
.	O
#openfollow	O
for	O
fg	O
/	O
fb	O
acc	O
.	O
.	O
rt	O
juseyo	O
^	O
^	O

@SoldierKidrauhl	O
wait	O
that	O
wasn't	O
even	O
bad	O
tho	O

Ima	O
shooter	O
wit	O
sum	O
shooters	O
I	O
ah	O
never	O
pay	O
for	O
dat	O

RT	O
@TheXpeK	O
:	O
@uhShadeY	O
I	O
was	O
still	O
being	O
breast	O
fed	O

chk	O
my	O
last	O
rt	O
"	O
@pinky_nikky	O
:	O
Cc	O
and	O
let	O
d	O
devil	O
be	O
put	O
to	O
shame	O
"	O
@Lt_timbus	O
:	O
Lmaooo	O
.	O
They	O
aff	O
expose	O
twitter	O
celeb	O
.	O
Just	O
200naira	O
"	O
"	O

If	O
you	O
seriously	O
want	O
to	O
change	O
your	O
circumstance	O
,	O
you	O
need	O
to	O
take	O
definitive	O
action	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
so	O
.	O
Just	O
wanting	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/bwIiDrqs21	O

Girls	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
All	O
I	O
really	O
want	O
is	O
girls	O
.	O

Y3ny	O
lo	O
'	O
9ay3ha	O
kan	O
9dg	O
bykoon	O
thor	O

RT	O
@andreamuhlach	O
:	O
hi	O
happy	O
birthday	O
!	O
check	O
your	O
messages	O
,	O
love	O
youu	O
x	O
@reynabismar	O

RT	O
@Miromurr	O
:	O
http://t.co/CTq6AXdYbj	O
Har	O
blogget	O
om	O
#LibraryBox	O
-	O
en	O
lokal	O
digital	O
bokhylle	O

@251Karim	O
w	O
smaaa3ny	O
salaaam	O
,	O
aywa	O
el	O
salaam	O
el	O
bl	O
eed	O
dh	O
.	O
.	O

@77ADE_	O
@United99_	O
@SkelMCFC	O
I	O
deserved	O
that	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
You	O
dragged	O
me	O
round	O
with	O
a	O
Wigan	O
fan	O
.	O
.	O

How	O
The	O
Cost	O
Of	O
College	O
Went	O
From	O
Affordable	O
To	O
Sky	O
-	O
High	O
http://t.co/1gmJHIPu2O	O
Via	O
@nprnews	O
:	O

I	O
talked	O
to	O
@RepCohen	O
for	O
this	O
story	O
http://t.co/pMOF2oNieF	O

140305	O
The	O
Story	O
of	O
Chen	B-person
and	O
Xiumin	B-person
http://t.co/wcf7FQlVLh	O
(	O
v	O
:	O
Lyyynaa	O
)	O
-	O
LK	O

@AfiqahRafi	O
fiqah	O
nak	O
karangan	O
kerjaya	O
tu	O
~	O
.	O
~	O

Arsedor	O
Rear	O
Guard	O
:	O
Faramanski	O
,	O
Vermlindon	O
,	O
Flamdring	O
Foehammer	O
,	O
Oakenshield	O
,	O
Oxlade	O
-	O
Celeborn	O
,	O
Gnaffer	O
,	O
Sanogolin	O

@envymendes	O
him	O
and	O
acacia	B-person
are	O
cute	O
i	O
want	O
their	O
friendship	O
but	O
she's	O
so	O
pretty	O
and	O
he's	O
so	O
beautiful	O
i	O
don't	O
get	O
it	O

The	O
Five	O
Super	O
Powers	O
of	O
#Marketing	O
http://t.co/equijgo26c	O
#CMO	O
#Strategy	O
via	O
@HarvardBiz	O

Coleman	B-person
not	O
looking	O
to	O
spare	O
Bale	B-person
http://t.co/Dpz0mbmONn	O
#Soccer	O

Change	O
in	O
the	O
market	O
?	O
Read	O
our	O
analysis	O
.	O

There's	O
a	O
place	O
that	O
serves	O
all	O
you	O
can	O
eat	O
sushi	O
on	O
a	O
conveyor	O
belt	O
in	O
Frederick	B-place
.	O
My	O
hometown	O
just	O
got	O
so	O
much	O
cooler	O
.	O

I	O
rather	O
get	O
money	O
than	O
have	O
Birthday	O
parties	O
just	O
having	O
one	O
that's	O
all	O

IM	O
DRUELING	O
ON	O
THE	O
SHIRT	O
I	O
WAS	O
GOING	O
TO	O
WEAR	O
TO	O
SCHOOL	O
TOMORROW	O
http://t.co/gToNDvJZfg	O

Socorro	O
comi	O
tanto	O
que	O
agora	O
to	O
enjoada	O
-	O
_	O
-	O

daerah	O
pelosok	O
yg	O
blm	O
terjangkau	O
brking	O
wkwkwkw	O

Doug	B-person
Christie	I-person
seems	O
like	O
he's	O
a	O
good	O
dude	O
!	O
#BBWLA	B-product

Done	O
drinkin	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
slowin	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
dank	O
too	O

@Jazz803	O
you	O
really	O
can't	O
,	O
I	O
just	O
like	O
your	O
enthusiasm	O
,	O
confidence	O
,	O
and	O
energy	O
when	O
you	O
slang	O
them	O
long	O
ass	O
arms	O
.	O

Just	O
reached	O
home	O
like	O
10	O
minutes	O
ago	O
.	O
.	O
_	O
.	O

wkwkw	O
iyuh	O
xD	O
RT	O
@	O
/	O
SoneVIETNAMs	O
:	O
lol	O
this	O
V	O
-	O
pose	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
=	O
.	O
=	O
http://t.co/1ZN6ZrhW0H	O

Ngedonlot	O
masih	O
lama	O
udah	O
ngantuk	O
aja	O
krik	O
.	O

RT	O
@deniseviolaplay	O
:	O
@CountryWatch1	O
@ericpaslay	O
love	O
him	O
!	O
!	O
Defiantly	O
love	O
to	O
hear	O
him	O
sing	O
this	O
song	O
!	O

Angry	O
pro	O
-	O
life	O
moms	O
:	O
Girl	B-organization
Scouts	I-organization
CEO	O
lying	O
about	O
Planned	O
Parenthood	O
connection	O
(	O
VIDEO	O
)	O
http://t.co/WcfDGctuiy	O
#LifeSiteNews	O

Lmao	O
RT	O
@Karabo_KB	O
:	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
RT	O
@_Mrena	O
:	O
Chelsea	B-organization
can	O
eat	O
a	O
dick	O
.	O
We're	O
giving	O
City	B-organization
those	O
3	O
points	O
tied	O
in	O
a	O
pretty	O
pink	O
bow	O
.	O

TALKING	O
ABOUT	O
CATE	B-person
OH	O
KAHAKAVABAS	O

RT	O
@TrendsWinnipeg	O
:	O
Alex	B-person
Forrest	I-person
,	O
@wpgfirefighter	O
is	O
now	O
trending	O
in	O
#Winnipeg	B-place
http://t.co/l8AKAC27C7	O

have	O
you	O
ever	O
eaten	O
so	O
many	O
sour	O
patch	O
kids	O
that	O
the	O
roof	O
of	O
you	O
mouth	O
hurts	O
like	O
the	O
sugar	O
scratched	O
it	O
or	O
something	O
idk	O
bc	O
thats	O
me	O
rn	O

@TaylorKropp	O
most	O
definitely	O
will	O
thanks	O
man	O
!	O
Keep	O
me	O
posted	O
with	O
everything	O
!	O

Guys	O
#StationTheFilm	O
is	O
releasing	O
on	O
March	O
28	O
!	O
@saadkhancs	O
@centerstageblr	O
#PVR	O
!	O
!	O
Trailer	O
:	O
http://t.co/QYpzqGiLti	O
http://t.co/8Zvb3U5jEa	O

RT	O
@ShairraAlpasan	O
:	O
@DavidArchie	O
!	O
Are	O
you	O
coming	O
back	O
here	O
in	O
the	O
Philippines	B-place
?	O
:)	O

Lmfao	O
RT	O
@MsThisPlane	O
:	O
Vegetarian	O
bitches	O
don't	O
suck	O
dick	O
?	O

@ashleighstar4	O
@TylerLayneMusic	O
yeah	O
that	O
was	O
me	O
!	O
:)	O

so	O
.	O
.	O
are	O
the	O
buses	O
not	O
running	O
?	O
am	O
I	O
missing	O
something	O
?	O

me	O
and	O
@baaberauhl	O
are	O
having	O
a	O
prayer	O
circle	O
for	O
justin	B-person
so	O
he	O
wont	O
get	O
targeted	O
by	O
the	O
paps	O
or	O
get	O
into	O
trouble	O
everyone	O
is	O
welcomed	O
:p	O

RT	O
@liliimccoy	O
:	O
@tylergrosso	O
i	O
never	O
got	O
naked	O
for	O
you	O
tho	O

Download	O
@shots	O
now	O
!	O
!	O
That's	O
amazing	O
.	O
.	O
Follow	O
me	O
(	O
m	O
_	O
katina	O
)	O
and	O
follow	O
@justinbieber	O
(	O
bizzle	O
)	O
http://t.co/Owr0LNKhV1	O
6	O

@NiallOfficial	O
YOU	O
LOOK	O
SO	O
SERIOUS	O

"	O
@Fascinatingpics	O
:	O
Because	O
eating	O
is	O
hard	O
work	O
http://t.co/JbsFtNCrkx	O
"	O
dor	O
!	O
!	O
:	O
3	O

@meganguza	O
that	O
works	O
for	O
me	O
!	O
See	O
you	O
around	O
then	O
.	O
Let	O
me	O
know	O
if	O
anything	O
changes	O
.	O

#CEF	B-organization
El	O
Nacional	O
1	O
Deportivo	O
Quito	O
1	O
[	O
Fecha	O
7	O
]	O

@martha_rhodes	O
yeyesyyesyeysheysytyesyyeys	O

RT	O
@CBS11Stew	O
:	O
Sun	O
coming	O
up	O
.	O
It's	O
geitting	O
active	O
at	O
the	O
ballpark	B-place
.	O
.	O
@cbsdfw	O
#OpeningDay	O
coverage	O
all	O
morning	O
!	O
http://t.co/hgufqgeHga	O

@padinpadin	O
@sutramaya	O
alolo	O
comel	O
je	O
nak	O
kacau	O
kite	O
.	O
Tapi	O
kite	O
x	O
suke	O
kacau	O
org	O
dating	O
berdua	O
kat	O
Delicious	O
.	O
;	O
)	O

RT	O
@Mishal4U	O
:	O
InFo	O
&	O
gt	O
;	O
Dunya	O
Ki	O
Pehly	O
Water	O
Proof	O
Ghari	O
(	O
Watch	O
)	O
Switzerland	B-place
Ne	O
1926	O
Main	O
Tyar	O
Kee	O
.	O
&	O
gt	O
;	O
Vitaman	O
C	O
1913	O
Main	O
Daryafat	O
Howa	O
.	O

Visit	O
your	O
local	O
#Menards	B-organization
retailer	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
this	O
T	O
&	O
amp	O
;	O
B	O
solution	O
can	O
turn	O
your	O
deck	O
into	O
a	O
better	O
summer	O
hangout	O
.	O
http://t.co/LDPxqzPBIw	O

Goodnight	O
Clearfield	B-place
,	I-place
PA	I-place
#bangarang	O
http://t.co/lZby2Edpot	O

I	O
AM	O
MEXICAN	B-other
WHY	O
DO	O
I	O
LOOK	O
ASIAN	B-other
FML	O
http://t.co/7BVHdT2YRh	O

#MakeUpTips	O
|	O
#Maquillaje	O
#HD	O
#MakeUp	O
#Airbrush	O
#MUA	O
http://t.co/qMrZdmqVZz	O

@iiivb	O
Yes	O
I'm	O
doing	O
some	O
coaching	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
to	O
help	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
interested	O
in	O
my	O
methodology	O
or	O
just	O
looking	O
for	O
more	O
edge	O
;	O
-	O
)	O

WE	O
WERE	O
SCREAMING	O
"	O
"	O
SEX	O
NA	O
"	O
"	O
"	O
"	O
ANG	O
TAGAL	O
MAG	O
SEX	O
"	O
"	O
AND	O
I	O
S2g	O
thE	O
GUARD'S	O
REACTION	O
WAS	O
SO	O
PRICELESS	O

@codykeene1	O
@RyanBorlaug	O
yeah	O
I	O
can	O
see	O
it	O
lol	O